<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teenager found unconscious in the park leads to a missing persons investigation; Benson must help Noah come to terms with the past when he questions the origins of his birth.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723010000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The squad is on edge as Carisi waits for a verdict in Maddie's kidnapping case; Benson tries to help the Flynn family pick up the pieces of their broken life.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A runaway bride calls the SVU for help on the day of her wedding; Rollins pitches in on her day off.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Agent Sykes struggles to cope on the anniversary of her sister's disappearance; Benson suspects a cold case from Manhattan could help her get closure.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU searches for a pattern assailant before his crimes escalate to murder; Fin must contend with a suspect's aggrieved son; Carisi is pressured to close the case quickly to ease public concern.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives investigate a school shooting that left three students dead and link the rifle used in the killings to a gun store serving as the headquarters of a white supremacist group.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a series of rapes is linked to a speed-dating service, Benson goes under cover and discovers Mike Jergens (Dean Cain) is the assailant.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a runaway teenage girl is found badly beaten, doctors discover the beating killed her unborn child, and detectives begin to question the father.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An investigation into the near-fatal beating of a 12-year-old boy uncovers a female suspect whose trial becomes about the rights of same-sex parents.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the accused killer of a teen's mother is released due to lack of evidence, the youth exacts his own justice by killing the man.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Burgess works an extra shift at the 13th District and gets caught in the middle of a drive-by attack on refugees; the team works together to track down the shooter and uncover the true motive behind the attack.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Returning from furlough, Torres goes under cover in a tense and high-stakes drug trafficking case.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Atwater turns to an unlikely source of support when a string of jewelry store robberies shakes his confidence.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Intelligence teams up with ASA Chapman to take on an abduction case involving a teenager; the case hits close to home for Voight, leading him to take a personal interest in finding justice for the victim.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>An ongoing case hits close to home for Voight as Intelligence teams up with an SVU detective to track down a prolific offender.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Upton brings SVU detective Petrovic back into the fold to help with the investigation of a tender-age kidnapping.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Torres' personal involvement with an informant jeopardizes his safety and threatens to expose an undercover operation.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>The members of Firehouse 51 struggle to cope when one of their own dies in a fire; as Lts. Casey and Severide blame each other for the tragedy, Casey also secretly goes through a separation.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide hides his serious shoulder injury as he tries to rescue a construction worker from a collapsed building; two teens are trapped in a vehicle.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723190000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey must decide whether to turn in a cop's son who paralyzed a teen in a drunken-driving accident; Severide learns he has a fractured vertebra; Mills is torn between his mother and the job.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Chief Boden faces accusations that he abandoned a homeless man to die in a warehouse fire; Severide helps an elderly woman; Detective Voight tries to convince Casey not to testify against his son; Shay has to face her ex during a call.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey must face the consequences of confronting Detective Voight; Dawson faces disciplinary action; Severide reaches out to an old friend about his injury.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Dawson receives help from a girl she saved; Detective Voight is determined to get Casey to retract his statement.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">John Wick: Chapter 4</title>
    <desc>With the price on his head ever increasing, legendary hit man John Wick takes his fight against the High Table global as he seeks out the most powerful players in the underworld, from New York to Paris to Japan to Berlin.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724023300 +0000" stop="20250724060600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">John Wick: Chapter 4</title>
    <desc>With the price on his head ever increasing, legendary hit man John Wick takes his fight against the High Table global as he seeks out the most powerful players in the underworld, from New York to Paris to Japan to Berlin.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724060600 +0000" stop="20250724070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A tip leads Benson and Cragen to the body of a 7-year-old boy, missing since 1980, and the detectives think the new information was a ploy to help the suspected killer, on death row for another murder, delay his execution.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724070400 +0000" stop="20250724080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenage girl disappears, a psychic (guest star Martin Short) is brought into the investigation.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724080200 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 9-year-old girl calls for help, claiming to be held hostage in a strange room for four days, many believe it is a prank, but Detective Benson feels otherwise.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After a high-school student is brutally assaulted, detectives interview a suspect who becomes enraged and attacks Detective Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Hetty is being tortured by her captors in Vietnam; Eric and Nell find a clue to her whereabouts; the team organizes a rescue mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>NCIS joins Hetty's team from the Vietnam War in a dangerous rescue mission to save Hetty from her captors in Vietnam; Mosley calls in Nell's sister to assist the team in Los Angeles with processing evidence connected to Hetty's time in Vietnam.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Callen and Sam pull Granger's daughter, former spy Jennifer Kim, from witness protection to help the team locate a spy who has obtained an arsenal of bomb materials.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The dismembered body of a woman is found in a junkyard, and detectives must determine who killed her and who attempted to harvest organs from her corpse.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While Fin deals with colleagues who accuse his son of murder, he learns a secret that reveals more about his family's relationship with Darius.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A serial pedophile murders members of a family and kidnaps the two younger children.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman believes her young son was molested by her husband; an online pedophile site is investigated.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An unstable woman stops taking medication and mows down 10 people with her car; a former rock star wages an anti-psychiatric-drug campaign.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Fin investigate the disappearance of two high-school students from a museum field-trip; Stabler meets his new partner.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Beck (Connie Nielsen) are unable to build a case against a rape suspect until a new witness (Leslie Caron) steps forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an assailant rapes his victim twice, detectives Stabler and Beck (Connie Nielsen) link the case to other victims of multiple rapes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>ADA Novak calls upon detective Benson, still under cover in Oregon, to present evidence that will strengthen the case against a brutal rapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A car accident involving two foster children leads detectives Beck and Stabler to the foster parents and questionable medical practices involving a controversial "rebirthing" therapy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250724230000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman is found dead in Central Park, and when the medical examiner can find no apparent cause of death, Stabler starts investigating the victim's husband (Chris Sarandon) and his friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A 15-year-old with a sexually transmitted disease says he caught it from his teacher (Melissa Joan Hart); Benson and Stabler uncover dark secrets while searching into the pair's lives.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-25</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723013000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the MLB following Boston Red Sox @ Philadelphia Phillies.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 16 of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a 171km route from Montpellier to the top of Mont Ventoux. Who will thrive on the famed Beast of Provence?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Fight Flashback</title>
    <desc>A look back at the pulsating clash between Tyron Woodley and Stephen Thompson at UFC 205 in New York from November 2016.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Fight Flashback</title>
    <desc>We look back at this classic bantamweight clash between Cody Garbrandt and Dominick Cruz at UFC 207 at the T-Mobile Arena in Paradise, Nevada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>The River Crouch in Essex plays host to 250 sea anglers in a one-day boat fishing competition. Presented by Andy Ford with additional commentary from Henry Gilbey.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 16 of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a 171km route from Montpellier to the top of Mont Ventoux. Who will thrive on the famed Beast of Provence?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>In the 1990's, Jeff Steber created what was widely credited as being the first ever downhill bike. Shaun Palmer, one of the sport's most important athletes, secured its legacy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723063000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What I Wore</title>
    <desc>Former Arsenal and England goalkeeper David Seaman describes his passion for football via the shirts which have defined his life.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Estonia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tri-Series International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>New Zealand and South Africa go head-to-head in the fifth match of this T20 Tri-Series at Harare Sports Club.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>SailGP Highlights from the 2025 Emirates Great Britain Sail Grand Prix, as a fleet of 12 F50s battle it out for victory in the tumultuous waters of the Solent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the carnage on the final day of the third Test between West Indies and Australia at Sabina Park, as the hosts slumped to their worst-ever Test innings.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723101500 +0000" stop="20250723103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review all the action from the Tour de France up until the second rest day. Also, we look ahead to the 2025 Tour de France Femme.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723103000 +0000" stop="20250723113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 16 of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a 171km route from Montpellier to the top of Mont Ventoux. Who will thrive on the famed Beast of Provence?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723113000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de France</title>
    <desc>Action from stage 17 of the 2025 Men's Tour de France, as the riders set off on a flat 160km route through the Rhone Valley from Bollene to Valence.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723191500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action between San Francisco Giants and Atlanta Braves at Truist Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723191500 +0000" stop="20250723193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723193000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723231600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Minnesota Twins face Los Angeles Dodgers at Dodgers Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250723231600 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as Philadelphia Phillies host Boston Red Sox at Citizens Bank Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724021500 +0000" stop="20250724023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tom Aspinall's Fight Lab</title>
    <desc>Heavyweight champion Tom Aspinall previews UFC Fight Night at Etihad Arena, where middleweights Robert Whittaker and Reinier de Ridder will face-off.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724023000 +0000" stop="20250724030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>In the 1990's, Jeff Steber created what was widely credited as being the first ever downhill bike. Shaun Palmer, one of the sport's most important athletes, secured its legacy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724030000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Supercars Championship and day one of the NTI Townsville 500 at Reid Park in Queensland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Supercars Championship and day two of the NTI Townsville 500 at Reid Park in Queensland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 17 of the 2025 Men's Tour de France, as the riders set off on a flat 160km route through the Rhone Valley from Bollene to Valence.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724063000 +0000" stop="20250724073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round nine of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Leicester Lions and Sheffield Tigers face-off at Hydroscand Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724073000 +0000" stop="20250724083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724083000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the unique legacy of footballing dynasties in the Premier League; where talent, passion, and pride are passed from one generation to the next. From the iconic saves of Peter Schmeichel to the rise of his son Kasper, the goal-scoring legacy of Ian Wright carried on by son's Shaun and Bradley, and the Lampards' deep-rooted Chelsea connection, this episode explores the bonds that tie foo</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 17 of the 2025 Men's Tour de France, as the riders set off on a flat 160km route through the Rhone Valley from Bollene to Valence.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de France</title>
    <desc>Stage 18 of the 2025 Tour de France sees the riders confront 5,450m of elevation on a tough 171km mountain route from Vif to Col de la Loze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724161500 +0000" stop="20250724163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review all the action from the Tour de France up until the second rest day. Also, we look ahead to the 2025 Tour de France Femme.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724163000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jens Voigt: Cycling Legacy</title>
    <desc>We delve into the legacy of legendary German cyclist Jens Voigt, who was renowned for his aggressive riding style and multiple Tour de France stage wins.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724201500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as Baltimore Orioles face Cleveland Guardians at Progressive Field.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724201500 +0000" stop="20250724204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Off The Bat</title>
    <desc>All the latest action from Major League Baseball wrapped up, featuring the league's top hitters and pitchers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724204500 +0000" stop="20250724211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724211500 +0000" stop="20250724213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Rewind</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724213000 +0000" stop="20250724223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>The River Crouch in Essex plays host to 250 sea anglers in a one-day boat fishing competition. Presented by Andy Ford with additional commentary from Henry Gilbey.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250724223000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 10 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>In the 1990's, Jeff Steber created what was widely credited as being the first ever downhill bike. Shaun Palmer, one of the sport's most important athletes, secured its legacy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723043000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What I Wore</title>
    <desc>Liverpool and England legend John Barnes describes his passion for football via the shirts which have defined his life.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Men's and Women's Lead finals at the 2025 IFSC Climbing World Cup in Madrid, Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as ladder leaders Collingwood play Fremantle at the MCG. The Magpies won 97-83 when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723073000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League Geelong Cats face St Kilda at GMHBA Stadium. The Cats have lost their past two meetings with the Saints.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Adelaide Crows face Gold Coast Suns at Adelaide Oval. The Suns have lost all 11 matches they have played at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723103000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round nine of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Leicester Lions and Sheffield Tigers face-off at Hydroscand Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>The River Crouch in Essex plays host to 250 sea anglers in a one-day boat fishing competition. Presented by Andy Ford with additional commentary from Henry Gilbey.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723173000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the second T20 International between West Indies and Australia at Sabina Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723190000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 17 of the 2025 Men's Tour de France, as the riders set off on a flat 160km route through the Rhone Valley from Bollene to Valence.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Training Day</title>
    <desc>Peter Crouch and Joe Cole dust off their boots to spend the day training at Premier League side Brentford.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723203000 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>In the 1990's, Jeff Steber created what was widely credited as being the first ever downhill bike. Shaun Palmer, one of the sport's most important athletes, secured its legacy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723213000 +0000" stop="20250723223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>SailGP Highlights from the 2025 Emirates Great Britain Sail Grand Prix, as a fleet of 12 F50s battle it out for victory in the tumultuous waters of the Solent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723223000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as Philadelphia Phillies host Boston Red Sox at Citizens Bank Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724021500 +0000" stop="20250724024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724024500 +0000" stop="20250724044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the second Test between West Indies and Australia at National Cricket Stadium in Grenada, as the visitors looked to clinch this three-match series.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724044500 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB classic action from the All-Star Highlights 1973 from the Royals Stadium in Kansas City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the second T20 International between West Indies and Australia at Sabina Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Essendon meet GWS Giants at Marvel Stadium. Can the Giants extend their winning streak to five games?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724073000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Brisbane Lions take on Western Bulldogs at the Gabba. The Dogs will need a big upset to keep in the top-eight hunt.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724091500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724091500 +0000" stop="20250724123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Hawthorn play Carlton.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724123000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 10 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724143000 +0000" stop="20250724153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>West Indies look to bounce back from their crushing 3-0 Test series defeat as they take on Australia in the first T20 International at Sabina Park in Kingston, Jamaica.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724153000 +0000" stop="20250724163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the second T20 International between West Indies and Australia at Sabina Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724163000 +0000" stop="20250724173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Men's and Women's Lead finals at the 2025 IFSC Climbing World Cup in Madrid, Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724173000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the second leg of the 1993/94 UEFA Champions League second round tie between Manchester United and Galatasaray at Old Trafford. The controversial first leg finished 3-3.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Hawthorn play Carlton.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724193000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the unique legacy of footballing dynasties in the Premier League; where talent, passion, and pride are passed from one generation to the next. From the iconic saves of Peter Schmeichel to the rise of his son Kasper, the goal-scoring legacy of Ian Wright carried on by son's Shaun and Bradley, and the Lampards' deep-rooted Chelsea connection, this episode explores the bonds that tie foo</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the recent action from the Premier League, including Newcastle v Man City, Ipswich v Aston Villa and Man United v Tottenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the recent action from the Premier League, featuring Aston Villa v Man United, Arsenal v Southampton and Crystal Palace v Liverpool.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the recent action from the Premier League, including Liverpool v Chelsea, Tottenham v West Ham and Newcastle v Brighton.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250724230000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tri-Series International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>New Zealand and Zimbabwe meet in the sixth match of this T20 Tri-Series at Harare Sports Club.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723010000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Mubadala Citi DC Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Rock Creek Park Tennis Center in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Mubadala Citi DC Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Rock Creek Park Tennis Center in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-25</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723183000 +0000" stop="20250723185200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723185200 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>From Letzigrund Stadium in Zurich.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723213000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250723233000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724183000 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Atlantic Motorsport Park in Mill Village, Nova Scotia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250724233000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-25</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Action from the Sprint Race at the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno. Can anyone stop Marc Marquez from claiming an 11th Sprint win of the season?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723003000 +0000" stop="20250723013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno. Ducati's Marc Marquez will be chasing a fifth consecutive Grand Prix win.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723013000 +0000" stop="20250723023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723023000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at a classic Premier League clash.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 2014/15 New Year's Day Premier League meeting between Tottenham and Chelsea at White Hart Lane, featuring eight goals in total, including two for in-form Harry Kane.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We relive this six-goal classic between Manchester United and Manchester City from the 2014/15 season. Sergio Aguero got the visitors off to a flying start.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>West Ham and Arsenal locked horns in the Premier League at Upton Park. This London derby took on added significance with both clubs in the hunt for a Champions League spot.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723043000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit this Boxing Day clash between Bournemouth and West Ham. Marko Arnautovic and Callum Wilson were among the scorers in this six-goal thriller.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Newcastle United face Mikel Arteta's Arsenal at St. James' Park. The Magpies are winless in their last five league games.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723063000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Arne Slot's Liverpool face Unai Emery's Aston Villa at Anfield. Liverpool have won five of their last six home games against the Villans.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Leicester City welcome Enzo Maresca's Chelsea to King Power Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723093000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Premier League action as Everton face table toppers Liverpool in the final league Merseyside derby at Goodison Park. The Toffees claimed a 2-0 win in this fixture last season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Ange Postecoglou's out-of-form Tottenham travel to face bottom side Southampton at St Mary's Stadium. The Saints have won just one of their last 28 Premier League games.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723123000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Pep Guardiola's struggling Manchester City travel to the West Midlands to face an Aston Villa side who beat them 1-0 at Villa Park last season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Champions League final between Luis Enrique's Paris Saint-Germain and Simone Inzaghi's Inter at Allianz Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723153000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Conference League final between Manuel Pellegrini's Real Betis and Enzo Maresca's Chelsea at Stadion Wroclaw.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Europa League final between Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United at San Mames Stadium in Bilbao.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723183000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 10 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the unique legacy of footballing dynasties in the Premier League; where talent, passion, and pride are passed from one generation to the next. From the iconic saves of Peter Schmeichel to the rise of his son Kasper, the goal-scoring legacy of Ian Wright carried on by son's Shaun and Bradley, and the Lampards' deep-rooted Chelsea connection, this episode explores the bonds that tie foo</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723203000 +0000" stop="20250723213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the recent action from the Premier League, including Man United v Liverpool, Newcastle v Tottenham, and West Ham v Man City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723213000 +0000" stop="20250723223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the recent action from the Premier League, including Tottenham v Arsenal, Southampton v Man United and Wolves v Newcastle.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723223000 +0000" stop="20250723233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the recent action from the Premier League, featuring Man City v Arsenal, Aston Villa v Wolves and West Ham v Chelsea.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250723233000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the unique legacy of footballing dynasties in the Premier League; where talent, passion, and pride are passed from one generation to the next. From the iconic saves of Peter Schmeichel to the rise of his son Kasper, the goal-scoring legacy of Ian Wright carried on by son's Shaun and Bradley, and the Lampards' deep-rooted Chelsea connection, this episode explores the bonds that tie foo</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724000000 +0000" stop="20250724010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Estonia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724010000 +0000" stop="20250724020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 10 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 2009-10 season and a dramatic clash between Manchester City and Arsenal. The match was full of controversy, with Emmanuel Adebayor at the centre of it.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>One of this derby fixture's greatest ever contests. This Old Trafford thriller twists and turns right up to the game's very last kick.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724043000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at a classic match from the Premier League, as Manchester United hosted Manchester City at Old Trafford in the 2011-12 season. It would be a stunning result for the visitors.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Thomas Frank's Brentford host Mikel Arteta's Arsenal at Gtech Community Stadium. The Bees are winless in their last five against the Gunners.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724063000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Tottenham Hotspur face Newcastle United at Tottenham Hotspur Stadium. The Magpies have won four of their last five league games against Spurs.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Premier League action as Nottingham Forest meet Liverpool at the City Ground. Forest are looking to complete their first league double over Liverpool since the 1962/63 campaign.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724093000 +0000" stop="20250724103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tri-Series International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>New Zealand and South Africa go head-to-head in the fifth match of this T20 Tri-Series at Harare Sports Club.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724103000 +0000" stop="20250724143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tri-Series International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>New Zealand and Zimbabwe meet in the sixth match of this T20 Tri-Series at Harare Sports Club.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724143000 +0000" stop="20250724153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724153000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>David Moyes makes his return to the Goodison Park dugout as Everton host Aston Villa at Goodison Park. The Toffees are winless in their last 11 league games against the Villans.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Premier League action as Newcastle United face Wolverhampton Wanderers at St James' Park. The Magpies are looking to complete their first league double over Wolves since 1905/6.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724183000 +0000" stop="20250724184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Rewind</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best of the action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724184500 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review all the action from the Tour de France up until the second rest day. Also, we look ahead to the 2025 Tour de France Femme.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage 18 of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders confront 5,450m of elevation on a tough 171km mountain route from Vif to Col de la Loze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724203000 +0000" stop="20250724223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval in Barbados, which featured a lethal performance by pace bowler Josh Hazlewood.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250724223000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the second Test between West Indies and Australia at National Cricket Stadium in Grenada, as the visitors looked to clinch this three-match series.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723003000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Hawthorn go head-to-head with Port Adelaide at UTAS Stadium. The Power have won their past four matches against the Hawks.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Sydney Swans face North Melbourne at the SCG. The Swans have beaten their Kangaroos in their last nine matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League as Carlton take on Melbourne at the MCG. Both sides come into this contest with a 6-11 record.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ally's Social Club</title>
    <desc>Ally McCoist interviews legendary football manager Sir Alex Ferguson about his life and career.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723053000 +0000" stop="20250723063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round nine of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Leicester Lions and Sheffield Tigers face-off at Hydroscand Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723063000 +0000" stop="20250723073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto3 Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno. Britain's Scott Ogden will be looking to ride to his first victory of the season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723073000 +0000" stop="20250723083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno. Can Britain's Jake Dixon claim a third win of the season?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723083000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Action from the Sprint Race at the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno. Can anyone stop Marc Marquez from claiming an 11th Sprint win of the season?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno. Ducati's Marc Marquez will be chasing a fifth consecutive Grand Prix win.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Supercars Championship and day one of the NTI Townsville 500 at Reid Park in Queensland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Supercars Championship and day two of the NTI Townsville 500 at Reid Park in Queensland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Estonia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>SailGP Highlights from the 2025 Emirates Great Britain Sail Grand Prix, as a fleet of 12 F50s battle it out for victory in the tumultuous waters of the Solent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC: More Than Machine</title>
    <desc>Tensions reach a boiling point at the end of the season as the M-Sport team takes on Central Europe and Japan. And, their marquee driver reveals his plans for 2025 and beyond.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723173000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>We revisit the best tries of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, including Tom Roebuck, Kalaveti Ravouvou, Cadan Murley and many others.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: FISU Summer World University Games</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the Women's Volleyball Gold Medal Game at the 2025 Summer World University Games in Rhine-Ruhr.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723203000 +0000" stop="20250723213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round nine of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Leicester Lions and Sheffield Tigers face-off at Hydroscand Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723213000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fight Week</title>
    <desc>A review of UFC 318 at Smoothie King Center, New Orleans, featuring Dustin Poirier's retirement fight against old foe Max Holloway.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the second T20 International between West Indies and Australia at Sabina Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as West Coast Eagles meet Richmond at Optus Stadium. The Tigers won 90-81 when these sides last met in round nine.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724003000 +0000" stop="20250724020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League Geelong Cats face St Kilda at GMHBA Stadium. The Cats have lost their past two meetings with the Saints.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as ladder leaders Collingwood play Fremantle at the MCG. The Magpies won 97-83 when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Adelaide Crows face Gold Coast Suns at Adelaide Oval. The Suns have lost all 11 matches they have played at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724053000 +0000" stop="20250724063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>SailGP Highlights from the 2025 Emirates Great Britain Sail Grand Prix, as a fleet of 12 F50s battle it out for victory in the tumultuous waters of the Solent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724063000 +0000" stop="20250724073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>The River Crouch in Essex plays host to 250 sea anglers in a one-day boat fishing competition. Presented by Andy Ford with additional commentary from Henry Gilbey.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724073000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 10 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 Superbike World Championship season opener at Phillip Island Grand Prix Circuit in Australia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Superbike World Championship highlights from the Portuguese Round at Autodromo Internacional do Algarve.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Dutch Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Czechia at Automotodrom Brno.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 Superbike World Championship at Cremona Circuit in Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 Superbike World Championship in Czech Republic, including an epic showdown between Nicolo Bulega and Toprak Razgatlioglu in race two.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Prosecco DOC United Kingdom Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship at Donington Park in Leicestershire.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: FISU Summer World University Games</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the Men's Volleyball Gold Medal Game at the 2025 Summer World University Games in Rhine-Ruhr.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724203000 +0000" stop="20250724233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC 318 at Smoothie King Center in New Orleans, featuring Dustin Poirier's retirement fight against old rival Max Holloway.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250724233000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A look back at the heavyweight bout between Derrick Lewis and Shamil Abdurakhimov from December 2016 in Albany. Francis Ngannou and Anthony Hamilton clashed in the co-main event.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of various sailing grand prix races from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723183000 +0000" stop="20250723185200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723185200 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>From Letzigrund Stadium in Zurich.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723213000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250723233000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724173000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The race heads to the Fraser Valley in B.C. where everyone has to hit the right notes, and a Face Off leaves one team in the penalty box.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Dirt Tour Racing</title>
    <desc>A look at the action from dirt tracks across the country.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724213000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250724233000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Sports</title>
    <desc>Discussions of the positive aspects of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-25</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723043000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">We the North: From Prehistoric to Historic</title>
    <desc>An exploration of key moments and developments from throughout the Raptors' organization's history; examine "We the North" movement that sparked a diverse community across the country, culminating in the 2019 NBA Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723063000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723073000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723083000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723093000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723103000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723113000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723123000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723133000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723143000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723153000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Pat McAfee Show</title>
    <desc>Former NFL punter Pat McAfee brings his humor and candor to the microphone to highlight the day's top stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Atlantic Motorsport Park in Mill Village, Nova Scotia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723183000 +0000" stop="20250723190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Dirt Tour Racing</title>
    <desc>A look at the action from dirt tracks across the country.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723190000 +0000" stop="20250723193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723193000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The race heads to the Fraser Valley in B.C. where everyone has to hit the right notes, and a Face Off leaves one team in the penalty box.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724000000 +0000" stop="20250724020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724023000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724043000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724073000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724083000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724093000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724103000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724113000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724123000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724133000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724143000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724153000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724163000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724173000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724183000 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">AFL Premiership Football</title>
    <desc>From Melbourne Cricket Ground in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724230000 +0000" stop="20250724233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250724233000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">We the North: From Prehistoric to Historic</title>
    <desc>An exploration of key moments and developments from throughout the Raptors' organization's history; examine "We the North" movement that sparked a diverse community across the country, culminating in the 2019 NBA Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723010000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723163000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: College Football Live</title>
    <desc>ESPN's daily college football show sharing reactions to the day's biggest stories and previews of each week's most important matchups. Kelsey Riggs and Jen Lada host alongside contributors Desmond Howard, Sam Acho, Greg McElroy and Pete Thamel.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723190000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723213000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Athletes Unlimited Softball League</title>
    <desc>From Rhoads Stadium in Tuscaloosa, Ala.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724010000 +0000" stop="20250724020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Dirt Tour Racing</title>
    <desc>A look at the action from dirt tracks across the country.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724173000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The race heads to the Fraser Valley in B.C. where everyone has to hit the right notes, and a Face Off leaves one team in the penalty box.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724213000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250724233000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-25</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's ODI match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723010000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's ODI match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723040000 +0000" stop="20250723050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723050000 +0000" stop="20250723060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723060000 +0000" stop="20250723070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723070000 +0000" stop="20250723080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723080000 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723093000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>4th Test, Day 1.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723124000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>4th Test, Day 1.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>4th Test, Day 1.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723173000 +0000" stop="20250723184000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: World Championship of Legends Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage of cricket action from the legends tournament held in Edgbaston, Birmingham, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723184000 +0000" stop="20250723191000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723191000 +0000" stop="20250723193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723193000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's ODI match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724000000 +0000" stop="20250724010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724010000 +0000" stop="20250724020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724030000 +0000" stop="20250724040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724040000 +0000" stop="20250724050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724050000 +0000" stop="20250724060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724060000 +0000" stop="20250724070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724070000 +0000" stop="20250724080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724080000 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724093000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>4th Test, Day 2.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724124000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>4th Test, Day 2.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>4th Test, Day 2.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724173000 +0000" stop="20250724184000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: World Championship of Legends Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage of cricket action from the legends tournament held in Edgbaston, Birmingham, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724184000 +0000" stop="20250724191000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724191000 +0000" stop="20250724193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724193000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from various cricket tournaments, where top-performing teams from different countries compete against each other to win the coveted title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250724230000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-25</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
