<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU searches for three women suspected of drugging and robbing wealthy men; the case leads to personal connections for both Benson and Kat.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702010000 +0000" stop="20250702020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Garland asks Benson to investigate an unusual domestic violence case when his neighbor is found injured.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702020000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While Fin and Phoebe make wedding plans, Benson and Rollins try to help a homeless single mother who's being trafficked in exchange for safe housing.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>As the investigation into a sex-for-housing scheme expands, Benson's loyalty to Garland is tested; Rollins and Carisi try to keep their witnesses on board when a powerful congressman is identified as a suspect.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The search for a missing witness leads Fin and Kat down a dangerous path; Chief McGrath puts pressure on Garland and Benson to get a conviction.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a serial killer who justifies his crimes with paranoid religious motivation. Richard Thomas and Karen Allen guest star.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler pairs with a bitter cop (David Keith) to track a serial rapist/murderer who was recently released from prison.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate the rape/murder of a woman whose stepfather is a judge (Keir Dullea) known for his harsh sentencing of sex offenders.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler investigate two rapes that appear to have been committed by the same man; Mary Beth Hurt and Henry Winkler guest star.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An ex-convict who sexually assaulted prostitutes appears to have been killed by a would-be victim, then another homicide suggests the woman may be a manipulative serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a string of brutal pharmacy robberies, and Halstead connects with one of the victims about their Army careers; Upton suspects there is more to the story and confides in Voight.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702110000 +0000" stop="20250702120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A murder pulls rookie officer Dante Torres into his own neighborhood; as Voight and Atwater help him navigate the case and manage tricky personal dynamics with wary neighbors, Torres realizes his life may be forever changed.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702120000 +0000" stop="20250702130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Upton's dogged pursuit of a missing teenage girl leads the team into a dark web of human trafficking; chief O'Neal becomes involved with the unit's investigation when it becomes evident his son, Sean, has a connection to the missing girl.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702130000 +0000" stop="20250702140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Atwater's reactions during a tense arrest are called into question; the team must dig in to uncover key evidence that could aid in the ongoing investigation and clear Atwater's name.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702140000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When actionable evidence finally surfaces against Sean O'Neal, Upton and the team work relentlessly to build a case in secret; they discover Sean is more elusive and dangerous than anticipated.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>To distract Intelligence from the investigation into his son, Chief O'Neal forces the team to handle a "dead fish" case; when that dead fish turns into a complicated heater case, Burgess is thrown back into difficult memories from her past.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702160000 +0000" stop="20250702170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After a shocking discovery, the team begins closing in on Sean O'Neal with every shred of evidence they can find; determined to keep his son out of prison, Chief O'Neal hires a lawyer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702170000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd gets a glimpse into Carver's chaotic personal life; Mouch and Herrmann receive an unexpected gift.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 hosts a Halloween open house; Kidd and Severide help a young girl after she gets kicked out of her home.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702190000 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Herrmann is tasked with fulfilling a man's dying wish; Kidd reflects on her Girls on Fire program after one of her students graduates from the Fire Academy; a heckler harasses Firehouse 51.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Detective Pryma asks for Severide's help on a case involving explosives; Gallo and Carver clash.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 prepares for their semi-annual firehouse inspection; Brett fights to save her paramedicine program; Commander Martin Pearce asks Severide for a favor.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Truck and squad clash after a tense call rescuing a doomsday prepper; Herrmann struggles with Cindy's diagnosis; Violet gives Brett and Gallo dating advice.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 helps Herrmann put on a school fundraiser; Carver's troubled brother comes to town; a grateful citizen is determined to thank Brett and Severide for saving his life.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cast Away</title>
    <desc>A corporate troubleshooter survives a plane crash to spend five years seeking out an existence on a deserted island before returning to civilization with an altered view of his old life and values.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703030000 +0000" stop="20250703040200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and Heather reunite, but their relationship is more complicated than ever.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703040200 +0000" stop="20250703050200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Members of Firehouse 51 are dismayed to learn their boundaries have been redrawn to overlap with an adjacent station, and problems quickly arise; Casey and Gallo hunt a missing piece of equipment; Brett and Foster find themselves at odds.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703050200 +0000" stop="20250703060200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A pest control problem forces the 51 team to temporarily bunk with Firehouse 20; all under the same roof, Casey clashes with Capt. Delaney, while Foster, Kidd and Brett fear Capt. Leone has it out for them; Boden mulls a procedural overhaul.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703060200 +0000" stop="20250703070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An estranged son and a former patient are the prime suspects in the murder of a prominent doctor and the rape of his wife.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703070100 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a corporate mogul is found murdered, evidence points to his son, whom the detectives suspect was seduced by his stepmother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The squad spends New Year's Eve tracking down an Amber Alert, and Carisi faces off against counselor Rafael Barba in an emotional courtroom battle.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A high-profile activist suspects her sister has been kidnapped by a hate group; Garland and Benson push for change with NYPD brass; Kat gets some good news.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cast Away</title>
    <desc>A corporate troubleshooter survives a plane crash to spend five years seeking out an existence on a deserted island before returning to civilization with an altered view of his old life and values.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The investigation of a young woman's death reveals that she and other women were recently accused of a raping a male stripper.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703140000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A boy, 6, is shot and then abandoned in an emergency room by his fearful mother, sending detectives in search of his missing family and the gunman.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Fin are forced to team up to investigate a rape-murder case in which a police officer (guest star Michael O'Keefe) might be the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703160000 +0000" stop="20250703170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Stabler races against time to determine if a convicted man on death row also murdered and raped another victim.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703170000 +0000" stop="20250703180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a cellist's (Tamara Gorski) orchestra conductor (Michael Nader) after she is brutally attacked in her apartment.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703180000 +0000" stop="20250703190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Assistant DA Cabot jeopardizes the detectives' careers and her own when she exceeds legal limits to collect evidence against a serial child-abuser.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703190000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the detectives find a baby's finger in a rape victim's purse, their investigation widens to encompass three generations of women harboring secrets.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate to determine whether a 22-year-old with Down syndrome is pregnant as a result of rape, as her mother contends.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a transsexual is found murdered in a church, suspicion falls on a priest (Eric Stoltz) who resigned from a parochial school after rumors of abuse.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler clash with an assistant U.S. attorney (Pam Grier) when their rape victim and their prime suspect disappear into witness protection.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250703230000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</title>
    <desc>On his 11th birthday Harry Potter learns he is the orphaned son of two wizards and is invited to attend Hogwarts School of Witchcraft &amp; Wizardry where he embarks on the adventure of a lifetime.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action as Chicago Cubs host Cleveland Guardians at Wrigley Field.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the MLB following Cleveland Guardians @ Chicago Cubs.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702033000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at Rally Greece and the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP: Racing on the Edge</title>
    <desc>An unprecedented look at SailGP and the sport's best athletes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702063000 +0000" stop="20250702064500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Rewind</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at the iconic TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702064500 +0000" stop="20250702084500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702084500 +0000" stop="20250702173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the first One Day International between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R Premadasa International Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702173000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Uncharted</title>
    <desc>After being abruptly cut from the US SailGP Team, Australian Jimmy Spithill is left with no team and plenty left to prove. What will this sailing legend do next?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Uncharted</title>
    <desc>After his retirement from sailing, Jimmy Spithill steps into uncharted waters as CEO of the newly formed Red Bull Italy SailGP Team. Can he lead his team in a bold new direction?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702183000 +0000" stop="20250702190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Uncharted</title>
    <desc>As Season 5 begins, the Red Bull Italy SailGP Team races against the clock to finish their boat and get their brand-new crew trained. Can they silence the critics?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702190000 +0000" stop="20250702191500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>The No Filter cameras capture all angles as Bath take the Gallagher Premiership Rugby crown in an epic 23-21 battle against Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702191500 +0000" stop="20250702193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We provide all the information you need to know about the upcoming Tour de France and Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702193000 +0000" stop="20250702203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702203000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoE</title>
    <desc>All the best action from the 2025 Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen, part of the MotoE season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action as Cleveland Guardians face off against Chicago Cubs at Wrigley Field.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703031500 +0000" stop="20250703034500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703034500 +0000" stop="20250703041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB classic action from the All-Star Highlights 1967 from Anaheim Stadium in California.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703041500 +0000" stop="20250703044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day two of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703044500 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Rewind</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at the iconic TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703083000 +0000" stop="20250703084500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We provide all the information you need to know about the upcoming Tour de France and Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703084500 +0000" stop="20250703091500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703091500 +0000" stop="20250703123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the AFL as North Melbourne face off against Western Bulldogs at Marvel Stadium in Melbourne.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703123000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703140000 +0000" stop="20250703143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoE</title>
    <desc>All the best action from the 2025 Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen, part of the MotoE season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703143000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA TCR World Tour</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action from the TCR World Tour in Monza.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703153000 +0000" stop="20250703163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Cycling</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from the 2025 Men's Giro d'Italia, as British rider Simon Yates secured a second Grand Tour title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703163000 +0000" stop="20250703180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>A presentation of the 23 teams taking part in the 2025 Men's Tour de France.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703180000 +0000" stop="20250703183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>An A to Z look at cycling's oldest and most prestigious Grand Tour, the Tour de France.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703183000 +0000" stop="20250703190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the Champions League semi final 1st leg between Manchester City and Real Madrid at the Etihad Stadium. Real haven't won any of their previous three trips to face City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703190000 +0000" stop="20250703221500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action as Colorado Rockies host Houston Astros at Coors Field.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703221500 +0000" stop="20250703224500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Off The Bat</title>
    <desc>All the latest action from Major League Baseball wrapped up, featuring the league's top hitters and pitchers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703224500 +0000" stop="20250703231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703231500 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We provide all the information you need to know about the upcoming Tour de France and Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP: Racing on the Edge</title>
    <desc>An unprecedented look at SailGP and the sport's best athletes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702013000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702043000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day one of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the dramatic 2000/01 UEFA Champions League final between Bayern Munich and Valencia at the San Siro in Milan. Bayern were chasing their first title in a quarter-century.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702053000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 2002/03 UEFA Champions League final between Juventus and AC Milan at Old Trafford. Paolo Maldini aimed to lift the trophy as captain, just as his father did in 1963.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 2004 final between Monaco and Porto in Gelsenkirchen. Porto were led by Jose Mourinho, who would leave the club to take over at Chelsea two days after the final.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702063000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day one of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702083000 +0000" stop="20250702093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the 2017 British Carp Angling Championships at Wraysbury, one of the most high profile competitions in the angling calendar.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702093000 +0000" stop="20250702103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Porsche Supercup Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Action from round four of the 2025 Porsche Supercup at the Red Bull Ring in Spielberg, Austria.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702103000 +0000" stop="20250702110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP: Racing on the Edge</title>
    <desc>An unprecedented look at SailGP and the sport's best athletes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702110000 +0000" stop="20250702120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">British National Road Championship Cycling</title>
    <desc>Cycling action from the Men's Elite Road Race in Aberystwyth, Wales.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702120000 +0000" stop="20250702130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702130000 +0000" stop="20250702143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702143000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>We revisit the best tries of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, including Tom Roebuck, Kalaveti Ravouvou, Cadan Murley and many others.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>Action from the Golden Trail World Series 2025, as the world's top trail runners take on the four-day Broken Arrow Skyrace at Palisades Tahoe, in Sierra Nevada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702153000 +0000" stop="20250702160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Relive Man City and Tottenham's Champions League quarter-final. It was a classic at the Etihad with seven goals, five of them coming in 17 pulsating minutes, and late VAR drama.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702160000 +0000" stop="20250702163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Revisit Tottenham's sensational UEFA Champions League semi-final second leg with Ajax at the Amsterdam Arena. Spurs' final hopes hung in the balance after a 1-0 first-leg defeat.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702163000 +0000" stop="20250702170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702170000 +0000" stop="20250702201500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action as Philadelphia Phillies host San Diego Padres at Citizens Bank Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702201500 +0000" stop="20250702211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Chicago Sky take on Los Angeles Sparks at Crypto.com Arena. Chicago won 97-86 in their previous meeting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702211500 +0000" stop="20250702213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702213000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day two of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702223000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>Action from the Golden Trail World Series 2025, as the world's top trail runners take on the four-day Broken Arrow Skyrace at Palisades Tahoe, in Sierra Nevada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Repco Supercars Championship highlights from the Betr Darwin Triple Crown.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Repco Supercars Championship highlights from the Betr Darwin Triple Crown.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703010000 +0000" stop="20250703023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703023000 +0000" stop="20250703034500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Born Racers</title>
    <desc>We meet Alex, Eddie, Cormac and Casey whose families have given up everything for them to reach the MotoGP Academy, from their marriages to the countries they call home.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703034500 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We provide all the information you need to know about the upcoming Tour de France and Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Chicago Sky take on Los Angeles Sparks at Crypto.com Arena. Chicago won 97-86 in their previous meeting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 5 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703063000 +0000" stop="20250703073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703073000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day two of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at Rally Greece and the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP: Racing on the Edge</title>
    <desc>An unprecedented look at SailGP and the sport's best athletes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703093000 +0000" stop="20250703103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Chicago Sky take on Los Angeles Sparks at Crypto.com Arena. Chicago won 97-86 in their previous meeting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703103000 +0000" stop="20250703104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Under the Lights</title>
    <desc>Relive the memorable European footballing nights for Manchester United at Old Trafford, including clashes with Barcelona, Real Madrid and AC Milan.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703104500 +0000" stop="20250703114500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the first One Day International between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R Premadasa International Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703114500 +0000" stop="20250703134500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703134500 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day one of the second Test between West Indies and Australia at National Cricket Stadium in Grenada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day three of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703223000 +0000" stop="20250703224500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best batting action from the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703224500 +0000" stop="20250703230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best bowling action from the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250703230000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the first One Day International between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R Premadasa International Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Wimbledon Tennis Primetime</title>
    <desc>Action and highlights from the day's matches at the 2025 Wimbledon Championships.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Wimbledon Match Point</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive wrapup of the winners and losers from the day's action at Wimbledon.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702213000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All-Star Selection Show</title>
    <desc>Players selected to compete in the 2025 MLB All-Star Game are announced.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Wrigley Field in Chicago.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703030000 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Semifinal.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703060000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Wimbledon Match Point</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive wrapup of the winners and losers from the day's action at Wimbledon.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703213000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702020000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702110000 +0000" stop="20250702120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702120000 +0000" stop="20250702130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702130000 +0000" stop="20250702140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702140000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702155200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702155200 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702183000 +0000" stop="20250702184600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702184600 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702213000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>From Energizer Park in St. Louis, Mo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703010000 +0000" stop="20250703020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703020000 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Semifinal.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703060000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703110000 +0000" stop="20250703120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703120000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703140000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703155200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703155200 +0000" stop="20250703180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703180000 +0000" stop="20250703183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703183000 +0000" stop="20250703185200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703185200 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703213000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702003000 +0000" stop="20250702013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto3 Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen. Can rookie Maximo Quiles secure back-to-back wins?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702013000 +0000" stop="20250702023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen. Can Manuel Gonzalez extend his lead at the top of the standings?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702023000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Action from the Sprint Race at the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands. Francesco Bagnaia claimed a dominant victory in this race last season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen. Can Ducati's Marc Marquez claim a third GP race win in a row?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Bournemouth host Tottenham Hotspur at the Vitality Stadium. The two meetings between these sides last season were goal-fests, with the away team winning 3-2 on both occasions.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702063000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Sheffield United entertain Everton at Bramall Lane. Both sides are looking for their first points of the Premier League season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto3 Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen. Can rookie Maximo Quiles secure back-to-back wins?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen. Can Manuel Gonzalez extend his lead at the top of the standings?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Action from the Sprint Race at the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands. Francesco Bagnaia claimed a dominant victory in this race last season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702103000 +0000" stop="20250702113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen. Can Ducati's Marc Marquez claim a third GP race win in a row?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702113000 +0000" stop="20250702123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Netherlands at TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702123000 +0000" stop="20250702140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action between Collingwood and West Coast Eagles at Marvel Stadium. Can the Eagles pull off a shock against the league leaders?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702140000 +0000" stop="20250702153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Fremantle and St Kilda go head-to-head at Optus Stadium. The Dockers are searching for a sixth win on the spin.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702153000 +0000" stop="20250702170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Richmond face Adelaide Crows at MCG. The Tigers have won four of their past five matches against the Crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702170000 +0000" stop="20250702173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702173000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA TCR World Tour</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action from the TCR World Tour in Monza.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702183100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702183100 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 5 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Porsche Supercup Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Action from round four of the 2025 Porsche Supercup at the Red Bull Ring in Spielberg, Austria.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702223000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP: Racing on the Edge</title>
    <desc>An unprecedented look at SailGP and the sport's best athletes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Bouldering and Lead finals in Innsbruck, Austria.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day two of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, as rowers vie for glory on the River Thames.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703003000 +0000" stop="20250703020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action between Collingwood and West Coast Eagles at Marvel Stadium. Can the Eagles pull off a shock against the league leaders?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703020000 +0000" stop="20250703033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Fremantle and St Kilda go head-to-head at Optus Stadium. The Dockers are searching for a sixth win on the spin.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703033000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Richmond face Adelaide Crows at MCG. The Tigers have won four of their past five matches against the Crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Wolverhampton Wanderers host Liverpool at Molineux Stadium. Wolves beat Liverpool 3-0 in this fixture last season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703063000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Burnley clash with Manchester United at Turf Moor. Man United have lost just one of their last 24 league games against promoted sides.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Aston Villa face Brighton at Villa Park. Aston Villa have won their last four top flight games against Brighton.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703093000 +0000" stop="20250703110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Luton Town host Tottenham at Kenilworth Road. This is the first meeting between Luton and Tottenham in any competition since 1992.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703110000 +0000" stop="20250703113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Relive Man City and Tottenham's Champions League quarter-final. It was a classic at the Etihad with seven goals, five of them coming in 17 pulsating minutes, and late VAR drama.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703113000 +0000" stop="20250703120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Revisit Tottenham's sensational UEFA Champions League semi-final second leg with Ajax at the Amsterdam Arena. Spurs' final hopes hung in the balance after a 1-0 first-leg defeat.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703120000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 5 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703143000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703160000 +0000" stop="20250703191500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action between Miami Marlins and Minnesota Twins at LoanDepot Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703191500 +0000" stop="20250703193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Rewind</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Netherlands at the iconic TT Circuit Assen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703193000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>Action from the Golden Trail World Series 2025, as the world's top trail runners take on the four-day Broken Arrow Skyrace at Palisades Tahoe, in Sierra Nevada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultra-Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>UTMB World Series highlights from the 2025 Salzburg Ultra Trail, taking participants through beautiful Austrian scenery and ending in the world-famous city of Mozart.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703223000 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the 2017 British Carp Angling Championships at Wraysbury, one of the most high profile competitions in the angling calendar.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 5 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702003000 +0000" stop="20250702020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Sydney Swans face Western Bulldogs at the SCG. Can the Dogs continue their top-eight push against a dangerous Swans side?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702020000 +0000" stop="20250702033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as Gold Coast Suns take on Melbourne at People First Stadium. The Demons now have little margin for error as they seek to keep their faint finals hopes alive.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702033000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as Hawthorn take on North Melbourne at UTAS Stadium. The Hawks have beaten the Kangaroos in their last six meetings by an average of 50 points.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Paulo Fonseca's AC Milan meet Lecce at San Siro. Milan have already scored 11 league goals in this term.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Napoli face Monza at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Napoli have won their first two home league games under Antonio Conte.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Inter welcome Paolo Vanoli's Torino to San Siro. Torino are unbeaten in their opening three league away games this season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Fiorentina face-off against AC Milan at Artemio Franchi Stadium. Fiorentina are unbeaten in ten of their last eleven home league games.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Empoli face-off against at Napoli at Stadio Carlo Castellani. Empoli are unbeaten in their last seven league home matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Ivan Juric's Roma face Inter at Stadio Olimpico. Roma have lost their last three home league games against Inter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702110000 +0000" stop="20250702120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Inter and Juventus face-off at San Siro. Can Thiago Motta's Juve side continue their unbeaten start to the Serie A season?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702120000 +0000" stop="20250702130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Raffaele Palladino's Fiorentina meet Ivan Juric's Roma at Artemio Franchi Stadium. Roma have not won any of their last three away league games against Fiorentina.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702130000 +0000" stop="20250702140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Antonio Conte's Napoli look to continue their promising start to the Serie A season as they welcome free-scoring Atalanta to Stadio Diego Armando Maradona.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702140000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Simone Inzaghi's Inter host Eusebio Di Francesco's Venezia at San Siro. Can the Winged Lions cause an upset against the champions?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between West Indies and Australia at Kensington Oval.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702170000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 2017/18 Premier League season as Manchester City win their third title, Mohamed Salah scores 32 goals for Liverpool and Stoke's top flight status ends.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 2018/19 Premier League season that was competitive until the very end, with fans captivated by an epic title race between Manchester City and Liverpool.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702190000 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 2019/20 Premier League season as a pandemic-disrupted season saw Liverpool win their first ever Premier League title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 2020/21 Premier League season as Manchester City regained the title and won their fifth Premier League title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit a memorable night at the Nou Camp as Barcelona faced Bayer Leverkusen in the last 16 second leg from the 2011/12 UEFA Champions League. Barca led 3-1 from the first leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250702213000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC 317 at T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas, featuring the lightweight title clash between Ilia Topuria and former champion Charles Oliveira.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703003000 +0000" stop="20250703021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Relive the exhilarating UFC middleweight bout between Michael Bisping and Kelvin Gastelum at the Mercedes-Benz Arena in Shanghai, China.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703021500 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A look back at classic UFC action from UFC EMEA 14.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fight Week</title>
    <desc>A review of UFC 317 at T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas, which featured the lightweight title clash between Ilia Topuria and former champion Charles Oliveira.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703043000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit a memorable night at the Nou Camp as Barcelona faced Bayer Leverkusen in the last 16 second leg from the 2011/12 UEFA Champions League. Barca led 3-1 from the first leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Ivan Juric's struggling Roma meet Vincenzo Italiano's Bologna at Stadio Olimpico. Bologna have won their last two league matches against Roma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703060000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as champions Inter face Antonio Conte's Napoli at San Siro. Napoli have won just one of their last 10 league matches against Inter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Napoli host Roma at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Lazio face Bologna at Stadio Olimpico.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the rescheduled Serie A match between Fiorentina and Inter at Artemio Franchi Stadium. Can the Nerazzurri get back to winning ways after a draw in the Milan Derby?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Marco Giampaolo's Lecce host Juventus at Stadio Via del mare. Can Thiago Motta's Juve side continue their unbeaten run in the league?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703110000 +0000" stop="20250703120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Thiago Motta's Juventus face Fabio Pecchia's Parma at Allianz Stadium. Can Parma cause a big upset and claim their second win of the season?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703120000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Cesc Fabregas' Como host Lazio at Stadio Giuseppe Sinigaglia. Como are unbeaten at home in the league so far this term.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Atalanta host AC Milan at Gewiss Stadium. Gian Piero Gasperini's Atalanta have scored at least two goals in each of their last 11 home games in the league.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703140000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action from the Derby del Sole between Napoli and Lazio at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Lazio are unbeaten in their last three league games against Napoli.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Bouldering and Lead finals in Innsbruck, Austria.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703160000 +0000" stop="20250703170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at Rally Greece and the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703170000 +0000" stop="20250703183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 5 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703183000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the AFL as North Melbourne face off against Western Bulldogs at Marvel Stadium in Melbourne.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC 317 at T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas, featuring the lightweight title clash between Ilia Topuria and former champion Charles Oliveira.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250703230000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Reloaded</title>
    <desc>We relive an action-packed UFC 223 as Khabib Nurmagomedov and Al Iaquinta battled it out at the Barclays Center in New York.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: CEBL Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Langley Events Centre in Langley, British Columbia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702020000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702213000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>From Energizer Park in St. Louis, Mo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703010000 +0000" stop="20250703020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703020000 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>From Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703060000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703213000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Navigator Cup</title>
    <desc>TSN's James Duthie and Jeff O'Neill take their legendary on-air rivalry to the course in a head-to-head, match-play golf challenge. Featuring hockey stars Nazem Kadri and Brendan Gallagher.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702063000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702073000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702083000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702093000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702110000 +0000" stop="20250702120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702120000 +0000" stop="20250702130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702130000 +0000" stop="20250702140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702140000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702160000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702190000 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250702233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>Top plays from the 2024-25 NFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250702233000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703020000 +0000" stop="20250703023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703023000 +0000" stop="20250703033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703033000 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703073000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703083000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703093000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703110000 +0000" stop="20250703120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703120000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703140000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703160000 +0000" stop="20250703180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703180000 +0000" stop="20250703183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Atlantic Motorsport Park in Mill Village, Nova Scotia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703183000 +0000" stop="20250703190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703190000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250703230000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Wimbledon Tennis Primetime</title>
    <desc>Action and highlights from the day's matches at the 2025 Wimbledon Championships.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702020000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702213000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250702233000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Wimbledon Tennis Primetime</title>
    <desc>Action and highlights from the day's matches at the 2025 Wimbledon Championships.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703030000 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Semifinal.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703060000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703213000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Broward County Stadium in Lauderhill, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702021000 +0000" stop="20250702024000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702024000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702040000 +0000" stop="20250702050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702050000 +0000" stop="20250702060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702060000 +0000" stop="20250702070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702070000 +0000" stop="20250702080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702080000 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the fifth day of the first Test match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702093000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702124000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702170000 +0000" stop="20250702173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702173000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the fifth day of the first Test match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702190000 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702223000 +0000" stop="20250702225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702225000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Broward County Stadium in Lauderhill, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Broward County Stadium in Lauderhill, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703021000 +0000" stop="20250703024000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703024000 +0000" stop="20250703030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703030000 +0000" stop="20250703040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703040000 +0000" stop="20250703050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703050000 +0000" stop="20250703060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703060000 +0000" stop="20250703070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703070000 +0000" stop="20250703080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703080000 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703093000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703124000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703170000 +0000" stop="20250703173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703173000 +0000" stop="20250703180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703180000 +0000" stop="20250703190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703190000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703223000 +0000" stop="20250703225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703225000 +0000" stop="20250703230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250703230000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Broward County Stadium in Lauderhill, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Broward County Stadium in Lauderhill, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-04</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
