<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A fellow detective asks the SVU for help when he suspects his two daughters are being groomed by a serial predator; Kat disobeys the captain's orders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A desperate father takes matters into his own hands in the case against his daughter's rapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806020000 +0000" stop="20250806025900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives uncover a shocking theory as they work to learn the identity of a man Rollins arrested for exposing himself in the park; Detective Benson finds herself in mortal danger.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806025900 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rainmaker</title>
    <desc>Featuring a preview of USA's new series, The Rainmaker.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU squad searches for Detective Benson and her abductor (Pablo Schreiber).</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 7-year-old girl escapes from her rapist, detectives Benson and Stabler begin an intensive search for the predator.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The life of a law-abiding engineer (Robin Williams) goes terribly wrong, leading him to challenge authority and to urge others to do so as well.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a missing 5-year-old boy is found dead, suspicion falls on his unstable 13-year-old neighbor, whose mental problems began after he was abused at a camp recommended by the dead child's father.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler suspect the drug-dealing uncle of a girl (Shareeka Epps) found raped and beaten, but the theft of the rape kit identifying her attacker leads them to a crooked prison guard.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Elliot Stabler puts his marriage at risk when he goes under cover to gain access to an animal-smuggling ring, with Olivia posing as a prostitute.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler help a repeat rape victim (Jennifer Love Hewitt) stand up to her attacker; the investigation leads Benson to Los Angeles, where she meets a detective (Skeet Ulrich) with information that could help the victim get justice.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight's new Internal Affairs handler proves to be suspicious of his actions; Voight must work with his former partner from the Gang Unit; Halsted enlists Jin to help him gather more information on Lonnie Rodiger; Olinsky takes Ruzek down a peg.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Burgess and Atwater come across a gunshot victim and the only witness is Olinsky's daughter; Ruzek goes to Burgess for help with an undercover mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Halstead's badge is revoked when Lonnie Rodiger is found dead; Severide (Taylor Kinney) and Clarke (Peter Mills) find Dr. Elliot's torso; Sumner (Sydney Tamiia Poitier) tries to prove herself; Lindsay shares a moment with Severide.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Dueling gangs are suspected when a massacre occurs and $8 million is stolen; Platt asks Ruzek for help.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>As Voight and his team search for the bombers, they realize there might be more bombs set to detonate; Burgess' niece fights for her life.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Cmdr. Perry notifies the unit that Pulpo has been released to help with a case; Ruzek gets difficult news; when a bit of Lindsay's past resurfaces, Voight reminds her how far she's come.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Platt and Voight discuss their pasts; Jin uses a scapegoat when he is caught tinkering with Voight's computer; Lindsay realizes she needs to come clean.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide realizes he shares a similar past with the lieutenant who has been helping out at the firehouse; Dawson shares a secret with Shay; Casey faces family issues.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Dawson turns to an unlikely source for assistance as she tries to help her brother; Severide does a favor for Lt. Whaley; Herrmann and Otis make tough discoveries about their silent partner.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz puts himself and his fellow firefighters in danger; Casey tries to resolve issues with his sister and mother; the team assists the bomb squad with a dangerous call.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>When Severide's father (Treat Williams) visits, he clashes with Chief Boden over a former colleague's death; Shay makes a decision about Clarice; the mystery about Herrmann, Otis and Dawson's bar is revealed.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mills questions Bennie about the fire that killed Mills' father; Casey, Severide and Bennie investigate two mysterious diner fires.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A failed rescue attempt deeply affects the men and women of firehouse 51; Dawson and Shay deal with a junkie's crazy behavior during a call; the team upsets local drug dealers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A paramedic candidate joins Shay and Dawson for a few shifts; Cindy Herrmann experiences pregnancy complications while her husband is out of town; Casey receives an unexpected visit.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807000000 +0000" stop="20250807020100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">John Wick</title>
    <desc>New York City becomes the bullet-riddled playground of a former assassin (Keanu Reeves) as he hunts down the Russian mobsters who destroyed everything he held dear.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807020100 +0000" stop="20250807043400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">John Wick: Chapter 2</title>
    <desc>Legendary hit man John Wick comes out of retirement when a former associate plots to seize control of an international assassins' guild. Bound by a blood oath to help him, Wick travels to Rome to square off against the world's deadliest killers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807043400 +0000" stop="20250807063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">John Wick</title>
    <desc>New York City becomes the bullet-riddled playground of a former assassin (Keanu Reeves) as he hunts down the Russian mobsters who destroyed everything he held dear.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807063500 +0000" stop="20250807073400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An abused foster child (Jae Head), apprehended while driving a runaway van, leads the detectives to re-examine a case involving a rape victim (Sara Gilbert).</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807073400 +0000" stop="20250807083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teen named Eric admits to looking at a Web site in an attempt to curb pedophilic urges toward his stepbrother; when Eric goes missing, the stepfather (Tom Noonan) is questioned.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807083200 +0000" stop="20250807093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the body of a 14-year-old girl is found in the Hudson River, Benson and Stabler think she was smuggled into the country by sex traffickers; in an attempt to identify her, Benson poses as a madam.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807093000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>Serial arsonist on the loose leaves no evidence.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>A man becomes the prime suspect in his wife's death after forensic science raises questions about her apparent suicide.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807103000 +0000" stop="20250807113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the murder of a federal prison inmate who was the adopted daughter of a notorious counterfeiter; Callen is summoned by the ATF Internal Affairs board to discuss Anna Kolcheck's actions.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807113000 +0000" stop="20250807123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Sam is shot during a firefight with the cartel; an interrogated suspect reveals new information on the whereabouts of Spencer Williams, the man who kidnapped Mosley's son.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807123000 +0000" stop="20250807133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Despite several team members having reservations, the team travels to Mexico to locate and rescue Mosley's son.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807133000 +0000" stop="20250807143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler begin to question the story of a missing teenager (Ellen Woglom) who returns home after four years, claiming to have been kept as a sex slave in a concrete cell.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807143000 +0000" stop="20250807153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man is found badly beaten in a parking lot, with no memory of what happened, and detectives suspect his transgender teen may be responsible.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807153000 +0000" stop="20250807163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A mute girl is raped and beaten, and her drawing of her attacker resembles a local priest.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807163000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An artist's shocking death leads detectives to uncover a long string of murders by an elusive serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 2-year-old girl goes missing, her irresponsible young mother (Hilary Duff) becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Officer Nate Kendall (Wentworth Miller) helps a woman in trouble and gets roped into investigating a rape; when evidence connects multiple cases, the team realizes there may be a serial rapist responsible.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807193000 +0000" stop="20250807203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Benson suspect a sugar daddy (Matt C. Burns) of murder when a young woman's body is found stuffed inside a suitcase.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807203000 +0000" stop="20250807213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a woman goes missing, her boyfriend points Detectives Benson and Stabler in the direction of convicted bank robber Callum Donovan (Stephen Rea); to comprehend the impact of solitary confinement, Stabler experiences it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807213000 +0000" stop="20250807222900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Stabler investigate when a 10-year-old girl goes missing.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807222900 +0000" stop="20250807232800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives try to identify a girl who is so traumatized after being raped that she cannot tell them her name.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250807232800 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">John Wick: Chapter 2</title>
    <desc>Legendary hit man John Wick comes out of retirement when a former associate plots to seize control of an international assassins' guild. Bound by a blood oath to help him, Wick travels to Rome to square off against the world's deadliest killers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Cincinnati Reds face Chicago Cubs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the MLB following Cincinnati Reds @ Chicago Cubs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Epic Moments</title>
    <desc>A look back at MLB's Epic Moments including the Colorado Rockies winning 14 of their final 15 matches to set-up a play-off game against San Diego Padres.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prime 9</title>
    <desc>A countdown of the nine greatest animal nicknames of all-time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806043000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>Ric heads to South Africa to come face-to-face with perhaps the most mythical mountain bike of all-time, the Honda RN-01.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Poland, which takes the riders on a steep route from Hotel Golebiewski Karpacz to the legendary Orlinek.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shanghai Masters Snooker</title>
    <desc>A review of all the best action and stories from the 2025 Shanghai Masters at Luwan Gymnasium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Porsche Supercup Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Action from the round six of the 2025 Porsche Mobil 1 Supercup in Budapest, Hungary.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World E-Bike Series</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from the Monaco Alpes-Maritimes Round of the 2025 World E-Bike Series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806083000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We delve into the remarkable journey of Sunderland AFC; a club defined by its dramatic highs and painful lows. From their proud top-flight legacy to the heartbreak of consecutive relegations, Sunderland's story is one of resilience, identity, and unbreakable community spirit. Now, under the leadership of new head coach Regis Le Bris, the Black Cats are preparing for a new chapter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Poland, which takes the riders on a steep route from Hotel Golebiewski Karpacz to the legendary Orlinek.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Poland, as the riders tackle a challenging 161km mountainous route around Walbrzych.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806144500 +0000" stop="20250806163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Ain, as the riders set out on a route from Feillens to Belley.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806163000 +0000" stop="20250806194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Baltimore Orioles travel to face Philadelphia Phillies.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806194500 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB classic action from the All-Star Highlights 1973 from the Royals Stadium in Kansas City.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as St. Louis Cardinals travel to face Los Angeles Dodgers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806231500 +0000" stop="20250806234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250806234500 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807000000 +0000" stop="20250807003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807003000 +0000" stop="20250807013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Poland, as the riders tackle a challenging 161km mountainous route around Walbrzych.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 8 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807030000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford. The boys go head-to-head in a challenge decider and take a serious look at the state of British rivers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Ain, as the riders set out on a route from Feillens to Belley.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>Ric heads to South Africa to come face-to-face with perhaps the most mythical mountain bike of all-time, the Honda RN-01.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807053000 +0000" stop="20250807063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights round 10 of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Belle Vue Aces went head-to-head with Ipswich Witches at National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807063000 +0000" stop="20250807073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round eight the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at the Bikernieki racing circuit in Riga, Latvia.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807073000 +0000" stop="20250807083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Ain, as the riders set out on a route from Feillens to Belley.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807083000 +0000" stop="20250807093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Poland, as the riders tackle a challenging 161km mountainous route around Walbrzych.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807093000 +0000" stop="20250807144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Poland, as the peloton face a 200km journey from Rybnik to Cieszyn.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807144500 +0000" stop="20250807163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Ain, which takes the riders from Saint-Vulbas to Lelex-Monts Jura.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807163000 +0000" stop="20250807170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World E-Bike Series</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from the Monaco Alpes-Maritimes Round of the 2025 World E-Bike Series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807170000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Polo</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the 2025 British Open Polo Championship, as international stars of the game compete in the setting of Cowdray Park's stunning grounds.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We delve into the remarkable journey of Sunderland AFC; a club defined by its dramatic highs and painful lows. From their proud top-flight legacy to the heartbreak of consecutive relegations, Sunderland's story is one of resilience, identity, and unbreakable community spirit. Now, under the leadership of new head coach Regis Le Bris, the Black Cats are preparing for a new chapter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Hawthorn face Collingwood.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball action as Chicago White Sox take on Seattle Mariners.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807231500 +0000" stop="20250807234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Off The Bat</title>
    <desc>All the latest action from Major League Baseball wrapped up, featuring the league's top hitters and pitchers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250807234500 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806004500 +0000" stop="20250806014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Poland, which takes the riders on a steep route from Hotel Golebiewski Karpacz to the legendary Orlinek.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806014500 +0000" stop="20250806024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights round 10 of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Belle Vue Aces went head-to-head with Ipswich Witches at National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806024500 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kenny Allstar's Number 1s</title>
    <desc>Kenny Allstar heads to Tottenham to explore all things 'Firsts' with Spurs captain and Premier League icon Son Heung-Min.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford. The boys go head-to-head in a challenge decider and take a serious look at the state of British rivers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Football's On</title>
    <desc>Ex-players Mark Crossley and Paul McGregor join Becky Ives and Charlie Baker to share classic Brian Clough tales and ask if the glory days are coming back to Nottingham Forest.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806054500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MX2 race one at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806054500 +0000" stop="20250806063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MX2 race two at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806063000 +0000" stop="20250806071500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MXGP race one at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806071500 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MXGP race two at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford. The boys go head-to-head in a challenge decider and take a serious look at the state of British rivers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the first T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. How will the Windies respond after their humiliating defeat at the hands of Australia?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the second T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. The Windies need a win to stay in this three-match series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the third T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Watch our favourite interviews and moments from last season, all featuring British Sign Language and subtitles. Guests include Arne Slot, Phil Foden, John McGinn and Eberechi Eze.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shanghai Masters Snooker</title>
    <desc>A review of all the best action and stories from the 2025 Shanghai Masters at Luwan Gymnasium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806163000 +0000" stop="20250806164500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Rob Hatch, The Gruppetto brings you everything you need to stay up to speed with the world of cycling, from in-depth race reviews to the latest news from the peloton.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806164500 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the third T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806173000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We delve into the remarkable journey of Sunderland AFC; a club defined by its dramatic highs and painful lows. From their proud top-flight legacy to the heartbreak of consecutive relegations, Sunderland's story is one of resilience, identity, and unbreakable community spirit. Now, under the leadership of new head coach Regis Le Bris, the Black Cats are preparing for a new chapter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round eight the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at the Bikernieki racing circuit in Riga, Latvia.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806193000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>Ric heads to South Africa to come face-to-face with perhaps the most mythical mountain bike of all-time, the Honda RN-01.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">EWC All Access</title>
    <desc>Behind the scenes access to the 2025 FIM Endurance World Championship and the 8 Hours of Suzuka race in Japan.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>Formed in 1993, the UFC has risen from tough beginnings to become a leading force in combat sports. This documentary delves into the history of this powerhouse company.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250806223000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC Fight Night at UFC Apex in Enterprise, Nevada, featuring the main event showdown between flyweights Tatsuro Taira and Park Hyun-sung.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Fight Flashback</title>
    <desc>We look back at this classic bantamweight clash between Cody Garbrandt and Dominick Cruz at UFC 207 at the T-Mobile Arena in Paradise, Nevada.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807020000 +0000" stop="20250807030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shanghai Masters Snooker</title>
    <desc>A review of all the best action and stories from the 2025 Shanghai Masters at Luwan Gymnasium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807030000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Porsche Supercup Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Action from the round six of the 2025 Porsche Mobil 1 Supercup in Budapest, Hungary.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from Rally Finland and the 2025 World Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807053000 +0000" stop="20250807073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between Zimbabwe and New Zealand at Queens Sports Club in Bulawayo, which featured brilliant performances by Matt Henry and Devon Conway.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807073000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Day one of the second Test between Zimbabwe and New Zealand at Queens Sports Club in Bulawayo. The Black Caps will be looking to put on another dominant display.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807191500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action as Washington Nationals host the Athletics.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807191500 +0000" stop="20250807194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Off The Bat</title>
    <desc>All the latest action from Major League Baseball wrapped up, featuring the league's top hitters and pitchers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807194500 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Rob Hatch, The Gruppetto brings you everything you need to stay up to speed with the world of cycling, from in-depth race reviews to the latest news from the peloton.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We delve into the remarkable journey of Sunderland AFC; a club defined by its dramatic highs and painful lows. From their proud top-flight legacy to the heartbreak of consecutive relegations, Sunderland's story is one of resilience, identity, and unbreakable community spirit. Now, under the leadership of new head coach Regis Le Bris, the Black Cats are preparing for a new chapter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807203000 +0000" stop="20250807213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A review of the 2024/25 Premier League season, as Arne Slot made history in his first campaign in charge of Liverpool and Manchester United struggled at the wrong end of the table.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807213000 +0000" stop="20250807224500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>TNT Sports Films tells the story of Molly McCann, from troubled beginnings on Merseyside, to becoming the first English female fighter to win in the UFC.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250807224500 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC Fight Night at UFC Apex in Enterprise, Nevada, featuring the main event showdown between flyweights Tatsuro Taira and Park Hyun-sung.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806013000 +0000" stop="20250806023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806023000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From RAD Torque Raceway in Edmonton, Alberta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806173000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806203000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806213000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250806233000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Leagues Cup</title>
    <desc>From Mercedes-Benz Stadium in Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807060000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807140000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Cincinnati Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Lindner Family Tennis Center in Cincinnati.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Cincinnati Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Lindner Family Tennis Center in Cincinnati.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Leagues Cup</title>
    <desc>From Lower.com Field in Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806013000 +0000" stop="20250806023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806023000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Truist Park in Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807060000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807140000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807190000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250807233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: CFL on TSN Pregame</title>
    <desc>The CFL on TSN panel sets up the game ahead.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250807233000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: CFL Football</title>
    <desc>From Tim Hortons Field in Hamilton, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Racing Louisville FC face league leaders Kansas City Current at Lynn Family Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Washington Spirit face Portland Thorns at Audi Field. The Thorns won 2-0 when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806020000 +0000" stop="20250806023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Brian Priske's Feyenoord meet Sparta Prague at De Kuip. Feyenoord are winless in their four games against Sparta Prague.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806023000 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Borussia Dortmund and Barcelona face-off at Signal Iduna Park. Barca are looking to secure their fifth win in a row in the UCL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as AC Milan face Serbian champions Red Star at San Siro. Paulo Fonseca's Milan are looking to make it four UCL wins in a row.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Atalanta takes on Sturm Graz at Gewiss Stadium. Atalanta are winless in their last five home games in this competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Red Star take on PSV Eindhoven at Rajko Mitic Stadium. Red Star are on the longest current run of UCL games without a clean sheet.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806043000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as winless Bologna face Nuri Sahin's top-eight contenders Borussia Dortmund at Stadio Renato Dall'Ara.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League as Chelsea take on Gent at Stamford Bridge.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806053000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Enzo Maresca's Chelsea continue their UEFA Conference League campaign with a trip to face Diego Alonso's Panathinaikos at Athens Olympic Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League as Enzo Maresca's Chelsea host Armenian side Noah at Stamford Bridge. The visiting side were only founded seven years ago.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806063000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League as German side Heidenheim host Chelsea at Voith-Arena. Enzo Maresca's Blues have already scored 16 goals in this competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League as Astana face Chelsea at Astana Arena. Enzo Maresca's in-form Blues have already scored 18 goals in this competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806073000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Chelsea host Irish side Shamrock Rovers at Stamford Bridge. Can Enzo Maresca's Blues make it six wins on the spin in the UEFA Conference League?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>UEFA Europa Conference League Round of 16 first leg as Copenhagen take on Chelsea at Parken Stadium. Can Chelsea assert their dominance, or will Copenhagen spring a surprise at home?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806083000 +0000" stop="20250806093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League Round of 16 2nd leg clash between Chelsea and Copenhagen at Stamford Bridge. The Blues hold a 2-1 lead from the 1st leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806093000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League quarter-final 1st leg between Legia Warsaw and Chelsea. Can Enzo Maresca's Blues secure a big win in Poland?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League quarter-final 2nd leg between Chelsea and Legia Warsaw at Stamford Bridge. The Blues hold a commanding 3-0 lead from the 1st leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806103000 +0000" stop="20250806113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League semi-final 1st leg between Djurgardens and Chelsea at 3Arena. Can Enzo Maresca's side secure a big win in Stockholm?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806113000 +0000" stop="20250806123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Conference League semi-final 2nd leg between Chelsea and Djurgardens at Stamford Bridge. The Blues were 4-1 winners in the 1st leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806123000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Conference League final between Manuel Pellegrini's Real Betis and Enzo Maresca's Chelsea at Stadion Wroclaw.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Race Bikes</title>
    <desc>Ric heads to South Africa to come face-to-face with perhaps the most mythical mountain bike of all-time, the Honda RN-01.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806143000 +0000" stop="20250806163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Ain, as the riders set out on a route from Feillens to Belley.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806163000 +0000" stop="20250806173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Fiorentina face-off against AC Milan at Artemio Franchi Stadium. Fiorentina are unbeaten in ten of their last eleven home league games.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806173000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Empoli face-off against at Napoli at Stadio Carlo Castellani. Empoli are unbeaten in their last seven league home matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Ivan Juric's Roma face Inter at Stadio Olimpico. Roma have lost their last three home league games against Inter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806193000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 8 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Poland, as the riders tackle a challenging 161km mountainous route around Walbrzych.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Ain, as the riders set out on a route from Feillens to Belley.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Racing Louisville FC face league leaders Kansas City Current at Lynn Family Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807000000 +0000" stop="20250807010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Washington Spirit face Portland Thorns at Audi Field. The Thorns won 2-0 when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807010000 +0000" stop="20250807020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights round 10 of the British Speedway ROWE Motor Oil Premiership as Belle Vue Aces went head-to-head with Ipswich Witches at National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807020000 +0000" stop="20250807024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MX2 race one at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807024500 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MX2 race two at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MXGP race one at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807041500 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MXGP race two at Stedelijk Motorcrossterrein Lommel in Flanders.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807053000 +0000" stop="20250807063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Inter and Juventus face-off at San Siro. Can Thiago Motta's Juve side continue their unbeaten start to the Serie A season?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807063000 +0000" stop="20250807073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Raffaele Palladino's Fiorentina meet Ivan Juric's Roma at Artemio Franchi Stadium. Roma have not won any of their last three away league games against Fiorentina.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807073000 +0000" stop="20250807083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shanghai Masters Snooker</title>
    <desc>A review of all the best action and stories from the 2025 Shanghai Masters at Luwan Gymnasium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807083000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 8 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Racing Louisville FC face league leaders Kansas City Current at Lynn Family Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Washington Spirit face Portland Thorns at Audi Field. The Thorns won 2-0 when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807133000 +0000" stop="20250807143100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Femmes</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from the 2025 Tour de France Women.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807143100 +0000" stop="20250807163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Ain, which takes the riders from Saint-Vulbas to Lelex-Monts Jura.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807163000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the first T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. How will the Windies respond after their humiliating defeat at the hands of Australia?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the second T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. The Windies need a win to stay in this three-match series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the third T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. Who will come out on top in this series decider?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807193000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Pologne</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Poland, as the peloton face a 200km journey from Rybnik to Cieszyn.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Ain, which takes the riders from Saint-Vulbas to Lelex-Monts Jura.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Arctic Race of Norway Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Arctic Race of Norway, as the peloton embarks on a 182km route from Borkenes to Harstad.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Day one of the second Test between Zimbabwe and New Zealand at Queens Sports Club in Bulawayo. The Black Caps will be looking to put on another dominant display.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Juventus host Napoli at Allianz Stadium. Could Antonio Conte get one over his former side?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action from one of the biggest derbies in football as Inter face AC Milan at San Siro. This tense Derby della Madonnina would be decided by a late goal.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806020000 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Paulo Fonseca's AC Milan meet Lecce at San Siro. Milan have already scored 11 league goals in this term.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Napoli face Monza at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Napoli have won their first two home league games under Antonio Conte.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Inter welcome Paolo Vanoli's Torino to San Siro. Torino are unbeaten in their opening three league away games this season.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Formula E Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Andretti is a name synonymous with American motorsport. But can the team and hotshot driver Jake Dennis make their mark on Formula E?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806053000 +0000" stop="20250806063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Racing Louisville FC face league leaders Kansas City Current at Lynn Family Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806063000 +0000" stop="20250806073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Washington Spirit face Portland Thorns at Audi Field. The Thorns won 2-0 when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806073000 +0000" stop="20250806093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the first Test between Zimbabwe and New Zealand at Queens Sports Club in Bulawayo.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806093000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Western Bulldogs face GWS Giants at Marvel Stadium. The Giants have only won one of their last nine games against the Dogs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Adelaide Crows face Hawthorn at Adelaide Oval. The Hawks have won 15 of their past 19 matches against the Crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806123000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Melbourne take on West Coast Eagles at Marvel Stadium. Can the Eagles find their second win of the season?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Gold Coast Suns meet Richmond at People First Stadium. Can the Tigers do the double over the Suns?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806153000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League showdown between Sydney Swans and Essendon at the SCG. The Bombers won 71-63 when these sides met in round nine.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Collingwood face Brisbane Lions at the MCG. Can the Magpies take another big step towards securing a crucial top-two spot?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as St Kilda face North Melbourne at Marvel Stadium. Can the Saints build on their epic comeback last time out?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Geelong Cats take on Port Adelaide at GMHBA Stadium. Can the Power bounce back from their Showdown defeat?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806213000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Fremantle and Carlton go head-to-head at Optus Stadium. The Dockers have won nine of their past 10 matches in Perth.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250806231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look at the best batting action from the first Test between Zimbabwe and New Zealand.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806231500 +0000" stop="20250806233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look at the best bowling action from the first Test between Zimbabwe and New Zealand.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250806233000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the first T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. How will the Windies respond after their humiliating defeat at the hands of Australia?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807003000 +0000" stop="20250807013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the second T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. The Windies need a win to stay in this three-match series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the third T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida. Who will come out on top in this series decider?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807030000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the WNBA as Las Vegas Aces host Minnesota Lynx at Michelob Ultra Arena. The Lynx won 109-78 in the last meeting between these sides.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the WNBA as Indiana Fever face Seattle Storm at Climate Pledge Arena. Aliyah Boston scored 31 points to help the Fever to a 94-86 win when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Football's On</title>
    <desc>Becky Ives is joined by Man City legend Paul Dickov, as well as comedians Mike Newall and Charlie Baker, to chat about what's next for the Pep Guardiola's side.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807060000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">EWC All Access</title>
    <desc>Behind the scenes access to the 2025 FIM Endurance World Championship and the 8 Hours of Suzuka race in Japan.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Porsche Supercup Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Action from the round six of the 2025 Porsche Mobil 1 Supercup in Budapest, Hungary.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from Rally Finland and the 2025 World Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807091500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kenny Allstar's Number 1s</title>
    <desc>Kenny Allstar heads to Manchester to explore all things 'firsts and favourites' with Manchester United and England rising star Kobbie Mainoo.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807091500 +0000" stop="20250807123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Hawthorn face Collingwood.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807123000 +0000" stop="20250807133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the WNBA as Las Vegas Aces host Minnesota Lynx at Michelob Ultra Arena. The Lynx won 109-78 in the last meeting between these sides.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807133000 +0000" stop="20250807143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the WNBA as Indiana Fever face Seattle Storm at Climate Pledge Arena. Aliyah Boston scored 31 points to help the Fever to a 94-86 win when these sides last met.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807143000 +0000" stop="20250807153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807153000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the third T20 between West Indies and Pakistan in Lauderhill, Florida.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807161500 +0000" stop="20250807163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>What does the future hold for cycling in the battle against global warming? Reshmin Chowdhury meets people at all levels to discuss how cycling can be a positive force for change.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807163000 +0000" stop="20250807170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807170000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action between Atletico Madrid and Bayer Leverkusen at Riyadh Air Metropolitano. A win for Atletico would see them leapfrog Leverkusen in the table.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Arsenal host Croatian giants Dinamo Zagreb at Emirates Stadium. The Gunners will seal automatic qualification with a win.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Carlo Ancelotti's Real Madrid look to strengthen their grip on a UEFA Champions League play-off place when they face strugglers RB Salzbug at Santiago Bernabeu.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Feyenoord face Bayern Munich at De Kuip. Bayern are unbeaten in their last eight UCL games against Dutch opponents.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807190000 +0000" stop="20250807193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Manchester City fight for their place in the UEFA Champions League as they face Club Brugge at Etihad Stadium. Only a win will be enough for City to qualify for the play-off round.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807193000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Lille meet Dutch side Feyenoord at Stade Pierre-Mauroy. Both sides are still in the hunt for a top-eight finish.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Inter and Monaco face-off at San Siro. Can Adi Hutter's Monaco side cause an upset and break into the top eight?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807203000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Spanish side Girona welcome Arsenal to Estadi Montilivi. Mikel Arteta's Gunners are looking to make it six wins out of eight in the UCL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the top ten finals in the history of the UEFA Champions League, including Liverpool's miraculous comeback against AC Milan in Istanbul.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shanghai Masters Snooker</title>
    <desc>A review of all the best action and stories from the 2025 Shanghai Masters at Luwan Gymnasium.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Leagues Cup</title>
    <desc>From Lower.com Field in Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806013000 +0000" stop="20250806023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806023000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From RAD Torque Raceway in Edmonton, Alberta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806173000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806203000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806213000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Truist Park in Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807060000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807140000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807170000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP: Racing on the Edge</title>
    <desc>In a display of skill amidst New York's chaotic waters, Martine Grael and the Brazilian team secure a milestone: their first fleet race victory.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>Top plays from the 2024-25 NFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From RAD Torque Raceway in Edmonton, Alberta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807190000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807203000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807213000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250807233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: CFL on TSN Pregame</title>
    <desc>The CFL on TSN panel sets up the game ahead.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250807233000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: CFL Football</title>
    <desc>From Tim Hortons Field in Hamilton, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806043000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806053000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806063000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806073000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806083000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806093000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806103000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806113000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806123000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806133000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806143000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806153000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Ice</title>
    <desc>John Saunders profiles black college hockey players Mike Grier and Anson Carter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NASCAR Canada Series</title>
    <desc>From Sutherland Automotive Speedway in Saskatoon, Saskatchewan.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806203000 +0000" stop="20250806213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806213000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>Teams of pairs race around Canada, through its urban centres to its most-remote outposts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807000000 +0000" stop="20250807020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807020000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807073000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807083000 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807093000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807103000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807113000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807123000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807133000 +0000" stop="20250807140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807140000 +0000" stop="20250807143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807143000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807153000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807170000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">AFL Premiership Football</title>
    <desc>From Melbourne Cricket Ground in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807213000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 U.S. Women's Amateur</title>
    <desc>From Bandon Dunes Golf Resort in Bandon, Ore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806013000 +0000" stop="20250806023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806023000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806183000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806203000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806213000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Why We Love Football</title>
    <desc>Sports talk centered around the latest moves and news in the CFL and NFL.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 U.S. Women's Amateur</title>
    <desc>From Bandon Dunes Golf Resort in Bandon, Ore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807010000 +0000" stop="20250807013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Truist Park in Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807060000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IWL Wrestball 3x3</title>
    <desc>The explosive fusion of basketball, rugby, and wrestling -- where agility, power, and strategy collide. Be the first to experience this new-rules-arena revolution.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Golden Tee Golf World Championships</title>
    <desc>The world's best Golden Tee players converge at the Palms Casino Resort in Las Vegas to battle for nearly $200,000 in prizes. The stakes are high, the legends are ready -- who will take home the title in the game that helped shape esports?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807133000 +0000" stop="20250807140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mailboat Jumping</title>
    <desc>Carriers compete to secure a spot on the historic Mailboat Team, jumping from boat to dock and back again while in motion. It's part timing, part chaos,and a century-old tradition that defines summer. Don't fall in-or do, but don't expect sympathy.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807140000 +0000" stop="20250807143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 National Bubble Gum Blowing Championship</title>
    <desc>Finalists chew. They blow. They pray it doesn't pop too soon. The biggest unburst bubble wins. One gum blower will be crowned the 2025 Champion. The rest go home sticky and defeated.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807143000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goodyear Blimp Sky Race of the Century</title>
    <desc>To mark the 100th anniversary of the Goodyear Blimp in 2025, Goodyear brought all three of its U.S. airships to Akron, Ohio for the Sky Race of the Century. While blimps aren't known for speed, this race has no shortage of action.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pop-A-Shot 2025 National Championship</title>
    <desc>The Pop-A-Shot 2025 National Championship brings together the top qualifiers from across the country. A head-to-head, tournament-style competition and the thrilling finale of the Pop-A-Shot National Series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diving Chess: Duel in the Depths</title>
    <desc>Two champions face off in a high-stakes underwater chess match -- where every move is made on a single breath.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807163000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Blackbird Cup - Alberta Pro Roller Hockey League</title>
    <desc>The championship game of the Alberta ProRoller Hockey League (APRHL), highlighting Canada's emerging inline hockey talent, community roots, and diverse player stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Microsoft Excel World Championship 2024 Finals</title>
    <desc>Microsoft Excel World Championship is an Excel Esports competition where players solve unusual game tasks in Microsoft Excel. For the second year, the Finals were held at the HyperXArena Las Vegas, uniting top players from around the globe.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 2025 Big Boy Soap Hockey Tournament</title>
    <desc>The biggest and baddest soap hockey league in the world faces off in an eight-team, single elimination tournament to win the ultimate prize... the Golden Duck.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807183000 +0000" stop="20250807190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Donk Toss World Championship</title>
    <desc>The Donk Toss World Championships is a glorious backyard sport that blends skill, chaos, and comedy. Players toss an inflatable donkey and score points by landing it in funny positions -- on its feet, ears-down, snout-first, or even upside down.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807190000 +0000" stop="20250807193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 T-Rex World Championship Races</title>
    <desc>It's a race of prehistoric proportion as men, women, children and seniors compete to be the 2025 T-Rex World Champion!</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807193000 +0000" stop="20250807203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Slippery Stairs at The Ocho</title>
    <desc>Competitors attempt to reach the top of the slippery stairs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807203000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bike Polo</title>
    <desc>The mastery of polo meets the intensity of biking. Watch as this innovative sport takes to the streets of Brooklyn New York, with City bragging rights on the line.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 World Dog Surfing Championships Best Waves</title>
    <desc>The World Dog Surfing Championships Best Waves competition rewards the best waves, champion dog surfers have surfed over the past year.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807213000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Corgi Races at Emerald Downs</title>
    <desc>Get ready for the cutest and most unpredictable event of the year as over 100 Corgis race for the Championship trophy!</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250807233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250807233000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Leagues Cup</title>
    <desc>From Bank of America Stadium in Charlotte, N.C.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806020000 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806040000 +0000" stop="20250806050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806050000 +0000" stop="20250806060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the first Women's ODI match between England and West Indies, where they compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806060000 +0000" stop="20250806070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806070000 +0000" stop="20250806080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806080000 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the second ODI match between England and West Indies, where they compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from various cricket tournaments, where top-performing teams from different countries compete against each other to win the coveted title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from various cricket tournaments, where top-performing teams from different countries compete against each other to win the coveted title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806133000 +0000" stop="20250806135000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806135000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Women's The Hundred</title>
    <desc>From Emirates Old Trafford in Manchester, England, United Kingdom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806163000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806172000 +0000" stop="20250806173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806173000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's The Hundred</title>
    <desc>From Emirates Old Trafford in Manchester, England, United Kingdom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806203000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the first Women's T20I match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807000000 +0000" stop="20250807010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807010000 +0000" stop="20250807020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807020000 +0000" stop="20250807030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807030000 +0000" stop="20250807040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807040000 +0000" stop="20250807050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807050000 +0000" stop="20250807060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807060000 +0000" stop="20250807070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807070000 +0000" stop="20250807073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807073000 +0000" stop="20250807075000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807075000 +0000" stop="20250807080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807080000 +0000" stop="20250807104000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807104000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage from a test match, a contest between two international teams played over five days.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Women's The Hundred</title>
    <desc>From Headingley Cricket Ground in Leeds, United Kingdom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807163000 +0000" stop="20250807170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807170000 +0000" stop="20250807172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807172000 +0000" stop="20250807173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807173000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's The Hundred</title>
    <desc>From Headingley Cricket Ground in Leeds, United Kingdom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807203000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's T20I match between England and India, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250808000000 +0000" stop="20250809000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-08</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
