<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenage sex worker disappears, Rollins and Velasco find a key clue in a pile of neglected missing persons reports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi asks the SVU for help with a murder investigation when one of the witnesses shows signs of abuse.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi tries Richard Wheatley for the murder of Kathy Stabler; Benson finds herself at odds with a friend when Barba agrees to take the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry struggles to find balance with his new human form.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708040200 +0000" stop="20250708050200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The death of a boy and his abusive guardian leads the detectives to a travel agency specializing in exotic trips for sexual predators.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708050200 +0000" stop="20250708060200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A 15-year-old rape victim steps off of a subway platform, and two suspects in the case admit to being sexually involved with the girl's mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708060200 +0000" stop="20250708070200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A drug dealer dies in jail after being beaten and sexually assaulted.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708070200 +0000" stop="20250708080100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an 8-year-old beauty queen's body is found in a suitcase on a Manhattan bus, detectives hunt for a pedophile with a fetish for pageants.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708080100 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a California housewife is murdered in broad daylight, the suspected killer claims it was a burglary gone awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a California housewife is murdered in broad daylight, the suspected killer claims it was a burglary gone awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When Hetty turns in retirement papers and disappears, Shay Mosley comes to Los Angeles to oversee the team and makes staffing changes; Sam insists that Callen find a new partner.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When the daughter of a notorious counterfeiter arrives in Los Angeles, Sam goes under cover as a financier; Callen partners with Anna to track the family's latest scheme.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>During the murder investigation of a Navy Lieutenant on leave in Los Angeles, the team uncovers classified surveillance briefs she smuggled into the city that may have been sold to a foreign buyer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Alexandra Cabot questions a pediatrician (Judd Hirsch) about a dead baby found in a cooler in the East River.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708140000 +0000" stop="20250708150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler hunts for a missing 14-year-old girl who may have been abducted by a foreign child pornographer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708150000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Stabler look for a killer with a foot fetish.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy witnesses the brutal sexual assault and murder of his mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708170000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man (Fred Savage) accused of rape becomes a formidable opponent when he decides to handle his own defense.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Evidence points to an angry ex-boyfriend when a cocktail waitress is murdered outside a popular nightspot.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives suspect several young socialites of raping a girl at a Manhattan nightclub, then killing her.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives face off against a Colombian cartel and the Drug Enforcement Administration while investigating the brutal rape and murder of an undercover agent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young woman learning about her birth parents asks Benson for help; Carisi and Rollins weigh the risks of taking their relationship public.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The creator of a dating app is accused of using it to rape women; Velasco's experience as an SVU detective is put on trial.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Velasco asks Benson for help finding three girls who were trafficked from his hometown to New York City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Garland asks Benson to reopen a missing persons case he worked as a rookie officer; a victim in one of Carisi's recent cases is arrested.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709010000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the only evidence in a crime is a church confession, Carisi must find another way to prove his suspect guilty; Benson agrees to meet with an old friend seeking to make amends for past transgressions.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU provides help and protection for a longtime domestic violence victim, but when she winds up at the defendant's table in court, Rollins surprises Carisi with a formidable opponent at trial.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A girl is shot and Cosgrove teams with Detective Jalen Shaw to track down her killer; Benson and Stabler assist and realize it's more than a typical homicide; McCoy and Price seek justice against an international crime ring; part 2 of 3.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A group of teens terrorizing tourists has the SVU squad working overtime; McGrath teams them up with the Bronx gang unit to track down a crucial lead.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Alexandra Cabot questions a pediatrician (Judd Hirsch) about a dead baby found in a cooler in the East River.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler hunts for a missing 14-year-old girl who may have been abducted by a foreign child pornographer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Stabler look for a killer with a foot fetish.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy witnesses the brutal sexual assault and murder of his mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man (Fred Savage) accused of rape becomes a formidable opponent when he decides to handle his own defense.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709100000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A series of brutal home invasion robberies finds the team paired with Detective Borkowski, an old friend of Ruzek's, to work the case; things get complicated for Torres when it becomes clear Borkowski has a vastly different policing style.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A shocking ambush at a funeral leads the team into a heated investigation to find the shooters; much to Atwater's surprise, he must rely on someone from his past to help in the investigation, dredging up old memories and revealing new truths.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Sean O'Neal surprises Upton with a call from prison, revealing sensitive information; while Upton grapples with how to keep O'Neal at a distance, the team quickly mobilizes to stop a crime in progress before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight and the team help ASA Nina Chapman pursue a drug runner who dodged prison years ago after Chapman's informant mysteriously disappeared; the investigation takes a turn when Voight uncovers a damaging secret from Chapman's past.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After a brutal shooting, Burgess and Ruzek find themselves trapped aboard the busy "L" subway; as they piece together scant evidence, the team is drawn into a dark family drama; Burgess' proximity to the shooting triggers harsh memories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a family is poisoned in their home, the team discovers a connection to the Becks; Ruzek goes undercover to work for their business, and as he gets closer to Samantha, chilling information about her father, Richard, comes to light.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709160000 +0000" stop="20250709170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight takes the stand in a high-stakes murder trial against notorious drug kingpin Arturo Morales; when it becomes clear that Morales and his henchmen have compromised a juror, Voight and the team work furiously to ensure justice prevails.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709170000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>An annoying floater takes a romantic interest in Violet; Ritter catches a local politician in a compromising position; Mouch and Severide help Trudy with an arson investigation.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd, Seager and Carver investigate a fire at the city stables; Kylie clashes with some of the firefighters over changes due to budget cuts; Herrmann struggles to keep it together as Cindy's condition worsens.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz feels the burden of his increased responsibilities; Kidd, Gallo and Carver get caught in the middle of a gang war on a call; Herrmann wrangles Trudy for help lifting Cindy's mood.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mouch builds a classic firetruck model for the Deputy District Chief but needs assistance from Gallo and Ritter; Brett and Violet encounter multiple victims with a strange set of symptoms; Cindy's chemotherapy results loom over the Herrmann family.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A familiar face returns to Firehouse 51 to serve with Kidd on a special task force; with Tony close to breaking the CFD's perfect attendance record, Mouch and Capp work to keep him safe; old grudges resurface when Gallo reunites with a family member.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Boden, Ritter, Herrmann and Kidd work together to take down a local politician responsible for a chemical fire; after his aunt's accident, Gallo worries about their future; Brett steps in to perform Dylan's magic show when he's out of town.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Herrmann works on becoming a better man after Cindy's cancer journey; Kidd bonds with a homeless victim on a call; Kylie takes her firefighter exams; a harrowing call takes a toll on Brett.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250710000000 +0000" stop="20250711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ticket to Paradise</title>
    <desc>A man and his ex-wife race to Bali, Indonesia, to stop their daughter from marrying a seaweed farmer. As they desperately try to sabotage the wedding, the bickering duo soon find themselves rekindling old feelings that once made them happy together.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-10</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708014500 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Series Film</title>
    <desc>The New York Yankees advanced to the Fall Classic for the third time in four years, facing the Atlanta Braves who they defeated in the 1996 World Series. Mariano Rivera, Derek Jeter and Paul O'Neill led the Bronx Bombers to the Club's 25th championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Seattle Storm travel to face New York Liberty at the Barclays Center. The Storm beat Liberty 89-79 back in June.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage two of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the riders take on a hilly 92km route from Clusone to the town of Aprica.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage three of the 2025 Tour de France. This largely flat route takes the riders 178km from Valenciennes to the coastal city of Dunkirk.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708061500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the first ODI between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R. Premadasa Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708061500 +0000" stop="20250708063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the second ODI between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R. Premadasa Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708063000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Watch our favourite interviews and moments from last season, all featuring British Sign Language and subtitles. Guests include Arne Slot, Phil Foden, John McGinn and Eberechi Eze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage two of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the riders take on a hilly 92km route from Clusone to the town of Aprica.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage three of the 2025 Tour de France. This largely flat route takes the riders 178km from Valenciennes to the coastal city of Dunkirk.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de France</title>
    <desc>The 2025 Tour de France continues with a hilly 174km route for stage four, which takes the peloton from Amiens to Rouen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage three of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the peloton travels 122km from Vezza d'Oglio to the city of Trento.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708170000 +0000" stop="20250708171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708171500 +0000" stop="20250708174500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We sit down with Claude Makélélé to reflect on the career of a true midfield master. Celebrated for redefining the defensive midfield role, Makélélé shares his memories of life in the Premier League, from joining Chelsea during a transformative era to becoming the heartbeat of a title-winning side. With insight from teammates, coaches, and opponents, we explore the intelligence, discipline, and in</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708174500 +0000" stop="20250708184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grand Slam of Showjumping</title>
    <desc>2025 Rolex Grand Slam action from CHIO Aachen, taking place in the heart of the equestrian sport at the famous showgrounds in Aachen, Germany.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708184500 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage four of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a hilly 174km route from Amiens to Rouen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage three of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the peloton travels 122km from Vezza d'Oglio to the city of Trento.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Watch our favourite interviews and moments from last season, all featuring British Sign Language and subtitles. Guests include Arne Slot, Phil Foden, John McGinn and Eberechi Eze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Lead Off</title>
    <desc>A look at the upcoming MLB action ahead of Los Angeles Dodgers @ Milwaukee Brewers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as Los Angeles Dodgers face-off against Milwaukee Brewers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709023000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the MLB following Los Angeles Dodgers @ Milwaukee Brewers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage four of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a hilly 174km route from Amiens to Rouen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage three of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the peloton travels 122km from Vezza d'Oglio to the city of Trento.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A mid-season review of the 2025 World Rally Championship, including events in Kenya, Italy and Monte Carlo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709053000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Rome, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage four of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a hilly 174km route from Amiens to Rouen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709083000 +0000" stop="20250709084500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709084500 +0000" stop="20250709094500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage three of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the peloton travels 122km from Vezza d'Oglio to the city of Trento.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709094500 +0000" stop="20250709104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage four of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders face a hilly 174km route from Amiens to Rouen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709104500 +0000" stop="20250709161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de France</title>
    <desc>Action from stage five and the first individual time trial of the 2025 Tour de France. Who will triumph in this 33km chrono race in the historic port city of Caen?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709161500 +0000" stop="20250709171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage four of the 2026 Giro d'Italia Women sees the riders tackle a tough 142km mountain route from Castello Tesino to the town of Pianezze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709171500 +0000" stop="20250709173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709173000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709183000 +0000" stop="20250709193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709193000 +0000" stop="20250709224500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Philadelphia Phillies face San Francisco Giants.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709224500 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">British Superbikes Rewind</title>
    <desc>We look back at the best action from round four of British Superbikes, which took place at Knockhill Racing Circuit in Scotland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Major League Baseball action as New York Mets face Baltimore Orioles.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global Champions Tour</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the Longines Global Champions Tour and the 2025 Grand Prix of Monaco, as the best riders in the world compete in a breathtaking waterfront setting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708023000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>We revisit the best tries of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, including Tom Roebuck, Kalaveti Ravouvou, Cadan Murley and many others.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708043000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ally's Social Club</title>
    <desc>Ally McCoist interviews legendary football manager Sir Alex Ferguson about his life and career.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Krakow, Poland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">British Superbikes Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 British Superbike Championship at Knockhill Racing Circuit in Scotland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FA Disability Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the best action from the 2025 FA Disability Cup at St. George's Park, as six finals were played over one weekend.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day five of the second Test between West Indies and Australia at National Cricket Stadium in Grenada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford, featuring the 2025 Sea Angling Classic.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the 2025 Golden Trail World Series, as the runners take on the Tepec Trail. This diverse course reaches almost 3,000 meters at its highest point.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708103000 +0000" stop="20250708104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708104500 +0000" stop="20250708124500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage three of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the peloton travels 122km from Vezza d'Oglio to the city of Trento.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708124500 +0000" stop="20250708133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Moto 2 race one in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708133000 +0000" stop="20250708141500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the ETC race one in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708141500 +0000" stop="20250708150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the JuniorGP in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708150000 +0000" stop="20250708154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Moto2 race two in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708154500 +0000" stop="20250708163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the ETC race two in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708163000 +0000" stop="20250708171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Stock class of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship in Nevers Magny-Cours.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708171500 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League: Stories of the Finals</title>
    <desc>Take a look back at the 2007 UEFA Champions League final between AC Milan and Liverpool. The Italian side got their revenge for the Miracle of Istanbul two years earlier.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">British Superbikes Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 British Superbike Championship at Knockhill Racing Circuit in Scotland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round seven of British Speedway as Oxford take on Ipswich.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brussels Urban Sessions</title>
    <desc>Action from Women's Freestyle final, part of the BMX Urban Sessions in Brussels.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brussels Urban Sessions</title>
    <desc>Action from Men's Freestyle final, part of the BMX Urban Sessions in Brussels.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We sit down with Claude Makélélé to reflect on the career of a true midfield master. Celebrated for redefining the defensive midfield role, Makélélé shares his memories of life in the Premier League, from joining Chelsea during a transformative era to becoming the heartbeat of a title-winning side. With insight from teammates, coaches, and opponents, we explore the intelligence, discipline, and in</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Seattle Storm travel to face New York Liberty at the Barclays Center. The Storm beat Liberty 89-79 back in June.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709003000 +0000" stop="20250709011500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Moto 2 race one in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709011500 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the ETC race one in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the JuniorGP in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709024500 +0000" stop="20250709033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Moto2 race two in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709033000 +0000" stop="20250709041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the ETC race two in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709041500 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Stock class of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship in Nevers Magny-Cours.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">British Superbikes Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 British Superbike Championship at Knockhill Racing Circuit in Scotland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round seven of British Speedway as Oxford take on Ipswich.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Krakow, Poland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the third One Day International between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R Premadasa International Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709091500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best batting action from the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh in Galle, featuring big centuries by Mushfiqur Rahim and Pathum Nissanka.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709091500 +0000" stop="20250709094500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Rome, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709094500 +0000" stop="20250709104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brussels Urban Sessions</title>
    <desc>Action from Women's Freestyle final, part of the BMX Urban Sessions in Brussels.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709104500 +0000" stop="20250709124500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage four of the 2026 Giro d'Italia Women sees the riders tackle a tough 142km mountain route from Castello Tesino to the town of Pianezze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709124500 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FA Disability Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the best action from the 2025 FA Disability Cup at St. George's Park, as six finals were played over one weekend.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round seven of British Speedway as Oxford take on Ipswich.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709160000 +0000" stop="20250709163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day one of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, including the Thames Challenge Cup, Wargrave Challenge Cup and Wyfold Challenge Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709163000 +0000" stop="20250709170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day two of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, including the Thames Challenge Cup, Wargrave Challenge Cup and Britannia Challenge Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709170000 +0000" stop="20250709173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day three of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, including the Double Sculls Challenge Cup, Diamond Challenge Sculls and Princess Royal Challenge Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709173000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day four of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, including the Queen Mother Challenge Cup, Diamond Challenge Sculls and Princess Royal Challenge Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from day five of the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta, including the semi-finals of the Grand Challenge Cup, Remenham Challenge Cup and Princess Royal Challenge Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709183000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Henley Royal Regatta</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 Henley Royal Regatta finals, including the Grand Challenge Cup, Diamond Challenge Sculls and Remenham Challenge Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Red Bull Cliff Diving World Series</title>
    <desc>Action from the Cliff Diving World Series in the dazzling setting of Polignano a Mare, Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 6 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709213000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We sit down with Claude Makélélé to reflect on the career of a true midfield master. Celebrated for redefining the defensive midfield role, Makélélé shares his memories of life in the Premier League, from joining Chelsea during a transformative era to becoming the heartbeat of a title-winning side. With insight from teammates, coaches, and opponents, we explore the intelligence, discipline, and in</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250709223000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>A look back at the story of the 2024/25 Gallagher Premiership Rugby season, as Bath claimed the title for the first time since 1996.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Summer League Basketball</title>
    <desc>Basketball action from the NBA Summer League.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708073000 +0000" stop="20250708083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708083000 +0000" stop="20250708093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708093000 +0000" stop="20250708103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708103000 +0000" stop="20250708113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708113000 +0000" stop="20250708123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708123000 +0000" stop="20250708133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708133000 +0000" stop="20250708143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708143000 +0000" stop="20250708153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708153000 +0000" stop="20250708163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708163000 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>Top plays from the 2024-25 NFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708183000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">College Football Live</title>
    <desc>ESPN's daily college football show sharing reactions to the day's biggest stories and previews of each week's most important matchups. Kelsey Riggs and Jen Lada host alongside contributors Desmond Howard, Sam Acho, Greg McElroy and Pete Thamel.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708213000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>WNBA news, analysis, highlights and interviews.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709073000 +0000" stop="20250709083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709083000 +0000" stop="20250709093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709093000 +0000" stop="20250709103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709103000 +0000" stop="20250709113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709113000 +0000" stop="20250709123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709123000 +0000" stop="20250709133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709133000 +0000" stop="20250709143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709143000 +0000" stop="20250709153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709153000 +0000" stop="20250709163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709163000 +0000" stop="20250709173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709173000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Atlantic Motorsport Park in Mill Village, Nova Scotia.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709183000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>Dave Hatch and Emily Roberts share their passion for the sport as they interview motorcycle enthusiasts, share hard won tips and tricks, review the latest bikes, and travel to some of the best riding locations across North America.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709213000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250710000000 +0000" stop="20250711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-10</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Summer League Basketball</title>
    <desc>Basketball action from the NBA Summer League.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708140000 +0000" stop="20250708150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708150000 +0000" stop="20250708155200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708155200 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group C.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>Top plays from the 2024-25 NFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708183000 +0000" stop="20250708185200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708185200 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group C.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">College Football Live</title>
    <desc>ESPN's daily college football show sharing reactions to the day's biggest stories and previews of each week's most important matchups. Kelsey Riggs and Jen Lada host alongside contributors Desmond Howard, Sam Acho, Greg McElroy and Pete Thamel.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708213000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>WNBA news, analysis, highlights and interviews.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709100000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709155200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709155200 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group D.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709183000 +0000" stop="20250709185200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709185200 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UEFA Women's EURO 2025</title>
    <desc>Group D.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709213000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Kauffman Stadium in Kansas City, Mo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708003000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI World Cup Mountain Biking</title>
    <desc>Women's UCI Mountain Bike World Series action from the DHI Elite Final in La Thuile, Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI World Cup Mountain Biking</title>
    <desc>Men's UCI Mountain Bike World Series action from the DHI Elite Final in La Thuile, Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708013000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ally's Social Club</title>
    <desc>Ally McCoist interviews legendary football manager Sir Alex Ferguson about his life and career.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the second leg of the 2003/04 UEFA Champions League quarter-final between Deportivo La Coruna and AC Milan at the Riazor Stadium. Milan led 4-0 from the first leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708023000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 2004/05 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Manchester United and Fenerbahce at Old Trafford. The match saw Wayne Rooney make his highly anticipated debut.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the last 16 second leg from the 2004/05 UEFA Champions League between Chelsea and Barcelona at Stamford Bridge. Barca were in the driving seat after a 2-1 first leg win.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708033000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit this 2005/06 UEFA Champions League group stage epic at Ibrox between Rangers and 2004 champions Porto. A tough group also included Inter Milan and Artmedia Bratislava.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at this enthralling 2006/07 UEFA Champions League group stage clash between Manchester United and Gordon Strachan's Celtic at Old Trafford.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708043000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the quarter-final second leg from the 2006/07 UEFA Champions League at Old Trafford between Manchester United and Roma. United had to overturn a 2-1 first leg deficit.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Brighton welcome Wolves to American Express Stadium. Brighton have won their last four league games against Wolves.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708063000 +0000" stop="20250708064500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League: Stories of the Finals</title>
    <desc>Take a look back at the 2007 UEFA Champions League final between AC Milan and Liverpool. The Italian side got their revenge for the Miracle of Istanbul two years earlier.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708064500 +0000" stop="20250708074500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Sri Lanka seek to continue their impressive white ball home form as they face Bangladesh in the first of three ODIs at R Premadasa International Stadium in Colombo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708074500 +0000" stop="20250708084500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the second One Day International between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R Premadasa International Stadium in Colombo. The Lions hold a 1-0 lead in the series.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708084500 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from the third One Day International between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at R Premadasa International Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Rome, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FA Disability Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the best action from the 2025 FA Disability Cup at St. George's Park, as six finals were played over one weekend.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Goals of the Season</title>
    <desc>Revisit the best goals from the 2018/19 season. Three players shared the Golden Boot after Pierre Emerick-Aubameyang equalled Liverpool duo Mo Salah and Sadio Mane as top scorers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708223000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day five of the second Test between West Indies and Australia at National Cricket Stadium in Grenada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage three of the 2025 Giro d'Italia Women, as the peloton travels 122km from Vezza d'Oglio to the city of Trento.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709003000 +0000" stop="20250709021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A look back at UFC 62 from 2006 in Las Vegas, featuring the thrilling headline light heavyweight bout between Chuck Liddell and Renato Sobral.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709021500 +0000" stop="20250709024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Connected</title>
    <desc>UFC Connected brings fans a unique look inside the UFC with exclusive access to fighters, teams and events from around the globe.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709024500 +0000" stop="20250709041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709041500 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ally's Social Club</title>
    <desc>Ally McCoist is joined by Newcastle United legend and the Premier League's all-time leading goalscorer, Alan Shearer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Aston Villa face Newcastle United at Villa Park. The Villans are unbeaten in their last six Premier League home games against the Magpies.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709063000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Nottingham Forest host Arsenal at City Ground. Forest have won their last three home games against Arsenal in all competitions.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Liverpool welcome Chelsea to Anfield. Jurgen Klopp is looking for his 200th Premier League win in charge of the Reds.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709093000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Tottenham host Brentford at Tottenham Hotspur Stadium. Spurs have lost just one of their last nine league games against Brentford.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League</title>
    <desc>Action from the Premier League as Manchester City take on Burnley at Etihad Stadium. Burnley are winless in 16 top-flight away games against Man City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709123000 +0000" stop="20250709133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Watch our favourite interviews and moments from last season, all featuring British Sign Language and subtitles. Guests include Arne Slot, Phil Foden, John McGinn and Eberechi Eze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709133000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action between St Kilda and Hawthorn at Marvel Stadium. The Hawks have not lost at this venue for almost two years.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Sydney Swans face Fremantle at the SCG. Can the Dockers extend their winning streak to seven games?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709163000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Adelaide Crows take on Melbourne at Adelaide Oval. Can the Crows continue their push for a first finals appearance in eight seasons?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage four of the 2026 Giro d'Italia Women sees the riders tackle a tough 142km mountain route from Castello Tesino to the town of Pianezze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage five and the first individual time trial of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders tackle a 33km chrono race in the historic port city of Caen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brussels Urban Sessions</title>
    <desc>Action from Men's Freestyle final, part of the BMX Urban Sessions in Brussels.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wimbledon 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from Wimbledon, the third of the four tennis Grand Slams each year.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709223000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Giro d'Italia Women</title>
    <desc>Stage four of the 2026 Giro d'Italia Women sees the riders tackle a tough 142km mountain route from Castello Tesino to the town of Pianezze.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de France Cycling</title>
    <desc>Highlights from stage five and the first individual time trial of the 2025 Tour de France, as the riders tackle a 33km chrono race in the historic port city of Caen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708004500 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gruppetto</title>
    <desc>We review the opening weekend of the Tour de France and opening stage of the Giro D'Italia Women's races.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Connected</title>
    <desc>UFC Connected brings fans a unique look inside the UFC with exclusive access to fighters, teams and events from around the globe.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708013000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Reloaded</title>
    <desc>We revisit UFC 218, one of the most exciting cards of 2017, as Max Holloway successfully defended his featherweight belt against Jose Aldo in the main event in Detroit.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford, featuring the 2025 Sea Angling Classic.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Inter look to get their Serie A title challenge back on track as they host Patrick Vieira's Genoa at San Siro. Nerazzurri are unbeaten in their last 11 league games against Genoa.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Juventus return to Serie A action as they travel to face Cagliari at Unipol Domus. How will Juve respond after their disappointing UEFA Champions League exit?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Napoli host Inter at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Can the champions stop Inter's title charge, or will the Nerazzurri dominate in Naples?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action from San Siro as AC Milan face Lazio. Can the Rossoneri secure a crucial win, or will Lazio stun them in Milan?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A clash as Lazio host Udinese at Stadio Olimpico. Can Lazio continue their push for Europe, or will Udinese cause an upset in Rome?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Juventus take on Atalanta at the Allianz Stadium. A crucial battle for the top four-can Juve assert dominance, or will Atalanta strike in Turin?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A showdown as Fiorentina host Juventus at the Stadio Artemio Franchi. Can Fiorentina rise to the challenge, or will Juve take control in Florence?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as West Coast Eagles take on GWS Giants at Optus Stadium. Can finals hopefuls the Giants avoid a slip up against the bottom-placed Eagles?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708143000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Essendon face Gold Coast Suns at Marvel Stadium. Can the injury-hit Bombers put a dent in the Suns' top-eight push?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Geelong Cats take on Richmond at GMHBA Stadium. The Tigers have not won on the Cats' home deck since 2006.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as Brisbane Lions and Port Adelaide face-off at the Gabba. Can the Lions avoid an upset against the resurgent Power?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Seattle Storm travel to face New York Liberty at the Barclays Center. The Storm beat Liberty 89-79 back in June.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global Champions Tour</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the Longines Global Champions Tour and the 2025 Grand Prix of Monaco, as the best riders in the world compete in a breathtaking waterfront setting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford, featuring the 2025 Sea Angling Classic.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultra-Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>UTMB World Series highlights from the 2025 Salzburg Ultra Trail, taking participants through beautiful Austrian scenery and ending in the world-famous city of Mozart.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as West Coast Eagles take on GWS Giants at Optus Stadium. Can finals hopefuls the Giants avoid a slip up against the bottom-placed Eagles?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709003000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Essendon face Gold Coast Suns at Marvel Stadium. Can the injury-hit Bombers put a dent in the Suns' top-eight push?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Geelong Cats take on Richmond at GMHBA Stadium. The Tigers have not won on the Cats' home deck since 2006.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709033000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>AFL action as Brisbane Lions and Port Adelaide face-off at the Gabba. Can the Lions avoid an upset against the resurgent Power?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A clash as Atalanta face Inter at the Gewiss Stadium. A key battle in the title race-can Atalanta stop Inter's momentum, or will the Nerazzurri prevail in Bergamo?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Marco Baroni's Lazio face Paolo Vanoli's Torino at Stadio Olimpico. How will Lazio respond after their 5-0 defeat to Bologna last time out?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as title contenders Napoli host AC Milan at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Milan are unbeaten in each of their last six away matches against Napoli.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as AC Milan take on Raffaele Palladino's Fiorentina at San Siro. The Viola could record a league double over Milan for the first time since 2000/01.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Roma face Juventus at Stadio Olimpico. Can the Giallorossi make it nine league wins in a row, or will Igor Tudor pick up back-to-back wins in charge of Juve?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709100000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action from Derby della Capitale as Lazio and Roma battle it out at Stadio Olimpico. Roma could do the league double over Lazio for the first time since 2015/16.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as Napoli face Empoli at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Antonio Conte's Napoli have won just two of their last nine league games.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as Parma host Juventus at Stadio Ennio Tardini. The Ducali could avoid defeat in both league matches against the Bianconeri for the first time since 2010/11.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Action from Serie A as AC Milan host Atalanta at San Siro. Milan have lost two of their last three league games against the Black and Blues.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>The Serie A title race continues to heat up as league leaders Inter host Roma at San Siro. Can Simone Inzaghi's side secure a big win to pile the pressure on Napoli?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Serie A action as title contenders Napoli face Torino at Stadio Diego Armando Maradona. Can Antonio Conte's side take another huge step towards a fourth Scudetto?</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709160000 +0000" stop="20250709170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serie A Football</title>
    <desc>Inter look to get their hunt for a 21st Scudetto back on track as they welcome Hellas Verona to San Siro. Verona have never won away against Inter in Serie A.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709170000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round seven the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Malilla's Skrotfrag Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>A review of the second Test between West Indies and Australia at National Cricket Stadium in Grenada.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Moto 2 race one in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709204500 +0000" stop="20250709213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the ETC race one in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709213000 +0000" stop="20250709221500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the JuniorGP in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709221500 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Moto2 race two in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250709234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the ETC race two in Nevers Magny-Cours, part of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250709234500 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM JuniorGP World Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from the Stock class of the 2025 FIM JuniorGP Championship in Nevers Magny-Cours.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Summer League Basketball</title>
    <desc>Basketball action from the NBA Summer League.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708073000 +0000" stop="20250708083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708083000 +0000" stop="20250708093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708093000 +0000" stop="20250708103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708103000 +0000" stop="20250708113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708113000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">College Football Live</title>
    <desc>ESPN's daily college football show sharing reactions to the day's biggest stories and previews of each week's most important matchups. Kelsey Riggs and Jen Lada host alongside contributors Desmond Howard, Sam Acho, Greg McElroy and Pete Thamel.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708213000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>WNBA news, analysis, highlights and interviews.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709073000 +0000" stop="20250709083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709083000 +0000" stop="20250709093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709093000 +0000" stop="20250709103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709103000 +0000" stop="20250709113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709113000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709213000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Kauffman Stadium in Kansas City, Mo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708013000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Ice</title>
    <desc>John Saunders profiles black college hockey players Mike Grier and Anson Carter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708043000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708053000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708063000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708073000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708083000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708093000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708103000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708113000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708123000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708133000 +0000" stop="20250708140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708140000 +0000" stop="20250708143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708143000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 for 30</title>
    <desc>On June 15, 2011, Vancouver hosts Game 7 of the Stanley Cup Finals between the Canucks and Boston Bruins; when Boston stuns the home team to win the Cup, the situation quickly devolves.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708163000 +0000" stop="20250708170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708170000 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708193000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Athletes Unlimited Softball League</title>
    <desc>From The Stadium at the Parkway Bank Sports Complex in Rosemont, Ill.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709010000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709043000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709053000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709063000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709073000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709083000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Wimbledon Tennis Primetime</title>
    <desc>Action and highlights from the day's matches at the 2025 Wimbledon Championships.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Wimbledon Championships</title>
    <desc>From the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, England.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">College Football Live</title>
    <desc>ESPN's daily college football show sharing reactions to the day's biggest stories and previews of each week's most important matchups. Kelsey Riggs and Jen Lada host alongside contributors Desmond Howard, Sam Acho, Greg McElroy and Pete Thamel.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708213000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Wimbledon Tennis Primetime</title>
    <desc>Action and highlights from the day's matches at the 2025 Wimbledon Championships.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the second ODI match between England and West Indies, where they compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708132000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708132000 +0000" stop="20250708133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708133000 +0000" stop="20250708164000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Women's T20 Blast Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the professional women's Twenty20 cricket league in England and Wales.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708164000 +0000" stop="20250708171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708171000 +0000" stop="20250708172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708172000 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708204000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the professional Twenty20 cricket league in England and Wales.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708204000 +0000" stop="20250708211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708211000 +0000" stop="20250708213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708213000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250708235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250708235000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709031000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Grand Prairie Stadium in Grand Prairie, Texas.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709031000 +0000" stop="20250709034000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709034000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's Twenty20 International match between England and India.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709100000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709160000 +0000" stop="20250709170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's Twenty20 International match between England and India.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709170000 +0000" stop="20250709172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709172000 +0000" stop="20250709173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709173000 +0000" stop="20250709204000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Women's International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709204000 +0000" stop="20250709211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709211000 +0000" stop="20250709213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709213000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's Twenty20 International match between England and India.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250709235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250709235000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250710000000 +0000" stop="20250711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Grand Prairie Stadium in Grand Prairie, Texas.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-10</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
