<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610000000 +0000" stop="20250610010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a crucial witness in the case of a fatal hate crime against a Muslim family is deported, Barba must drop the charges against a suspect, resulting in rising tensions between communities on either side of the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610010000 +0000" stop="20250610020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The release of a suspect in a hate crime case leaves Benson and Barba caught between two families seeking justice; as public protests escalate to violence, Benson goes to desperate lengths to make an arrest.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Fin crosses international borders to catch a fugitive rapist; a political tug-of-war derails Barba's legal case; shocking allegations against Benson lead to the return of an old friend.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry must escape an outer space prison to stop a dangerous threat in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins and Carisi suspect a woman's bizarre rape story is fabricated; Benson goes on the offensive when her personal life is scrutinized.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a man is found castrated and left for dead, Rollins and Carisi uncover three female suspects who have possible motives; Langan gives devastating news to Benson.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a janitor violently attacks a coach, the SVU team connects the janitor's behavior to a history of sexual abuse; the detectives find more victims of the same predator -- including a prisoner (Mike Tyson) on death row.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A mother of two who vanishes during a storm turns out to be a victim of something sinister.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>After a woman goes missing on Blood Mountain in the Chattahoochee National Forest, authorities suspect the man responsible was reenacting a horror movie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>After a woman goes missing on Blood Mountain in the Chattahoochee National Forest, authorities suspect the man responsible was reenacting a horror movie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Callen poses as a patient in a mental health facility to find an NSA agent who vanished while tracking an ISIS cell that was attempting to cross the Mexican border.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>An attack on a graduate student working on a new electromagnetic weapon for the Navy is linked to international warfare; Kensi struggles with physical therapy for her spinal injury.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Callen must interrogate his father after he is found in a patient's hospital room during a radiation poisoning case; members of the team discusses their plans for Thanksgiving.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an underage runaway is found beaten and raped, the SVU team works with federal prosecutor Connie Rubirosa (Alana De La Garza); ADA Barba suspects a cover-up when he fails to get the help he needs from Jersey law enforcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610140000 +0000" stop="20250610150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro suspects the boyfriend of a missing girl is involved with a gang; Sgt. Benson becomes the SVU's new commanding officer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610150000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The already frantic search for a missing diabetic boy becomes more urgent when he is spotted with a couple known for child endangerment and pornography.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a controversial misogynistic comic is accused of rape, Benson is happy to arrest him, but Barba feels the case is weak.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Rollins is contacted by a hometown friend when his nephew, a high school football star, goes missing in New York; Rollins seeks help with her escalating problems.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Rollins strikes a deal with the managers of a gambling club in order to protect her job, she ends up drawing the suspicion of Benson and Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson is assigned a 24/7 security detail when William Lewis (Pablo Schreiber) escapes from prison and starts killing again; Benson must decide how much she is willing to sacrifice to save a child's life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Sgt. Olivia Benson is investigated by Internal Affairs after William Lewis' death; as pressure mounts, Olivia has to choose between her convictions and her badge.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teenager disappears after schoolmates make her the subject of a vicious cyberbullying attack.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610220000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An old kidnapping case is reopened when a young woman is found wandering in Central Park; Carisi's conversation with a reporter puts him in hot water.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenage girl is found dead, Rollins goes under cover at a high-end rehab center where the victim was last seen; Benson tries to overcome her doubts about Sheila.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson must disclose the secrets of her past to help a rape victim recall the details of one terrible, traumatic night.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611010000 +0000" stop="20250611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU investigates a case involving two students in a special needs school; Rollins discovers that one child's medical issues stem from a surprising source.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611020000 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins races to rescue a girl being held captive by her father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young woman takes a man hostage at gunpoint; Benson makes an attempt to defuse the situation; the team discovers the shocking motive behind the abduction.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson's suspicions about a kidnapping victim uncover a dangerous criminal network prepared to silence anyone who gets in its way.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a masked pizza deliveryman assaults a seemingly random couple in their home, SVU must unravel a complicated revenge plot before anyone else is victimized.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an underage runaway is found beaten and raped, the SVU team works with federal prosecutor Connie Rubirosa (Alana De La Garza); ADA Barba suspects a cover-up when he fails to get the help he needs from Jersey law enforcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro suspects the boyfriend of a missing girl is involved with a gang; Sgt. Benson becomes the SVU's new commanding officer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a controversial misogynistic comic is accused of rape, Benson is happy to arrest him, but Barba feels the case is weak.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Rollins is contacted by a hometown friend when his nephew, a high school football star, goes missing in New York; Rollins seeks help with her escalating problems.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey returns to work after a brush with death; Shay's new partner is friendly to everyone but her; Dawson begins training; Severide prepares for his instructor duties; Clarke refuses to talk to the police about the murder.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611110000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey tries to convince everyone he is healthy; Shay avoids the lawyer who wants to talk about Daryl's suicide; Otis and Katie grow closer; Boden helps a woman with a negligent landlord.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A call to the field may throw a wrench in Dawson's plan to retake the firefighter exam; the firehouse welcomes a new addition; Boden makes a bold move.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey deals with the fallout from his sister's divorce; Dawson and Mills settle into their new roles at the station; Brett can't decide what she wants to do; the Molly's crew struggles to get the food truck started.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611140000 +0000" stop="20250611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey helps his sister and faces down his corrupt brother-in-law; Brett goes out of her way to assist a mother in need; Mills learns about unlicensed private investigation; Dawson starts training with Herrmann.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611150000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey discovers a new crack house on the block that's harboring a female junkie; a new trainee gets Dawson and Brett into trouble; Severide gets an unexpected visit from his father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey reunites with a former colleague; Dawson and Brett serve their time in retraining; Severide tries to fix what's going on with Anna.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Reeling from Dawson's continued absence, Casey makes a rash move during a rescue, while Brett struggles with a series of replacement partners; meanwhile, Boden faces scrutiny from Commissioner Grissom, who sends his deputy to monitor Firehouse 51.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mouch, Gallo, Ritter and Mackey report for training; a nasty blow to the head brings Casey unimaginable pain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A series of suspicious fires sends 51 on a search for the cause; Casey continues down a troubling path; Mouch is looking to make his long-awaited dream come true.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A new recruit with ties to the CFD tests Serveride's patience; Violet receives a mysterious note that sends her and Brett on a hunt for the person who wrote it.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611210000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Boden, Kidd and Severide work together to protect one of their own; at the Fire Academy, Herrmann meets an inspiring young man; talk of the annual CFD Gala dominates the firehouse.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Seager team up to investigate a fire at the home of a troubled young woman; Pelham moves into 51's rumored cursed office; Kylie assists Kidd with Girls on Fire.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>After witnessing a domestic dispute, Brett and Violet decide to take the investigation into their own hands; Mouch vets Truck 81's new firefighter; Herrmann relies on something new to aid him on the job.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy</title>
    <desc>An ancient Egyptian princess is awakened from her crypt beneath the desert, bringing with her malevolence grown over millennia, and terrors that defy human comprehension.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610014500 +0000" stop="20250610024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Las Vegas Aces face Golden State Valkyries at Chase Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610024500 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Goals Reload</title>
    <desc>The pick of the goals from the 2024/25 UEFA Champions League quarter-finals, semi-finals and final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Seb Hines' Orlando Pride take on Fabrice Gautrat's Houston Dash at Inter &amp; Co Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Washington Spirit and North Carolina Courage face-off at Audi Field.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Prague, Czech Republic, featuring the Men's and Women's Bouldering final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610071500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League Goals Reload</title>
    <desc>The pick of the goals from the 2024/25 UEFA Europa League quarter-finals, semi-finals and final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610071500 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Fara Williams, England Women's most-capped player, joins Rolf and Damaris to look back at the Premier League, Champions League and Women's Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of Criterium du Dauphine, as the riders journey 204km from Premilhat to Issoire.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Cup Road Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from the 2025 Antwerp Port Epic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global Champions Tour</title>
    <desc>Longines Global Champions Tour action from the 2025 Grand Prix of Cannes at Stade des Hesperides.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>It's challenge time as Rob takes on top match angler Andy May in a carp versus match challenge, and Andy Ford heads out on the river Itchen with The Mulletman Colin Macleod.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Off The Bat</title>
    <desc>All the latest action from Major League Baseball wrapped up, featuring the league's top hitters and pitchers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610133000 +0000" stop="20250610153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610153000 +0000" stop="20250610154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endurance Uncovered</title>
    <desc>An inside look at the World Endurance Championship, a global series of races that test the limits of both drivers and vehicles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610154500 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Fara Williams, England Women's most-capped player, joins Rolf and Damaris to look back at the Premier League, Champions League and Women's Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Magazine</title>
    <desc>We review all the stories and drama from the 2024/25 UEFA Champions League season, as a new league phase format was introduced and Luis Enrique's Paris Saint-Germain made history.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610173000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We chart the rise of Portuguese star Rúben Dias, from his early days in Portugal to the heart of Manchester City's defence. We meet the family, friends, and coaches who shaped his journey, offering a rare glimpse into the upbringing and mindset that forged a Premier League leader. Then, in Manchester, Rúben reflects on his career so far, his impact at City, and the values that continue to drive hi</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Review</title>
    <desc>A review of the 2024/25 Premier League season, as Southampton endured a campaign to forget and Arne Slot made history in charge of Liverpool.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from SailGP in New York, as 12 F50s battled for glory against the backdrop of one of the most famous cityscapes in the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endurance Uncovered</title>
    <desc>An inside look at the World Endurance Championship, a global series of races that test the limits of both drivers and vehicles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610211500 +0000" stop="20250610213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Rewind</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610213000 +0000" stop="20250610220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Rally-Raid Championship</title>
    <desc>World Rally Raid Championship action from the 2025 South African Safari Rally.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610220000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250610233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Lead Off</title>
    <desc>A look at the upcoming MLB action, including New York Yankees @ Kansas City Royals.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250610233000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as New York Yankees face Kansas City Royals.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611024500 +0000" stop="20250611031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best MLB action, including New York Yankees @ Kansas City Royals.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611031500 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Series Film</title>
    <desc>The Yankees seemed indestructible, winning 16 of 19 World Series games they had played over the previous five years. But the Diamondbacks - led by Curt Schilling and Randy Johnson - were unafraid of the pinstriped juggernaut.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Another chance to watch the 2015/16 Premier League clash between West Ham and Manchester United as the Hammers marked their departure from Upton Park with a thrilling victory.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611053000 +0000" stop="20250611063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611063000 +0000" stop="20250611073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from SailGP in New York, as 12 F50s battled for glory against the backdrop of one of the most famous cityscapes in the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611073000 +0000" stop="20250611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611083000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the 2025 Roland-Garros Women's Singles as the top two seeds, Belarusian Aryna Sabalenka and American Coco Gauff, vie for glory on Court Philippe-Chatrier.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Men's Singles final at Roland-Garros as world number one Jannik Sinner must overcome defending champion Carlos Alcaraz to claim a maiden title win in Paris.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>A review of the fourth race of the 2025 Golden Trail World Series, as the world's best trail runners took on the Zegama-Aizkorri mountain marathon in Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611133000 +0000" stop="20250611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of Criterium du Dauphine, as the riders take on an individual time-trial from Charmes-sur-Rhone to Saint-Peray.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611153000 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from SailGP in New York, as 12 F50s battled for glory against the backdrop of one of the most famous cityscapes in the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Milwaukee Brewers face Atlanta Braves.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611211500 +0000" stop="20250611231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as San Diego Padres face Los Angeles Dodgers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611231500 +0000" stop="20250611234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fight Week</title>
    <desc>A review of UFC 316 at Prudential Center as Merab Dvalishvili defended his bantamweight title against former champion Sean O'Malley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250611234500 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Connected</title>
    <desc>Austin Vanderford opens up about his unbreakable bond with combat sports veteran Paige VanZant. And, Welsh welterweight fighter Oban Elliott reveals what keeps him focused.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610013000 +0000" stop="20250610020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fight Week</title>
    <desc>A review of UFC 316 at Prudential Center as Merab Dvalishvili defended his bantamweight title against former champion Sean O'Malley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of Criterium du Dauphine, as the riders journey 204km from Premilhat to Issoire.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Cup Road Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from the 2025 Antwerp Port Epic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Formula E Flashback</title>
    <desc>Relive the thrilling action from the 2017 Montreal ePrix. Championship contenders Sebastien Buemi and Lucas di Grassi battled for valuable points in this season-defining race.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610043000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Formula E Flashback</title>
    <desc>We revisit the best action from the 2018 Punta del Este ePrix. The race would feature a breathtaking final lap with Jean-Eric Vergne, Lucas di Grassi and Sam Bird in contention.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto3 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>MotoGP action from the Grand Prix of Aragon Sprint Race at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610073000 +0000" stop="20250610083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610083000 +0000" stop="20250610093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610093000 +0000" stop="20250610103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610103000 +0000" stop="20250610113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the first One Day International between Ireland and West Indies at Clontarf Cricket Club. This is the West Indies' first game in Ireland since 2019.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610113000 +0000" stop="20250610123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the third One Day International between Ireland and West Indies at Clontarf Cricket Club in Dublin. Can the visitors salvage a series draw?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610123000 +0000" stop="20250610133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Action from the Gallagher Premiership Rugby semi-final between Bath Rugby and Bristol Bears at the Recreation Ground. Bristol won 36-14 when these sides met in May.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610133000 +0000" stop="20250610143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Action from the Gallagher Premiership Rugby semi-final between Leicester Tigers and Sale Sharks at Mattioli Woods Welford Road. The Tigers won 44-34 against the Sharks last month.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610143000 +0000" stop="20250610153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto3 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610153000 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>MotoGP action from the Grand Prix of Aragon Sprint Race at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round five of British Speedway as Leicester take on Sheffield.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Rally-Raid Championship</title>
    <desc>World Rally Raid Championship action from the 2025 South African Safari Rally.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610203000 +0000" stop="20250610213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610213000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>Charting George Dowell's determination to transform his childhood club Worthing FC into a National League team after saving it from financial ruin.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Joe Salisbury and Neal Skupski look to become Britain's first Men's Doubles champions at Roland-Garros since 1933, as they take on Marcel Granollers and Horacio Zeballos.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Roland-Garros Women's Doubles final, as Italian pair Jasmine Paolini and Sara Errani take on Aleksandra Krunic and Anna Danilina.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611010000 +0000" stop="20250611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the Roland-Garros Mixed Doubles, as Americans Taylor Townsend and Evan King take on Italian pair Sara Errani and Andrea Vavassori.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611020000 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Yui Kamiji seeks her fifth Roland-Garros Women's Wheelchair Singles title as she takes on Dutch second seed Aniek Van Koot.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Prague, Czech Republic, featuring the Men's and Women's Bouldering final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round five of British Speedway as Leicester take on Sheffield.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto3 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>MotoGP action from the Grand Prix of Aragon Sprint Race at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611083000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611103000 +0000" stop="20250611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Prague, Czech Republic, featuring the Men's and Women's Bouldering final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611113000 +0000" stop="20250611114500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reframe the Game</title>
    <desc>This is the story of trailblazer Carol Glenn, the first black woman to become a race official in the UK, as she sets out on a new venture to launch her own race team.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611114500 +0000" stop="20250611151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>FIA World Endurance Championship action from the first free practice session ahead of the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611151500 +0000" stop="20250611161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Speedway</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round five of British Speedway as Leicester take on Sheffield.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611161500 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reframe the Game</title>
    <desc>A young woman is uprooted from her country in terrifying circumstances. After a headline-hitting evacuation to the UK, she finds a new home and community in a Yorkshire football club.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611181500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>FIA World Endurance Championship action from the qualifying session ahead of the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611181500 +0000" stop="20250611184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611184500 +0000" stop="20250611194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611194500 +0000" stop="20250611221500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>FIA World Endurance Championship action from the second free practice session ahead of the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611221500 +0000" stop="20250611231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of Criterium du Dauphine, as the riders take on an individual time-trial from Charmes-sur-Rhone to Saint-Peray.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250611231500 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Crypto.com Arena in Los Angeles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610073000 +0000" stop="20250610083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610083000 +0000" stop="20250610093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610093000 +0000" stop="20250610103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610103000 +0000" stop="20250610113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610113000 +0000" stop="20250610123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610123000 +0000" stop="20250610133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610133000 +0000" stop="20250610143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610143000 +0000" stop="20250610153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610153000 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610173000 +0000" stop="20250610183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610183000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610213000 +0000" stop="20250610220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610220000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Canadian Shield Soccer Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage for Canadian Shield soccer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611003000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's International Soccer Friendlies</title>
    <desc>From BMO Field in Toronto.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611073000 +0000" stop="20250611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611083000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611103000 +0000" stop="20250611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611113000 +0000" stop="20250611123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611123000 +0000" stop="20250611133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611133000 +0000" stop="20250611143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611143000 +0000" stop="20250611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611153000 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611210000 +0000" stop="20250611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611213000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Fenway Park in Boston.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Crypto.com Arena in Los Angeles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610140000 +0000" stop="20250610150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610150000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610183000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's International Friendly Football</title>
    <desc>From BMO Field in Toronto.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Canadian Shield Soccer Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage for Canadian Shield soccer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611003000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's International Soccer Friendlies</title>
    <desc>From BMO Field in Toronto.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611110000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611140000 +0000" stop="20250611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611150000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of various sailing grand prix races from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 FIFA World Cup: 1 Year to Go Special</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Fenway Park in Boston.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610000000 +0000" stop="20250610010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 Moto2 Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610010000 +0000" stop="20250610013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>MotoGP action from the Grand Prix of Aragon Sprint Race at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610013000 +0000" stop="20250610023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610023000 +0000" stop="20250610033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610033000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What I Wore</title>
    <desc>Liverpool and England legend John Barnes describes his passion for football via the shirts which have defined his life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Connected</title>
    <desc>Austin Vanderford opens up about his unbreakable bond with combat sports veteran Paige VanZant. And, Welsh welterweight fighter Oban Elliott reveals what keeps him focused.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610043000 +0000" stop="20250610044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kenny Allstar's Number 1s</title>
    <desc>The latest episode of Kenny Allstar's Number 1s, featuring UFC star Paddy Pimblett.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610044500 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reframe the Game</title>
    <desc>This is the story of trailblazer Carol Glenn, the first black woman to become a race official in the UK, as she sets out on a new venture to launch her own race team.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Yui Kamiji seeks her fifth Roland-Garros Women's Wheelchair Singles title as she takes on Dutch second seed Aniek Van Koot.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the Roland-Garros Mixed Doubles, as Americans Taylor Townsend and Evan King take on Italian pair Sara Errani and Andrea Vavassori.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Roland-Garros Women's Doubles final, as Italian pair Jasmine Paolini and Sara Errani take on Aleksandra Krunic and Anna Danilina.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Joe Salisbury and Neal Skupski look to become Britain's first Men's Doubles champions at Roland-Garros since 1933, as they take on Marcel Granollers and Horacio Zeballos.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the 2025 Roland-Garros Women's Singles as the top two seeds, Belarusian Aryna Sabalenka and American Coco Gauff, vie for glory on Court Philippe-Chatrier.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610103000 +0000" stop="20250610123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Men's Singles final at Roland-Garros as world number one Jannik Sinner must overcome defending champion Carlos Alcaraz to claim a maiden title win in Paris.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610123000 +0000" stop="20250610133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of Criterium du Dauphine, as the riders journey 204km from Premilhat to Issoire.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610133000 +0000" stop="20250610153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610153000 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Cup Road Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from the 2025 Antwerp Port Epic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB: Off The Bat</title>
    <desc>All the latest action from Major League Baseball wrapped up, featuring the league's top hitters and pitchers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Men's Singles final at Roland-Garros as world number one Jannik Sinner must overcome defending champion Carlos Alcaraz to claim a maiden title win in Paris.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the 2025 Roland-Garros Women's Singles as the top two seeds, Belarusian Aryna Sabalenka and American Coco Gauff, vie for glory on Court Philippe-Chatrier.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610203000 +0000" stop="20250610233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC 316 at Prudential Center in New Jersey, featuring the bantamweight title bout between Merab Dvalishvili and former champion Sean O'Malley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250610233000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UFC Connected</title>
    <desc>Austin Vanderford opens up about his unbreakable bond with combat sports veteran Paige VanZant. And, Welsh welterweight fighter Oban Elliott reveals what keeps him focused.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611004500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MX2 race one at Kegums in Latvia.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611004500 +0000" stop="20250611013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MX2 race two at Kegums in Latvia.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611013000 +0000" stop="20250611021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MXGP race one at Kegums in Latvia.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611021500 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM World Championship Motocross Racing</title>
    <desc>Motocross World Championship action from MXGP race two at Kegums in Latvia.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP Chequered Flag</title>
    <desc>Post-race show featuring analysis, highlights and interviews with all the key riders following the Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Race action from the 2025 MotoGP Grand Prix of Aragon at MotorLand Aragon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League play-off second leg as Slovan Bratislava face Midtjylland. The tie is in the balance after a 1-1 draw in the first leg.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Young Boys host Aston Villa at Wankdorf Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611073000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Juventus take on PSV Eindhoven at Allianz Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Bayern Munich meet Dinamo Zagreb at Allianz Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611083000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as champions Real Madrid face Stuttgart at Santiago Bernabeu Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Celtic face Slovan Bratislava at Celtic Park.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Feyenoord face Bayer Leverkusen at De Kuip.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Monaco and Barcelona face-off at Stade Louis II.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611103000 +0000" stop="20250611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League and Conference League Magazine</title>
    <desc>A review of the 2024/25 UEFA Conference League season, as Enzo Maresca's Chelsea stormed their way to the final and familiar faces inspired Real Betis to make history.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611113000 +0000" stop="20250611123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League and Conference League Magazine</title>
    <desc>A review of the 2024/25 UEFA Europa League season, as Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United enjoyed a welcome distraction from their domestic woes.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611123000 +0000" stop="20250611133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611133000 +0000" stop="20250611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of Criterium du Dauphine, as the riders take on an individual time-trial from Charmes-sur-Rhone to Saint-Peray.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611153000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League: Stories of the Finals</title>
    <desc>We take a look back at Marseille's UEFA Champions League final against AC Milan's famous team in 1993 and Barcelona's victory over Juventus in the 2015 final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 2 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611193000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We chart the rise of Portuguese star Rúben Dias, from his early days in Portugal to the heart of Manchester City's defence. We meet the family, friends, and coaches who shaped his journey, offering a rare glimpse into the upbringing and mindset that forged a Premier League leader. Then, in Manchester, Rúben reflects on his career so far, his impact at City, and the values that continue to drive hi</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as San Diego Padres face Los Angeles Dodgers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611231500 +0000" stop="20250611234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250611234500 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prime 9</title>
    <desc>A countdown of the nine greatest animal nicknames of all-time.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610003000 +0000" stop="20250610020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Melbourne take on Collingwood at the MCG. Can the Magpies continue their impressive form?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>It's challenge time as Rob takes on top match angler Andy May in a carp versus match challenge, and Andy Ford heads out on the river Itchen with The Mulletman Colin Macleod.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Action from the Gallagher Premiership Rugby semi-final between Bath Rugby and Bristol Bears at the Recreation Ground. Bristol won 36-14 when these sides met in May.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Action from the Gallagher Premiership Rugby semi-final between Leicester Tigers and Sale Sharks at Mattioli Woods Welford Road. The Tigers won 44-34 against the Sharks last month.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Western Bulldogs face Hawthorn at Marvel Stadium. The Dogs have won their last nine matches at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610063000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Adelaide Crows take on Brisbane Lions at Adelaide Oval. The Lions have only won four times in 14 matches at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Richmond face a struggling Sydney Swans side at the MCG. The Swans have only won two of their past 10 matches at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610093000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Geelong Cats meet Gold Coast Suns at GMHBA Stadium. The Cats could overtake the Suns with a win.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Prague, Czech Republic, featuring the Men's and Women's Bouldering final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Las Vegas Aces face Golden State Valkyries at Chase Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 1 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder face Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center. Can the Pacers pull off yet another upset?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610143000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 2 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder face Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center. The Pacers edged the thrilling finals opener, stunning the Thunder with a 111-110 win.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Originals</title>
    <desc>Dikembe Mutombo is widely considered one of the best shot-blockers and defensive players of all time. We look back at his incredible journey in the NBA.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Seb Hines' Orlando Pride take on Fabrice Gautrat's Houston Dash at Inter &amp; Co Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610173000 +0000" stop="20250610183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Washington Spirit and North Carolina Courage face-off at Audi Field.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610183000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Western Bulldogs face Hawthorn at Marvel Stadium. The Dogs have won their last nine matches at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Adelaide Crows take on Brisbane Lions at Adelaide Oval. The Lions have only won four times in 14 matches at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610213000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Richmond face a struggling Sydney Swans side at the MCG. The Swans have only won two of their past 10 matches at this venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Geelong Cats meet Gold Coast Suns at GMHBA Stadium. The Cats could overtake the Suns with a win.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611003000 +0000" stop="20250611013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Critérium du Dauphiné Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of Criterium du Dauphine. This is the longest stage of the race, taking the riders 207km from Brioude to Charantonnay.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611013000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC Review</title>
    <desc>A look back at the latest action from the 2025 World Rally Championship and Rally Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WRC: More Than Machine</title>
    <desc>The M-Sport test their drivers for the upcoming season, determined to find the next leading contender. Step behind the scenes to see how these young drivers battle adversity.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fight Week</title>
    <desc>A review of UFC 316 at Prudential Center as Merab Dvalishvili defended his bantamweight title against former champion Sean O'Malley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611033000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 2 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder face Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center. The Pacers edged the thrilling finals opener, stunning the Thunder with a 111-110 win.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as GWS Giants face Port Adelaide at Corroboree Group Manuka Oval. Can the Giants make it three wins on the spin?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611063000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as North Melbourne take on West Coast Eagles at Hands Oval. Who will triumph in this meeting between two struggling sides?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Carlton and Essendon face-off at the MCG. The Blues will be looking to find some form after losing three of their last four matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Melbourne take on Collingwood at the MCG. Can the Magpies continue their impressive form?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611110000 +0000" stop="20250611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We take a look back at this thrilling encounter between Manchester United and Liverpool at Old Trafford. Mark Hughes scored twice late on to earn the hosts a share of the spoils.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611113000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit this seven-goal thriller between Chelsea and Tottenham at Stamford Bridge. Mark Stein scored a last-gasp penalty to snatch all three points for Glenn Hoddle's side.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We take a look back at this clash between the two Manchester rivals. City raced into a two-goal lead but it was the visitors who took the points after Eric Cantona's late winner.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611123000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit this classic 1994/95 clash between Tottenham Hotspur and Newcastle United at White Hart Lane. The match featured a stunning hat-trick from an England international.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Take a look back at one of the Premier League's classic derby matches between Everton and Liverpool. The points looked to be shared before Gary McAllister stepped up late on.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611133000 +0000" stop="20250611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit West Ham's trip to Stamford Bridge to face Chelsea in the 2002/03 Premier League season. Paulo Di Canio's brace earned the visitors their first win of the season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611140000 +0000" stop="20250611143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We take a look back at this classic Premier League clash between Tottenham and Leicester. The visitors thought they had snatched the win until Jermain Defoe's late leveller.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611143000 +0000" stop="20250611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Revisit Aston Villa and Chelsea's five-goal classic from the 2003/4 Premier League. Villa were pushing for a UEFA Cup spot while Chelsea hoped to keep pace with leaders Arsenal.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611150000 +0000" stop="20250611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the six-goal 2007/08 Premier League epic between Fulham and Tottenham at Craven Cottage. With pressure mounting on manager Martin Jol, Spurs desperately needed a win.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611153000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Take a look back at this classic Premier League clash between Manchester United and Liverpool. Dimitar Berbatov stole the show with a hat-trick for Sir Alex Ferguson's side.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We take a look back at this epic Premier League clash from the 2012/13 season as Arsenal and Fulham play out a six-goal thriller at the Emirates Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Take a look back at this pulsating seven-goal thriller between Manchester United and Newcastle. Javier Hernandez was the hero as his stoppage time goal sealed victory for United.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 2013/14 Premier League classic between Everton and Liverpool at Goodison Park. This pulsating Merseyside derby is regarded as one of the finest in living memory.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611173000 +0000" stop="20250611183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the IFSC Climbing World Cup in Prague, Czech Republic, featuring the Men's and Women's Bouldering final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611183000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 2 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder face Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center. The Pacers edged the thrilling finals opener, stunning the Thunder with a 111-110 win.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as GWS Giants face Port Adelaide at Corroboree Group Manuka Oval. Can the Giants make it three wins on the spin?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611213000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as North Melbourne take on West Coast Eagles at Hands Oval. Who will triumph in this meeting between two struggling sides?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Carlton and Essendon face-off at the MCG. The Blues will be looking to find some form after losing three of their last four matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610073000 +0000" stop="20250610083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610083000 +0000" stop="20250610093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610093000 +0000" stop="20250610103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610103000 +0000" stop="20250610113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610113000 +0000" stop="20250610123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610123000 +0000" stop="20250610133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610133000 +0000" stop="20250610143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610143000 +0000" stop="20250610153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610153000 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610173000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610183000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's International Friendly Football</title>
    <desc>From BMO Field in Toronto.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Canadian Shield Soccer Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage for Canadian Shield soccer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611003000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's International Soccer Friendlies</title>
    <desc>From BMO Field in Toronto.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611073000 +0000" stop="20250611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611083000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611103000 +0000" stop="20250611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611113000 +0000" stop="20250611123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611123000 +0000" stop="20250611133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611133000 +0000" stop="20250611143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611143000 +0000" stop="20250611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611153000 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611173000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pokerstars Big Game on Tour</title>
    <desc>Professional players and poker-loving celebrities are joined by players who won seats at the table through auditions and free qualifiers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611210000 +0000" stop="20250611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611213000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 FIFA World Cup: 1 Year to Go Special</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From Fenway Park in Boston.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610023000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610033000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 for 30</title>
    <desc>On June 15, 2011, Vancouver hosts Game 7 of the Stanley Cup Finals between the Canucks and Boston Bruins; when Boston stuns the home team to win the Cup, the situation quickly devolves.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610053000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610063000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610073000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610083000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610093000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610103000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610113000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610123000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610133000 +0000" stop="20250610140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610140000 +0000" stop="20250610143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610143000 +0000" stop="20250610150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610150000 +0000" stop="20250610153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610153000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Pat McAfee Show</title>
    <desc>Former NFL punter Pat McAfee brings his humor and candor to the microphone to highlight the day's top stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610183000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610193000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250610233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250610233000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>WNBA news, analysis, highlights and interviews.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Barclays Center in Brooklyn, N.Y.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611020000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611033000 +0000" stop="20250611063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611063000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611073000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611083000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610140000 +0000" stop="20250610150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610150000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610163000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610173000 +0000" stop="20250610183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610183000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610213000 +0000" stop="20250610220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250610220000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Northern Super League Soccer</title>
    <desc>From Wanderers Grounds in Halifax, Nova Scotia.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Canadian Shield Soccer Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage for Canadian Shield soccer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611003000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Men's International Soccer Friendlies</title>
    <desc>From BMO Field in Toronto.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611110000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611140000 +0000" stop="20250611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611150000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA Tour Highlight Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring round recaps and highlights from tournament events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611210000 +0000" stop="20250611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611213000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Formula 1 Racing</title>
    <desc>Classic Formula 1 racing action.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610000000 +0000" stop="20250610010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610010000 +0000" stop="20250610020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ICC World Test Championship 2025 Final - The Expert's View</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610040000 +0000" stop="20250610050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610050000 +0000" stop="20250610060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610060000 +0000" stop="20250610070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610070000 +0000" stop="20250610080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610080000 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610140000 +0000" stop="20250610150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the second Women's ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610150000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out of the Shadows: The Story of South Africa's Test Cricket</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610171000 +0000" stop="20250610172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610172000 +0000" stop="20250610203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>3rd T20I.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610203000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610212000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610212000 +0000" stop="20250610220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610220000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ICC World Test Championship 2025 Final - The Expert's View</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611010000 +0000" stop="20250611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611020000 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out of the Shadows: The Story of South Africa's Test Cricket</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out of the Shadows: The Story of South Africa's Test Cricket</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611121000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Final, Day 1.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611121000 +0000" stop="20250611143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Final, Day 1.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611143000 +0000" stop="20250611163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Final, Day 1.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611163000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611172000 +0000" stop="20250611173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611173000 +0000" stop="20250611174000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611174000 +0000" stop="20250611205000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611205000 +0000" stop="20250611212000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611212000 +0000" stop="20250611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611213000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
