<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An Alzheimer's patient claims she was raped, but her illness casts doubt on the case; Fin's sergeant orders come in.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the sexual assault of a 15-year-old boy, but when he won't cooperate, they must find another way to uncover his perpetrator; Rollins reconnects with her ex, and Benson worries she isn't the Wonder Woman she used to be.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the sexual assault of a 15-year-old boy, but when he won't cooperate, they must find another way to uncover his perpetrator; Rollins reconnects with her ex; Benson worries she isn't the Wonder Woman she used to be.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and Asta work together to try and get something Harry desperately needs.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the assault, murder and mutilation of a member of a women's empowerment group; Fin and Carisi wonder who the father of Rollins' baby is.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU must unravel the mystery of a sexually assaulted young homeless woman who has a dual personality; when she goes missing after being assaulted, the team is challenged to uncover not only her identity but also her whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A columnist who has been given access to the squad for a story declares a hate crime case a hoax, leaving the victim under media scrutiny and Benson fighting to get the case back on solid ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When the mysterious death of a 23-year-old mother in New Mexico goes unsolved, her family searches for answers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A pair of double homicides in Nebraska, five years apart, lead police to fear a serial killer may be on the loose.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A pair of double homicides in Nebraska, five years apart, leads police to fear a serial killer may be on the loose.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team gets a new lead in the mole investigation after an unknown assailant kills two men disguised as sheriff's deputies in front of Callen's home; Nell interviews a prison inmate who has information on the department's leak.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>NCIS looks into the disappearance of a Navy lieutenant commander who is working on foreign cyber threats with the NSA; the team celebrates the holidays.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>After a Navy reservist is killed protecting a city councilman, Sam goes under cover in a private security firm that has links to criminal organizations.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a female video game developer who has been receiving death threats refuses to delay the launch of her new game, the cops must work to protect her.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While working under cover to bust a sex trafficking ring, Carisi meets a woman who embedded herself in the organization in hope of finding and saving her daughter; Sgt. Benson is faced with a life-changing revelation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Barba's efforts to make an arrest in a case involving pornographic photos is stalled when several suspects come down with the measles; Amaro receives distressing news about his son.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Efforts to find an 8-year-old boy kidnapped for ransom are hindered by tension between the child's estranged parents; Sgt. Benson is asked to take the lieutenant's exam and officially become the leader of the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617170000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Johnny D (Charles Halford) is on trial for sex trafficking, rape, assault and kidnapping, Noah's adoption becomes involved with the case, causing Benson to fear for the child's future; a threat could permanently change the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 15-year-old who was part of a group of kids who put a transgender teen in the hospital is tried as an adult, the SVU team wonders whether the punishment fits the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An unarmed black man is shot during the pursuit of a suspect, raising racial tensions; Barba must indict the three officers involved -- who claim they followed procedure.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates when a father and his two young children are stabbed to death in their home; when the motives of the culprit are uncovered, Benson finds herself having mixed feelings about the nature of the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a waitress at a popular restaurant is sexually assaulted, SVU looks for the culprit at the top of the culinary food chain, but Benson and Stone hit a wall when it's time to prosecute.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stone asks Benson to investigate a sexual encounter from his past that he feels guilt and uncertainty about; Rollins considers a proposal from Doctor Al.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The murder of an elusive, shy teenage author living a double life leads Benson and the rest of the SVU on an investigation that uncovers a situation beyond their wildest imaginations.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU investigates a he-said, she-said case when a woman crashes a wedding to accuse her therapist of sexual assault.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the team work to uncover a pregnant teenager's secret when she refuses to name the baby's father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the SVU team help a teenage exchange student from Italy after she's assaulted by a cab driver.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU searches for two suspects that were spotted fleeing the scene after a Muslim woman was assaulted inside a synagogue; Benson is dismayed to find that Rob Miller is out on bail.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618040000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenager is found dead in the Hudson River, Lt. Benson suspects Rob Miller is behind the mysterious death but can't prove it; despite having only circumstantial evidence, ADA Stone takes the case to court before Miller can destroy more lives.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A serial predator targeting men in gay bars proves difficult to catch, until a celebrity comes forward with his story.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While working under cover to bust a sex trafficking ring, Carisi meets a woman who embedded herself in the organization in hope of finding and saving her daughter; Sgt. Benson is faced with a life-changing revelation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Efforts to find an 8-year-old boy kidnapped for ransom are hindered by tension between the child's estranged parents; Sgt. Benson is asked to take the lieutenant's exam and officially become the leader of the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Johnny D (Charles Halford) is on trial for sex trafficking, rape, assault and kidnapping, Noah's adoption becomes involved with the case, causing Benson to fear for the child's future; a threat could permanently change the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 15-year-old who was part of a group of kids who put a transgender teen in the hospital is tried as an adult, the SVU team wonders whether the punishment fits the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>With the FBI closing in on the Roy Walton investigation, Voight and Halstead strategize a way out; after a city bus driver is shot by a passenger, the team investigates a possible abduction.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a missing child in what turns out to be a very complicated case; Burgess and Ruzek are in for a shock when someone from Makayla's past comes forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight employs his new informant to help solve a tricky drug trafficking case; Atwater, who once again struggles to reconcile his personal and professional life, reaches a decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team works together to identify the head of the brutal Los Temidos gang; Voight dives deeper into his informant Anna Avalos' past when her undercover role is threatened.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>While out for a jog, Upton witnesses a horrible car crash and risks her own life to save the passengers; after learning more about the victims, the team must track down the man responsible for the brutal crash.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a brutal killer with a signature modus operandi; Burgess and Ruzek double down in their fight to retain custody of Makayla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a young man is shot outside the Cárabo Bakery, the team works to connect the shooting to bakery owner Javier Escano, who has been under surveillance; despite the increasing danger, Voight helps informant Anna Avalos get closer to their target.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Chief Hawkins goes above and beyond to help Brett and Violet with a problem; Kidd pursues an open lieutenant position; a blast from the past asks Mouch and Herrmann for a favor.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Following an injury in the aftermath of an industrial fire, Severide and Seager work together to investigate an anonymous tip; Kidd searches for the right person to fill the open spot on Truck 81; a possible new recruit to 51 gets tested at a call.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz forms a bond with a young immigrant boy he meets while fighting an apartment fire; Squad makes plans to prank the newest member of their team; Hawkins and Violet struggle to keep their relationship a secret.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Kidd work with CPD regarding a suspicious car wreck; Hawkins and Violet's relationship is in jeopardy; Chloe and Cruz adjust to a new family dynamic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together when one of its own is taken hostage.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beast</title>
    <desc>A father and his two teenage daughters find themselves hunted by a massive rogue lion intent on proving that the Savanna has but one apex predator.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther</title>
    <desc>Black Panther's mettle as king gets tested when an old enemy draws him into a conflict that puts his nation and the world at risk. The king must soon rally his allies and release his full power to defeat his foes and secure the safety of his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617003000 +0000" stop="20250617033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617033000 +0000" stop="20250617041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">International T20 Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from the third T20 between Ireland and West Indies at Bready Cricket Ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617041500 +0000" stop="20250617123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day one of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617123000 +0000" stop="20250617124500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We revisit the second T20 between Ireland and West Indies at Bready Cricket Ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617124500 +0000" stop="20250617153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617153000 +0000" stop="20250617154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617154500 +0000" stop="20250617171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>A film charting Tom Daley's career from his first Olympics in Beijing at 14 years old, through winning gold at Tokyo 2020 and his final Olympic appearance at Paris 2024.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617171500 +0000" stop="20250617173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617173000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the greatest goalscorers in Premier League history; the icons whose instinct, power, and flair have lit up stadiums and etched their names into footballing folklore. From Alan Shearer's relentless consistency to Thierry Henry's elegance, Sergio Agüero's killer instinct to Harry Kane's rise, we relive the moments that defined an era.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day one of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the FIA World Endurance Championship and the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Poland, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617223000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SailGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from SailGP in New York, as 12 F50s battled for glory against the backdrop of one of the most famous cityscapes in the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Poland, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Bath Rugby face Leicester Tigers in a titanic clash at Twickenham as both sides battle for Gallagher Premiership glory in a thrilling season finale.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We look back at the second One Day International between West Indies Women and South Africa Women.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618024500 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We revisit the second T20 between Ireland and West Indies at Bready Cricket Ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>Relive the third T20 between Ireland and West Indies at Bready Cricket Ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618031500 +0000" stop="20250618041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day one of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618041500 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day two of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618124500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618124500 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Cycling</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the 2025 Tour of Flanders, as Tadej Pogacar rode to victory in this historic one-day road race held in Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618154500 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies face-up against South Africa in the third Women's One Day International.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day two of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as Seattle Mariners and Boston Red Sox go head-to-head.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618231500 +0000" stop="20250618234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618234500 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617024500 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB classic action from the All-Star Highlights 1973 from the Royals Stadium in Kansas City.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Bath Rugby face Leicester Tigers in a titanic clash at Twickenham as both sides battle for Gallagher Premiership glory in a thrilling season finale.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617043000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crouchy and Cole</title>
    <desc>Peter Crouch and Joe Cole have been going head-to-head this year, trying their hand at various sports. This is the best of.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Cup Road Cycling</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from the 2025 Elfstedenronde Brugge, a one-day road race held in Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Bath Rugby face Leicester Tigers in a titanic clash at Twickenham as both sides battle for Gallagher Premiership glory in a thrilling season finale.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617123000 +0000" stop="20250617133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617133000 +0000" stop="20250617134500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We look back at the second One Day International between West Indies Women and South Africa Women.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617134500 +0000" stop="20250617223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Women's One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies face-up against South Africa in the third Women's One Day International.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617223000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day one of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250617234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250617234500 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>In Copsa Mica, the pollution created by industrial activity has impacted the health of the local team and forced them to transplant a football pitch from a nearby village.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Lead Off</title>
    <desc>A look at the upcoming MLB action.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618051500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Los Angeles Dodgers host San Diego Padres.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618051500 +0000" stop="20250618054500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the MLB.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618054500 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Pioneers</title>
    <desc>Eden Hazard set the Premier League alight with his dribbling skills and incredible creativity. We trace the story of how the Belgian attacker became a Chelsea hero.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the greatest goalscorers in Premier League history; the icons whose instinct, power, and flair have lit up stadiums and etched their names into footballing folklore. From Alan Shearer's relentless consistency to Thierry Henry's elegance, Sergio Agüero's killer instinct to Harry Kane's rise, we relive the moments that defined an era.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Six months after their title-deciding 1-0 mugging at St James's Park, Keegan's Newcastle, now armed with Shearer, are in the mood for revenge.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Action from the '97/98 Premier League season as a late winner from Platt puts Arsenal second.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 1998/99 thriller between leaders Aston Villa and Liverpool at Villa Park. Gerard Houllier was chasing his first victory since taking charge of the team on his own.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit this classic from 1999/00 as Manchester United faced Chelsea at Old Trafford, which featured four goals in the first half.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Goals galore as we revisit this classic from 2000/01 as Manchester United faced Chelsea at Old Trafford. Claudio Ranieri's first match as Chelsea manager was a thriller.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We delve into the Premier League archive to bring you a Classic Match from the 2001/2002 season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Manchester Derby game. Will the underdogs win out? Classic Premier League from the '02/03 season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit an eight-goal epic at Old Trafford between Manchester United and Newcastle United from the 2002/03 campaign.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Is this the best ever Arsenal team? Judge for yourself as Wenger's undefeated `Invincibles' look to maintain their impressive form against Liverpool.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618143000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the FIA World Endurance Championship and the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618174500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618174500 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Fara Williams, England Women's most-capped player, joins Rolf and Damaris to look back at the Premier League, Champions League and Women's Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>In Copsa Mica, the pollution created by industrial activity has impacted the health of the local team and forced them to transplant a football pitch from a nearby village.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618223000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crouchy and Cole</title>
    <desc>Peter Crouch and Joe Cole have been going head-to-head this year, trying their hand at various sports. This is the best of.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617013000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group C.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617073000 +0000" stop="20250617083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617083000 +0000" stop="20250617093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617093000 +0000" stop="20250617173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Terra Wortmann Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From OWL Arena in Halle, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Germany.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617173000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The most outrageous moments in NASCAR history.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617183000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617213000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Terra Wortmann Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From OWL Arena in Halle, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Germany.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617013000 +0000" stop="20250617023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617023000 +0000" stop="20250617033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617033000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617183000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage of the 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pokerstars Big Game on Tour</title>
    <desc>Professional players and poker-loving celebrities are joined by players who won seats at the table through auditions and free qualifiers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618233000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Men's and Women's Bouldering finals in Bern, Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Women's Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Women's Champions League final as Arsenal face Barcelona at Estadio Jose Alvalade in Lisbon, Portugal.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617033000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Champions League final between Luis Enrique's Paris Saint-Germain and Simone Inzaghi's Inter at Allianz Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Europa League final between Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United at San Mames Stadium in Bilbao.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617043000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Conference League final between Manuel Pellegrini's Real Betis and Enzo Maresca's Chelsea at Stadion Wroclaw.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as North Melbourne take on Fremantle at Optus Stadium. Both teams have had inconsistency in their recent games. Can be anyone's game.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617063000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Port Adelaide face Melbourne at Adelaide Oval. Whilst Port Adelaide has has a mixed run lately, will Melbourne secure a victory?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as West Coast Eagles take on Carlton at Optus Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617093000 +0000" stop="20250617103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617103000 +0000" stop="20250617113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617113000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Action from the Women's National Basketball Association as Los Angeles Sparks face Minnesota Lynx. A dominant home form powered by Napheesa Collier and Kayla McBride.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League and Conference League Magazine</title>
    <desc>A review of the 2024/25 UEFA Europa League season, as Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United enjoyed a welcome distraction from their domestic woes.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617170000 +0000" stop="20250617174500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Fara Williams, England Women's most-capped player, joins Rolf and Damaris to look back at the Premier League, Champions League and Women's Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617174500 +0000" stop="20250617191500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617191500 +0000" stop="20250617204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Bath Rugby face Leicester Tigers in a titanic clash at Twickenham as both sides battle for Gallagher Premiership glory in a thrilling season finale.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617204500 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>Featuring never-before-seen footage, Jonah Lomu shares his story and how he escaped gang violence to become one of the planet's most iconic rugby player.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC Fight Night at State Farm Arena in Atlanta, Georgia, featuring the welterweight showdown between former champion Kamaru Usman and Joaquin Buckley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618040000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618154500 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Goals Reload</title>
    <desc>The pick of the goals from the 2024/25 UEFA Champions League quarter-finals, semi-finals and final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 3 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC Fight Night at State Farm Arena in Atlanta, Georgia, featuring the welterweight showdown between former champion Kamaru Usman and Joaquin Buckley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 3 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Bayern Munich take on Benfica at Allianz Arena. Vincent Kompany's Bayern have lost their last two matches in this competiton.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617053000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Slovan Bratislava face AC Milan at Tehelne pole.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Bayern Munich face Paris Saint-Germain at Allianz Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617063000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Sporting CP meet Arsenal at Estadio Jose Alvalade.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Arne Slot's Liverpool take on Carlo Ancelotti's Real Madrid at Anfield. Can the Reds make it five wins out of five in this competition?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617073000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as PSV Eindhoven face Shakhtar Donetsk at Philips Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Monaco and Benfica face-off at Stade Louis II.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617083000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Aston Villa host Thiago Motta's Juventus at Villa Park. Juventus have won just one of their last seven away matches in this competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Atalanta and Real Madrid face-off at Gewiss Stadium. Can Madrid turn around their UCL form against Gian Piero Gasperini's unbeaten side?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617093000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Borussia Dortmund and Barcelona face-off at Signal Iduna Park. Barca are looking to secure their fifth win in a row in the UCL.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Juventus host Manchester City at Allianz Stadium. Pep Guardiola's City side have conceded seven goals in their last two UCL games.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617103000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Arsenal face Adi Hutter's Monaco at Emirates Stadium. Monaco have won five of their last seven matches against English sides in the UCL.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Brian Priske's Feyenoord meet Sparta Prague at De Kuip. Feyenoord are winless in their four games against Sparta Prague.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617113000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action between Atletico Madrid and Bayer Leverkusen at Riyadh Air Metropolitano. A win for Atletico would see them leapfrog Leverkusen in the table.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League and Conference League Magazine</title>
    <desc>A review of the 2024/25 UEFA Europa League season, as Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United enjoyed a welcome distraction from their domestic woes.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global Champions Tour</title>
    <desc>Longines Global Champions Tour action from the Grand Prix of St Tropez.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Men's and Women's Bouldering finals in Bern, Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as North Melbourne take on Fremantle at Optus Stadium. Both teams have had inconsistency in their recent games. Can be anyone's game.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617163000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Port Adelaide face Melbourne at Adelaide Oval. Whilst Port Adelaide has has a mixed run lately, will Melbourne secure a victory?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as West Coast Eagles take on Carlton at Optus Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617193000 +0000" stop="20250617203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Men's and Women's Bouldering finals in Bern, Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617203000 +0000" stop="20250617213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action and stories from Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617213000 +0000" stop="20250617223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the Roland-Garros Mixed Doubles, as Americans Taylor Townsend and Evan King take on Italian pair Sara Errani and Andrea Vavassori.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617223000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Joe Salisbury and Neal Skupski look to become Britain's first Men's Doubles champions at Roland-Garros since 1933, as they take on Marcel Granollers and Horacio Zeballos.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Roland-Garros Women's Doubles final, as Italian pair Jasmine Paolini and Sara Errani take on Aleksandra Krunic and Anna Danilina.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Yui Kamiji seeks her fifth Roland-Garros Women's Wheelchair Singles title as she takes on Dutch second seed Aniek van Koot.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Men's Singles final at Roland-Garros as world number one Jannik Sinner must overcome defending champion Carlos Alcaraz to claim a maiden title win in Paris.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618033000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the 2025 Roland-Garros Women's Singles as the top two seeds, Belarusian Aryna Sabalenka and American Coco Gauff, vie for glory on Court Philippe-Chatrier.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Manchester City fight for their place in the UEFA Champions League as they face Club Brugge at Etihad Stadium. Only a win will be enough for City to qualify for the play-off round.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League clash between Stuttgart and Paris Saint-Germain at MHPArena. Stuttgart need a point to secure their spot in the play-off round.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Inter and Monaco face-off at San Siro. Can Adi Hutter's Monaco side cause an upset and break into the top eight?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Barcelona take on Atalanta at Estadi Olimpic Lluis Companys. Aston Villa will be hoping top-eight rivals Atalanta slip up in this pivotal game.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Juventus face Benfica at Allianz Stadium. Juve have lost six of their eight previous meetings with Benfica in European competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Lille meet Dutch side Feyenoord at Stade Pierre-Mauroy. Both sides are still in the hunt for a top-eight finish.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the crucial UEFA Champions League clash between Aston Villa and Celtic at Villa Park. A win for Unai Emery's Villans could see them secure a top-eight finish.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Spanish side Girona welcome Arsenal to Estadi Montilivi. Mikel Arteta's Gunners are looking to make it six wins out of eight in the UCL.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Benfica host Barcelona at Estadio de Luz. Can Bruno Lage's Benfica halt Hansi Flick's free-scoring Barca side?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as winless Bologna face Nuri Sahin's top-eight contenders Borussia Dortmund at Stadio Renato Dall'Ara.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Red Star take on PSV Eindhoven at Rajko Mitic Stadium. Red Star are on the longest current run of UCL games without a clean sheet.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Paris Saint-Germain face Manchester City in a crucial showdown at Parc des Princes. Defeat for City could see them slip out of the play-off places.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Feyenoord face Bayern Munich at De Kuip. Bayern are unbeaten in their last eight UCL games against Dutch opponents.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618113000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Dutch champions PSV Eindhoven face Liverpool at Philips Stadion. Arne Slot's Reds are guaranteed to finish top of the table if they avoid defeat.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the greatest goalscorers in Premier League history; the icons whose instinct, power, and flair have lit up stadiums and etched their names into footballing folklore. From Alan Shearer's relentless consistency to Thierry Henry's elegance, Sergio Agüero's killer instinct to Harry Kane's rise, we relive the moments that defined an era.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crouchy and Cole</title>
    <desc>Peter Crouch and Joe Cole have been going head-to-head this year, trying their hand at various sports. This is the best of.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618144500 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as St Kilda take on Western Bulldogs at Marvel Stadium. With both teams having lost 3 games in the last 5, it will be a tight match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Hawthorn face Adelaide Crows at UTAS Stadium. In their last game Hawthorn break a losing streak, while Adelaide secures a win against Brisbane.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Brisbane Lions go head-to-head with GWS Giants at The Gabba. This highly anticipated match is part of Round 14 of the AFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Essendon face Geelong Cats at Marvel Stadium. With Geelong Cats on form, will Essendon keep possession and ensure precise ball movement for a win?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617013000 +0000" stop="20250617023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617023000 +0000" stop="20250617033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617033000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617073000 +0000" stop="20250617083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617083000 +0000" stop="20250617093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617093000 +0000" stop="20250617103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617103000 +0000" stop="20250617113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617113000 +0000" stop="20250617123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617123000 +0000" stop="20250617133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617133000 +0000" stop="20250617143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617143000 +0000" stop="20250617153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617153000 +0000" stop="20250617163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617163000 +0000" stop="20250617173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617173000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 for 30</title>
    <desc>Filmmaker Brett Morgen chronicles events: Arnold Palmer plays his last round at a U.S. Open, the FIFA World Cup kicks off in Chicago, the Rangers celebrate on Broadway, O.J. Simpson leads America on a slow speed chase in a white Ford Bronco.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617213000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage of the 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618113000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618143000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pokerstars Big Game on Tour</title>
    <desc>Professional players and poker-loving celebrities are joined by players who won seats at the table through auditions and free qualifiers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618233000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Formula 1 Racing</title>
    <desc>McLaren aim to keep up their dominant Formula One form for the Canadian Grand Prix. Oscar Piastri and Lando Norris finished one-two in Spain. Max Verstappen moved within a single penalty point of a one-race ban for crashing into George Russell.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The most outrageous moments in NASCAR history.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617023000 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617033000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">26.2 to Life</title>
    <desc>Inmates inside California's oldest state prison train for and run a marathon. The transformative power of San Quentin's 1,000 Mile Club touches the incarcerated men.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617063000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617073000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617083000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617093000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617103000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617113000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617123000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617133000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617143000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617153000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Pat McAfee Show</title>
    <desc>Former NFL punter Pat McAfee brings his humor and candor to the microphone to highlight the day's top stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>Top plays from the 2024-25 NFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617183000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617193000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617203000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617213000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 for 30</title>
    <desc>Filmmaker Brett Morgen chronicles events: Arnold Palmer plays his last round at a U.S. Open, the FIFA World Cup kicks off in Chicago, the Rangers celebrate on Broadway, O.J. Simpson leads America on a slow speed chase in a white Ford Bronco.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Grizzlie Truth</title>
    <desc>Superfan filmmaker Kat Jayme investigates the abrupt move of her NBA hometown team, the Vancouver Grizzlies, to Memphis in 2001. Much more than a sore spot, it's an unsolved mystery and possibly a criminal conspiracy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618113000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618143000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Pat McAfee Show</title>
    <desc>Former NFL punter Pat McAfee brings his humor and candor to the microphone to highlight the day's top stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618193000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617013000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group C.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617163000 +0000" stop="20250617170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617170000 +0000" stop="20250617173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617173000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 for 30</title>
    <desc>Filmmaker Brett Morgen chronicles events: Arnold Palmer plays his last round at a U.S. Open, the FIFA World Cup kicks off in Chicago, the Rangers celebrate on Broadway, O.J. Simpson leads America on a slow speed chase in a white Ford Bronco.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617213000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618033000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617003000 +0000" stop="20250617005000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617005000 +0000" stop="20250617010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617041000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum in Oakland, Calif.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617041000 +0000" stop="20250617044000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617044000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617133000 +0000" stop="20250617135000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617135000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Women's T20 Blast Cricket</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the professional women's Twenty20 cricket league in England and Wales.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617171000 +0000" stop="20250617174000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617174000 +0000" stop="20250617175000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617175000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617211000 +0000" stop="20250617214000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617214000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618005000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618005000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618041000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum in Oakland, Calif.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618041000 +0000" stop="20250618044000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618044000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the second Women's ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618172000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618204000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618204000 +0000" stop="20250618211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618211000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
