<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
<channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU investigates a he-said, she-said case when a woman crashes a wedding to accuse her therapist of sexual assault.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the team work to uncover a pregnant teenager's secret when she refuses to name the baby's father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the SVU team help a teenage exchange student from Italy after she's assaulted by a cab driver.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU searches for two suspects that were spotted fleeing the scene after a Muslim woman was assaulted inside a synagogue; Benson is dismayed to find that Rob Miller is out on bail.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618040000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenager is found dead in the Hudson River, Lt. Benson suspects Rob Miller is behind the mysterious death but can't prove it; despite having only circumstantial evidence, ADA Stone takes the case to court before Miller can destroy more lives.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A serial predator targeting men in gay bars proves difficult to catch, until a celebrity comes forward with his story.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While working under cover to bust a sex trafficking ring, Carisi meets a woman who embedded herself in the organization in hope of finding and saving her daughter; Sgt. Benson is faced with a life-changing revelation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Efforts to find an 8-year-old boy kidnapped for ransom are hindered by tension between the child's estranged parents; Sgt. Benson is asked to take the lieutenant's exam and officially become the leader of the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Johnny D (Charles Halford) is on trial for sex trafficking, rape, assault and kidnapping, Noah's adoption becomes involved with the case, causing Benson to fear for the child's future; a threat could permanently change the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 15-year-old who was part of a group of kids who put a transgender teen in the hospital is tried as an adult, the SVU team wonders whether the punishment fits the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>With the FBI closing in on the Roy Walton investigation, Voight and Halstead strategize a way out; after a city bus driver is shot by a passenger, the team investigates a possible abduction.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a missing child in what turns out to be a very complicated case; Burgess and Ruzek are in for a shock when someone from Makayla's past comes forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight employs his new informant to help solve a tricky drug trafficking case; Atwater, who once again struggles to reconcile his personal and professional life, reaches a decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team works together to identify the head of the brutal Los Temidos gang; Voight dives deeper into his informant Anna Avalos' past when her undercover role is threatened.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>While out for a jog, Upton witnesses a horrible car crash and risks her own life to save the passengers; after learning more about the victims, the team must track down the man responsible for the brutal crash.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a brutal killer with a signature modus operandi; Burgess and Ruzek double down in their fight to retain custody of Makayla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a young man is shot outside the Cárabo Bakery, the team works to connect the shooting to bakery owner Javier Escano, who has been under surveillance; despite the increasing danger, Voight helps informant Anna Avalos get closer to their target.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Chief Hawkins goes above and beyond to help Brett and Violet with a problem; Kidd pursues an open lieutenant position; a blast from the past asks Mouch and Herrmann for a favor.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Following an injury in the aftermath of an industrial fire, Severide and Seager work together to investigate an anonymous tip; Kidd searches for the right person to fill the open spot on Truck 81; a possible new recruit to 51 gets tested at a call.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz forms a bond with a young immigrant boy he meets while fighting an apartment fire; Squad makes plans to prank the newest member of their team; Hawkins and Violet struggle to keep their relationship a secret.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Kidd work with CPD regarding a suspicious car wreck; Hawkins and Violet's relationship is in jeopardy; Chloe and Cruz adjust to a new family dynamic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together when one of its own is taken hostage.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beast</title>
    <desc>A father and his two teenage daughters find themselves hunted by a massive rogue lion intent on proving that the Savanna has but one apex predator.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250619030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther</title>
    <desc>Black Panther's mettle as king gets tested when an old enemy draws him into a conflict that puts his nation and the world at risk. The king must soon rally his allies and release his full power to defeat his foes and secure the safety of his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619030000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beast</title>
    <desc>A father and his two teenage daughters find themselves hunted by a massive rogue lion intent on proving that the Savanna has but one apex predator.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The media spotlight shines on Sgt. Benson when she investigates a string of rapes that have similarities with crimes in Atlanta; a family court judge threatens to remove baby Noah from Benson's care.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a female video game developer who has been receiving death threats refuses to delay the launch of her new game, the cops must work to protect her.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Barba's efforts to make an arrest in a case involving pornographic photos is stalled when several suspects come down with the measles; Amaro receives distressing news about his son.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An unarmed black man is shot during the pursuit of a suspect, raising racial tensions; Barba must indict the three officers involved -- who claim they followed procedure.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU must unravel the mystery of a sexually assaulted young homeless woman who has a dual personality; when she goes missing after being assaulted, the team is challenged to uncover not only her identity but also her whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Callen, Sam, Granger and Deeks get arrested as the result of planted evidence on the day Under Secretary Duggan arrives for Hetty's resignation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When Hetty goes rogue, she leaves the NCIS team completely in the dark; the mole kidnaps one of the agents.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>An NCIS agent is held at an unknown location and tortured by the mole, and another agent discovers he was betrayed by someone he least expected.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a woman claims that the baby she kidnapped is hers with a respected legal expert, the investigation changes the lives of two families.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619140000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The media spotlight shines on Sgt. Benson when she investigates a string of rapes that have similarities with crimes in Atlanta; a family court judge threatens to remove baby Noah from Benson's care.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teenager is sexually assaulted and left for dead in an alley after attending a movie star's party; Benson is suspicious when security footage from the party goes missing.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman wants to recant her testimony and free her father, who was incarcerated for incest and rape when she was a child; Capt. Cragen, who remembers the original investigation, tries to help the team.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619170000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins' mother throws her a baby shower; the team's investigation into the rape of a violinist by her colleague leads to Rollins' fugitive sister; Sgt. Mike Dodds reports for his first day.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the 13-year-old daughter of a reality-TV family discovers she's pregnant, the team investigates.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Barba relies on old evidence, and faces off against a former colleague, during the trial of child abductor Lewis Hodda.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A high-school student plans a secret hookup with a female teacher, but ends up in a sinister situation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Sgt. Olivia Benson attempts to thwart a violent home invasion, she gets more than she bargains for and becomes a hostage.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Erin Lindsay and Antonio Dawson from Chicago P.D. help SVU when two convicted murderers escape.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619230000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU begins investigating members of a top youth hockey team after a savage hazing takes place in a locker room.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Independence Day</title>
    <desc>When alien invaders lay waste to planet Earth, it's up to a select group of survivors to make a last-ditch stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400477">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Poland, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premiership Rugby</title>
    <desc>Bath Rugby face Leicester Tigers in a titanic clash at Twickenham as both sides battle for Gallagher Premiership glory in a thrilling season finale.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We look back at the second One Day International between West Indies Women and South Africa Women.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618024500 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We revisit the second T20 between Ireland and West Indies at Bready Cricket Ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>Relive the third T20 between Ireland and West Indies at Bready Cricket Ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618031500 +0000" stop="20250618041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day one of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618041500 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day two of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618124500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618124500 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Cycling</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the 2025 Tour of Flanders, as Tadej Pogacar rode to victory in this historic one-day road race held in Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618154500 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies face-up against South Africa in the third Women's One Day International.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day two of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as Seattle Mariners and Boston Red Sox go head-to-head.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618231500 +0000" stop="20250618234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250618234500 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250619010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619010000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Men's and Women's Bouldering finals in Bern, Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>What does the future hold for cricket in the battle against global warming? Reshmin Chowdhury meets people at all levels to discuss how cricket can be a positive force for change.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619021500 +0000" stop="20250619031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Women's One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies face-up against South Africa in the third Women's One Day International.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619031500 +0000" stop="20250619041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day two of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619041500 +0000" stop="20250619123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day three of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619123000 +0000" stop="20250619124500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619124500 +0000" stop="20250619153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage five of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland. Riders depart from La Punt and end the day with a steep final climb to Santa Maria.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619153000 +0000" stop="20250619154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619154500 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Cricket Reload</title>
    <desc>We look back at the first One Day International between Ireland and West Indies at Clontarf Cricket Club, featuring a classy century by Andrew Balbirnie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Action</title>
    <desc>Action is the watchword for this fast paced highlights programme, which rounds up the latest action from the NBA.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619163000 +0000" stop="20250619170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619170000 +0000" stop="20250619201500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>MLB action as New York Yankees take on Los Angeles Angels at Yankee Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619201500 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>TNT Sports commemorates the centenary of armistice with an inspiring film that tells the story of non-league side Corinthians-Casuals and their links to Brazilian giants Corinthians.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Conference League final between Manuel Pellegrini's Real Betis and Enzo Maresca's Chelsea at Stadion Wroclaw.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619223000 +0000" stop="20250619230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Action</title>
    <desc>Action is the watchword for this fast paced highlights programme, which rounds up the latest action from the NBA.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400477" start="20250619230000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center. The Indiana Pacers and Oklahoma City Thunder are tied 2-2 heading into a pivotal Game 5.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400480">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>In Copsa Mica, the pollution created by industrial activity has impacted the health of the local team and forced them to transplant a football pitch from a nearby village.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Lead Off</title>
    <desc>A look at the upcoming MLB action.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618051500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as Los Angeles Dodgers host San Diego Padres.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618051500 +0000" stop="20250618054500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Closer</title>
    <desc>A look back at the best action from the MLB.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618054500 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Pioneers</title>
    <desc>Eden Hazard set the Premier League alight with his dribbling skills and incredible creativity. We trace the story of how the Belgian attacker became a Chelsea hero.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the greatest goalscorers in Premier League history; the icons whose instinct, power, and flair have lit up stadiums and etched their names into footballing folklore. From Alan Shearer's relentless consistency to Thierry Henry's elegance, Sergio Agüero's killer instinct to Harry Kane's rise, we relive the moments that defined an era.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Six months after their title-deciding 1-0 mugging at St James's Park, Keegan's Newcastle, now armed with Shearer, are in the mood for revenge.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Action from the '97/98 Premier League season as a late winner from Platt puts Arsenal second.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit the 1998/99 thriller between leaders Aston Villa and Liverpool at Villa Park. Gerard Houllier was chasing his first victory since taking charge of the team on his own.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit this classic from 1999/00 as Manchester United faced Chelsea at Old Trafford, which featured four goals in the first half.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Goals galore as we revisit this classic from 2000/01 as Manchester United faced Chelsea at Old Trafford. Claudio Ranieri's first match as Chelsea manager was a thriller.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We delve into the Premier League archive to bring you a Classic Match from the 2001/2002 season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Manchester Derby game. Will the underdogs win out? Classic Premier League from the '02/03 season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit an eight-goal epic at Old Trafford between Manchester United and Newcastle United from the 2002/03 campaign.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Is this the best ever Arsenal team? Judge for yourself as Wenger's undefeated `Invincibles' look to maintain their impressive form against Liverpool.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MLB Plays of the Week</title>
    <desc>This weekly MLB highlights show showcases the most exciting plays from the past week's matches.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618143000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the FIA World Endurance Championship and the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618174500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Superbike Rewind</title>
    <desc>We revisit the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618174500 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Fara Williams, England Women's most-capped player, joins Rolf and Damaris to look back at the Premier League, Champions League and Women's Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Films</title>
    <desc>In Copsa Mica, the pollution created by industrial activity has impacted the health of the local team and forced them to transplant a football pitch from a nearby village.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618223000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crouchy and Cole</title>
    <desc>Peter Crouch and Joe Cole have been going head-to-head this year, trying their hand at various sports. This is the best of.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250619010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619010000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the FIA World Endurance Championship and the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA European Rally Championship</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Rally Poland, part of the 2025 European Rally Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619023000 +0000" stop="20250619033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619033000 +0000" stop="20250619043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619043000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">IFSC Climbing World Cup</title>
    <desc>IFSC Climbing World Cup highlights from the Men's and Women's Bouldering finals in Bern, Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>A review of the fourth race of the 2025 Golden Trail World Series, as the world's best trail runners took on the Zegama-Aizkorri mountain marathon in Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619093000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA TCR World Tour</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action from the 2025 TCR World Tour in Valencia, Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Fremantle and Essendon go head-to-head.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619131500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619131500 +0000" stop="20250619140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sign Up: Into Football</title>
    <desc>Fara Williams, England Women's most-capped player, joins Rolf and Damaris to look back at the Premier League, Champions League and Women's Champions League.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619140000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Women's One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies host South Africa in the first Women's One Day International. Will South Africa prove too strong for the West Indies in this series?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Women's One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies face-up against South Africa in the second Women's One Day International. Who will take the lead?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Women's One-Day International Cricket</title>
    <desc>Cricket action from Three Ws Oval as West Indies face-up against South Africa in the third Women's One Day International.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619170000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day three of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Fremantle and Essendon go head-to-head.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619193000 +0000" stop="20250619194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619194500 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">TNT Sports Reload</title>
    <desc>The best bits from TNT Sports over the last week, including exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Action from Major League Baseball as San Francisco Giants face Cleveland Guardians.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400480" start="20250619231500 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day three of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405060">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN3</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Terra Wortmann Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From OWL Arena in Halle, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Germany.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619010000 +0000" stop="20250619013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619013000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619040000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619073000 +0000" stop="20250619083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619083000 +0000" stop="20250619093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619093000 +0000" stop="20250619173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Terra Wortmann Open Tennis</title>
    <desc>From OWL Arena in Halle, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Germany.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619173000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619213000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>Bold opinions, discussion and debate centered on the top storylines from around the league. Mike Greenberg hosts this pregame show with analysts Stephen A. Smith and Michael Wilbon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405060" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>Bold opinions, discussion and debate centered on the top storylines from around the league. Mike Greenberg hosts this pregame show with analysts Stephen A. Smith and Michael Wilbon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405134">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN4</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage of the 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pokerstars Big Game on Tour</title>
    <desc>Professional players and poker-loving celebrities are joined by players who won seats at the table through auditions and free qualifiers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250618233000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619030000 +0000" stop="20250619040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619040000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619140000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">First Take</title>
    <desc>Stephen A. Smith joins Molly Qerim to debate the hottest topics in sports with contributors and guests.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inbound</title>
    <desc>Documenting the shared trajectory between Canada's rise as a global basketball powerhouse and the circumstances that helped shape the country's multicultural identity.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>Bold opinions, discussion and debate centered on the top storylines from around the league. Mike Greenberg hosts this pregame show with analysts Stephen A. Smith and Michael Wilbon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405134" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>Bold opinions, discussion and debate centered on the top storylines from around the league. Mike Greenberg hosts this pregame show with analysts Stephen A. Smith and Michael Wilbon.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400479">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618040000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australia Championship Supercars</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Perth Super 440, part of the 2025 Supercars Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage three of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618154500 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Goals Reload</title>
    <desc>The pick of the goals from the 2024/25 UEFA Champions League quarter-finals, semi-finals and final.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 3 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Fighting Championship</title>
    <desc>Action from UFC Fight Night at State Farm Arena in Atlanta, Georgia, featuring the welterweight showdown between former champion Kamaru Usman and Joaquin Buckley.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 3 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619003000 +0000" stop="20250619013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619013000 +0000" stop="20250619023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619023000 +0000" stop="20250619033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619033000 +0000" stop="20250619040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Conference League</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Conference League final between Manuel Pellegrini's Real Betis and Enzo Maresca's Chelsea at Stadion Wroclaw.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619040000 +0000" stop="20250619043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Europa League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Europa League final between Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United at San Mames Stadium in Bilbao.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619043000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the 2025 UEFA Champions League final between Luis Enrique's Paris Saint-Germain and Simone Inzaghi's Inter at Allianz Arena.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619073000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ultimate Pool Pairs Cup</title>
    <desc>Ultimate Pool action from Group 3 of the Pairs Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the FIA World Endurance Championship and the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Baseball</title>
    <desc>Highlights from Major League Baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA TCR World Tour</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action from the 2025 TCR World Tour in Valencia, Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619133000 +0000" stop="20250619154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619154500 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Cycling</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the 2025 Tour of Flanders, as Tadej Pogacar rode to victory in this historic one-day road race held in Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Game 5 of the NBA Finals as Oklahoma City Thunder take on Indiana Pacers at Paycom Center. The Indiana Pacers and Oklahoma City Thunder are tied 2-2 heading into a pivotal Game 5.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619173000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">T100 Triathlon World Tour</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the T100 Triathlon World Tour in Vancouver, Canada.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage five of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland. Riders depart from La Punt and end the day with a steep final climb to Santa Maria.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovery Golf</title>
    <desc>A weekly show featuring the latest news from the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619223000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA World Endurance Championship Motor Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the FIA World Endurance Championship and the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400479" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA TCR World Tour</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action from the 2025 TCR World Tour in Valencia, Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="400478">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">TNT Sports 4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Yui Kamiji seeks her fifth Roland-Garros Women's Wheelchair Singles title as she takes on Dutch second seed Aniek van Koot.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the Men's Singles final at Roland-Garros as world number one Jannik Sinner must overcome defending champion Carlos Alcaraz to claim a maiden title win in Paris.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618033000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland Garros 2025</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the 2025 Roland-Garros Women's Singles as the top two seeds, Belarusian Aryna Sabalenka and American Coco Gauff, vie for glory on Court Philippe-Chatrier.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Manchester City fight for their place in the UEFA Champions League as they face Club Brugge at Etihad Stadium. Only a win will be enough for City to qualify for the play-off round.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League clash between Stuttgart and Paris Saint-Germain at MHPArena. Stuttgart need a point to secure their spot in the play-off round.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Inter and Monaco face-off at San Siro. Can Adi Hutter's Monaco side cause an upset and break into the top eight?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Barcelona take on Atalanta at Estadi Olimpic Lluis Companys. Aston Villa will be hoping top-eight rivals Atalanta slip up in this pivotal game.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Juventus face Benfica at Allianz Stadium. Juve have lost six of their eight previous meetings with Benfica in European competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Lille meet Dutch side Feyenoord at Stade Pierre-Mauroy. Both sides are still in the hunt for a top-eight finish.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the crucial UEFA Champions League clash between Aston Villa and Celtic at Villa Park. A win for Unai Emery's Villans could see them secure a top-eight finish.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Spanish side Girona welcome Arsenal to Estadi Montilivi. Mikel Arteta's Gunners are looking to make it six wins out of eight in the UCL.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Benfica host Barcelona at Estadio de Luz. Can Bruno Lage's Benfica halt Hansi Flick's free-scoring Barca side?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as winless Bologna face Nuri Sahin's top-eight contenders Borussia Dortmund at Stadio Renato Dall'Ara.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Red Star take on PSV Eindhoven at Rajko Mitic Stadium. Red Star are on the longest current run of UCL games without a clean sheet.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Paris Saint-Germain face Manchester City in a crucial showdown at Parc des Princes. Defeat for City could see them slip out of the play-off places.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>Action from the UEFA Champions League as Feyenoord face Bayern Munich at De Kuip. Bayern are unbeaten in their last eight UCL games against Dutch opponents.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618113000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UEFA Champions League Football</title>
    <desc>UEFA Champions League action as Dutch champions PSV Eindhoven face Liverpool at Philips Stadion. Arne Slot's Reds are guaranteed to finish top of the table if they avoid defeat.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Premier League Stories</title>
    <desc>We celebrate the greatest goalscorers in Premier League history; the icons whose instinct, power, and flair have lit up stadiums and etched their names into footballing folklore. From Alan Shearer's relentless consistency to Thierry Henry's elegance, Sergio Agüero's killer instinct to Harry Kane's rise, we relive the moments that defined an era.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crouchy and Cole</title>
    <desc>Peter Crouch and Joe Cole have been going head-to-head this year, trying their hand at various sports. This is the best of.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618144500 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Filter Rugby</title>
    <desc>A special behind the scenes look at the Gallagher Premiership Rugby clash between Bath Rugby and Leicester Tigers at Twickenham.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Chicago Red Stars face Seattle Reign. This match is part of the ongoing NWSL season and promises to be an exciting encounter.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NWSL</title>
    <desc>Action from the National Women's Soccer League as Portland Thorns host Washington Spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as St Kilda take on Western Bulldogs at Marvel Stadium. With both teams having lost 3 games in the last 5, it will be a tight match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Australian Football League action as Hawthorn face Adelaide Crows at UTAS Stadium. In their last game Hawthorn break a losing streak, while Adelaide secures a win against Brisbane.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Brisbane Lions go head-to-head with GWS Giants at The Gabba. This highly anticipated match is part of Round 14 of the AFL season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Essendon face Geelong Cats at Marvel Stadium. With Geelong Cats on form, will Essendon keep possession and ensure precise ball movement for a win?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619003000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as North Melbourne take on Fremantle at Optus Stadium. Both teams have had inconsistency in their recent games. Can be anyone's game.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Port Adelaide face Melbourne at Adelaide Oval. Whilst Port Adelaide has has a mixed run lately, will Melbourne secure a victory?</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619033000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as West Coast Eagles take on Carlton at Optus Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>An afternoon to remember for all Chelsea supporters as the Blues run riot at Anfield.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619053000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Great derby victory.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We rewind back to the 2005/06 campaign as Arsenal hosted West Ham in the 2,000th match to be staged at Highbury. The Hammers were looking for their first win here in 11 years.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619063000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>A look back at the thrilling match between Sheffield United and Arsenal from the 2006/07 season. Defender Phil Jagielka would end the game in goal for the hosts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Newcastle appeared in a thrilling game against Spurs at White Hart Lane during the 2006/07 season.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619073000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>We revisit a dramatic -of-season clash at Old Trafford from 2006/07 between Manchester United and West Ham. The Hammers needed to win to pull-off an amazing relegation escape.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Relive this classic Premier League clash between Tottenham and Aston Villa at White Hart Lane. The visitors led 4-1 after 60 minutes but Tottenham staged a remarkable comeback.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619083000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prem Classics</title>
    <desc>Relive this classic Premier League clash between Burnley and Manchester United at Turf Moor. Burnley's first ever Premier League home game would be a memorable one.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belgium Tour</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Tour of Belgium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tour de Suisse</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling World Tour action from stage four of the 2025 Tour of Switzerland.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage one of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie in France.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: UCI Continental Circuits</title>
    <desc>Men's Cycling Pro Series action from stage two of the 2025 Route d'Occitanie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619143000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golden Trail World Series</title>
    <desc>A review of the fourth race of the 2025 Golden Trail World Series, as the world's best trail runners took on the Zegama-Aizkorri mountain marathon in Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the latest round of the MotoGP in Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotoGP</title>
    <desc>MotoGP highlights from the Grand Prix of Italy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619170000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Superbike World Championship Motorcycle Racing</title>
    <desc>Highlights from the Misano Round of the 2025 Superbike World Championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIM Speedway Grand Prix</title>
    <desc>Highlights from round four of the 2025 FIM Speedway Grand Prix at Manchester's National Speedway Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIA TCR World Tour</title>
    <desc>A review of the best action from the 2025 TCR World Tour in Valencia, Spain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619193000 +0000" stop="20250619203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Action from day three of the first Test between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619203000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Australian Rules</title>
    <desc>Action from the Australian Football League as Fremantle and Essendon go head-to-head.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fishing: On the Bank</title>
    <desc>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619230000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="400478" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mass Participation</title>
    <desc>Coverage from Mass Participation World.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405049">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Gym</title>
    <desc>The journey of the Toronto Raptors and other NBA stars through the season both on and off the court.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame coverage of the 2025 CONCACAF Gold Cup.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618113000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618143000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pokerstars Big Game on Tour</title>
    <desc>Professional players and poker-loving celebrities are joined by players who won seats at the table through auditions and free qualifiers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250618233000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MLB Baseball</title>
    <desc>From George M. Steinbrenner Field in Tampa, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619030000 +0000" stop="20250619040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619040000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619073000 +0000" stop="20250619083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619083000 +0000" stop="20250619093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619093000 +0000" stop="20250619103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619103000 +0000" stop="20250619113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619113000 +0000" stop="20250619123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619123000 +0000" stop="20250619133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619133000 +0000" stop="20250619143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619143000 +0000" stop="20250619153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619153000 +0000" stop="20250619163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619163000 +0000" stop="20250619173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619173000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619213000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405049" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="404833">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN2</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Grizzlie Truth</title>
    <desc>Superfan filmmaker Kat Jayme investigates the abrupt move of her NBA hometown team, the Vancouver Grizzlies, to Memphis in 2001. Much more than a sore spot, it's an unsolved mystery and possibly a criminal conspiracy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CFL on TSN: Game of the Week</title>
    <desc>A top Canadian Football League matchup from TSN.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618083000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618113000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618133000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618143000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618153000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Pat McAfee Show</title>
    <desc>Former NFL punter Pat McAfee brings his humor and candor to the microphone to highlight the day's top stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618193000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619023000 +0000" stop="20250619033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619033000 +0000" stop="20250619040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619040000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PBR Bull Riding</title>
    <desc>Coverage of classic bull riding events from around the United States.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>All Elite Wrestling continues to inject new spirit, freshness and energy into mainstream wrestling featuring a world-class roster of diverse male and female wrestlers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619073000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619083000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619093000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619103000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619113000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619123000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619133000 +0000" stop="20250619140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619140000 +0000" stop="20250619143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619143000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619153000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Pat McAfee Show</title>
    <desc>Former NFL punter Pat McAfee brings his humor and candor to the microphone to highlight the day's top stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">STIHL Timbersports</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the world's best lumberjacks competing across six events.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619183000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619193000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619203000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619213000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Overdrive</title>
    <desc>Expert analysis on the day's biggest sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619230000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404833" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="405079">
    <display-name lang="Canada">TSN5</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group B.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618033000 +0000" stop="20250618043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618043000 +0000" stop="20250618053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618053000 +0000" stop="20250618063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618063000 +0000" stop="20250618073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618073000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618163000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PGA TOUR - The Drop</title>
    <desc>The Drop blends storytelling, competition, and personality. Each week, the show dives into the intensity of tournament play, previewing what's ahead and recapping the biggest storylines, giving fans a unique look at the players on and off the course.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Golf Talk Canada</title>
    <desc>TSN's Mark Zecchino and Bob Weeks discuss the latest news in the world of golf.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618183000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619010000 +0000" stop="20250619013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619013000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Concacaf Gold Cup Soccer</title>
    <desc>Group A.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619040000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619140000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC With Jay Onrait</title>
    <desc>The latest scores and highlights, with host Jay Onrait.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2025 Motorcycle Experience</title>
    <desc>News and reviews from cycle enthusiasts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619163000 +0000" stop="20250619170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Canadian Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Shannonville Motorsport Park in Belleville, Ontario.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619170000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pokerstars Big Game on Tour</title>
    <desc>Professional players and poker-loving celebrities are joined by players who won seats at the table through auditions and free qualifiers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inbound</title>
    <desc>Documenting the shared trajectory between Canada's rise as a global basketball powerhouse and the circumstances that helped shape the country's multicultural identity.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Today</title>
    <desc>In-depth, comprehensive daily coverage of all aspects of the NBA from expert analysts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NFL Live</title>
    <desc>Host Laura Rutledge takes the helm of this weekday show featuring the likes of Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Mina Kimes, and Adam Schefter, who offer the latest news and analysis from across the NFL.Guests: Marcus Spears, Dan Orlovsky, Ryan Clark, Mina Kimes, Field Yates, Adam Schefter, Keyshawn Johnson..</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619213000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Opinions regarding the day's top sports stories.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: SportsCentre</title>
    <desc>TSN's flagship show providing news, highlights, analysis and interviews from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="405079" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SC</title>
    <desc>The best and worst from the world of sports.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
<channel id="8821">
    <display-name lang="US">Willow Cricket HDTV (WILLOWHD)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618005000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618005000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618041000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum in Oakland, Calif.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618041000 +0000" stop="20250618044000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618044000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the second Women's ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the third Women's ODI match between England and West Indies, where both teams compete to emerge victorious.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618172000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618204000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618204000 +0000" stop="20250618211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618211000 +0000" stop="20250618213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618213000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250619003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619003000 +0000" stop="20250619005000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619005000 +0000" stop="20250619010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619010000 +0000" stop="20250619041000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Major League Cricket</title>
    <desc>From Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum in Oakland, Calif.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619041000 +0000" stop="20250619044000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619044000 +0000" stop="20250619050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619050000 +0000" stop="20250619060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619060000 +0000" stop="20250619070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619070000 +0000" stop="20250619080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619080000 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619132000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619132000 +0000" stop="20250619133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619133000 +0000" stop="20250619164000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619164000 +0000" stop="20250619171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619171000 +0000" stop="20250619172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619172000 +0000" stop="20250619173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Preview</title>
    <desc>A preview of an upcoming cricket match.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619173000 +0000" stop="20250619204000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: T20 Blast</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619204000 +0000" stop="20250619211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Cricket Review</title>
    <desc>Action from cricket matches around the world.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619211000 +0000" stop="20250619213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Filler</title>
    <desc>Filler cricket programming.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619213000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250619230000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="8821" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cricket Highlights</title>
    <desc>Highlights of all the action from international cricket tournaments, where teams compete to win the prestigious title.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
